Pick your heroes and pack your bags—we’re traveling to Busan!

In our newest map, heroes will fight in the heart of South Korea, home to former professional gamer and famed MEKA pilot, D.Va. Over the past six months, I’ve worked on creating the environment and buildings within each of Busan’s three stages: Sanctuary, Downtown, and MEKA Base.

We released this map alongside our latest cinematic short featuring D.Va, Shooting Star. Because of this, we worked closely with the cinematics department to recreate the MEKA Base as closely as possible. We wanted players to feel like they’re in the film as soon as they load into the map. This is the first time we’ve done this kind of collaboration, and we think it was a success! The way the map looks in game and in the short are much more similar than our previous attempts.

That said, it’s not a straight one-to-one. In the game, in addition to looking great, a map needs to be playable and—most importantly—fun. As such, we expanded and built out parts of the MEKA Base that made it intuitive for players to understand the space they’re in and to offer unique gameplay moments. You can see one of these changes on the control point in the MEKA Base. There are three blast shields that go up and down, providing cover from enemy fire. An alarm accompanied by a flashing light and steam indicates when the shields will rise from the ground, signaling to the team that it is safe to attack the point. This is the first time we’ve intentionally designed moving terrain as part of a map’s strategy.

The whole team poured a lot of love and effort into capturing the likeness of Busan and building out the story of D.Va and South Korea. You may notice that D.Va’s room inside the MEKA Base is full of trophies she won as a professional gamer, along with a top-of-the-line gaming rig—and even a couple of cans of Nano Cola.

We really do hope that you will love playing on this map, and we’re looking forward to reading and hearing what you have to say about it!

—Simon Fuchs, Senior Environment Artist