<item>
    <title>[NEW HERO – NOW PLAYABLE] Baptiste Origin Story | Overwatch</title>
    <meta>
        <summary>b'Mobilize alongside the combat medic who made the shrewd decision to make the world a better place, one bandage... or bullet at a time: Baptiste.\n\nBegin your watch: http://buyoverwatch.com\nLike us on Facebook: http://www.facebook.com/playoverwatch\nFollow us on Twitter: http://www.twitter.com/playoverwatch\nJoin us on Instagram: https://www.instagram.com/playoverwatch' </summary>
    </meta>
    <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ZfWgcjeG83E/</link>
    <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/ZfWgcjeG83E/sddefault.jpg</thumbnail>
</item>

<item>
    <title>Developer Update | Introducing Baptiste | Overwatch</title>
    <meta>
        <summary>b"Join Jeff Kaplan as he discusses the 30th hero in OverwatchBaptiste!\nHe provides some insight into his back story, abilities, and overall strategy. Baptiste is currently available for testing on the PTR. \n\nESRB Rating: TEEN with Blood, Use of Tobacco, Violence.\n\n00:14  Jeff introduces our newest heroBaptiste!\n00:28  The backstory of Baptiste\n01:59  The gameplay of the new support hero, Baptiste\n03:37  Baptiste's secondary ability, the Immortality Field\n04:55  The Exo Boots\n06:15  Baptiste's ultimate ability, the Amplification Matrix\n07:50  Thanks for joining us and have fun testing Baptiste on the PTR!\n\nBegin your watch: http://buyoverwatch.com\nLike us on Facebook: http://www.facebook.com/playoverwatch\nFollow us on Twitter: http://www.twitter.com/playoverwatch\nJoin us on Instagram: https://www.instagram.com/playoverwatch" </summary>
    </meta>
    <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=akplvZwGJZI/</link>
    <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/akplvZwGJZI/sddefault.jpg</thumbnail>
</item>

<item>
    <title>Overwatch: NEW Hero Baptiste Gameplay! - ALL Abilities Breakdown</title>
    <meta>
        <summary>b"Overwatch's NEW Hero Batiste is finally here and in todays video we break down all of his abilities in some gameplay on the PTR! Let us know what you think to this insane new hero and be sure to drop a Like & Subscribe if you enjoyed!\n\nSubscribe here - http://bit.ly/2aN1OuO\n\nRazer makes the best equipment, check out here! http://rzr.to/lnvvm\n\nWe are YOUR OVERWATCH:\nPatreon - https://www.patreon.com/YourOverwatch\nTwitter - https://twitter.com/youroverwatchyt\n\nDiscord Server:\nhttps://discordapp.com/invite/youroverwatch\n\nFREEDO's personal channel for Overwatch esports talk and more!\nhttps://www.youtube.com/user/xfreeedo" </summary>
    </meta>
    <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=WBE5cCJWAWo/</link>
    <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/WBE5cCJWAWo/sddefault.jpg</thumbnail>
</item>

<item>
    <title>Overwatch BAPTISTE - Gameplay & Initial Impressions (PTR)</title>
    <meta>
        <summary>b'New hero Baptiste gameplay is here!  With Overwatch Hero 30 on the PTR, we finally get to test out his kit and abilities in an actual match.  Feel feels pretty fun!\n\nThanks for watching and be sure to hit LIKE, SUBSCRIBE, and NOTIFICATIONS for more Master Ian Gamer Overwatch videos!\n\nYoutube Channel: https://www.youtube.com/masteriangamer\nTwitter: https://twitter.com/masteriangamer\nChannel Avatar by: https://twitter.com/XSEIDET\n\n#Overwatch #OverwatchBaptiste #Baptiste\n\nMy Computer Specs:\nIntel i7-4790K 4.0GHz Quad-Core Processor\nGigabyte GeForce GTX 970 4GB G1 Gaming Video Card\nGigabyte GA-Z97MX-Gaming 5 Micro ATX LGA1150 Motherboard\nCrucial Ballistix Sport 32GB DDR3-1600 Memory\nCorsair CX 600W 80+ Bronze Certified Semi-Modular ATX PSU\n\nPrograms Used:\nRecording: Action! Screen Recording\nEditing: Adobe Premiere Pro CC\nGame: Overwatch (duh)' </summary>
    </meta>
    <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=cSo_8SDhOIs/</link>
    <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/cSo_8SDhOIs/sddefault.jpg</thumbnail>
</item>

<item>
    <title>1 BAPTISTE TIP for EVERY HERO ft. mL7</title>
    <meta>
        <summary>b'mL7, the esteemed Ana player from Romania has been playing a ton of Baptiste so you know we had to continue the 1 TIP series.\n\n mL7 Socials:\n- https://twitch.tv/ml7_ow\n- https://youtube.com/ml7_ow\n\nAPR 2019 Ability interaction:\n- SHIELDS block REGENERATIVE BURST\n- SHIELDS do not block IMMORTALITY FIELD\n- MEI WALL does not block IMMORTALITY FIELD\n\n\n F O L L O W  K A R Q \n\nT W I T C H: https://twitch.tv/KarQ \nI N S TA G R A M: http://instagram.com/KarQGames\nT W I T T E R: https://twitter.com/KarQGames\nD I S C O R D: https://discord.gg/karq\nF A C E B O O K: https://www.facebook.com/KarQGames/\nM E R C H: https://karqgames.com\n\nP.O. B O X: \n\nNathan Chan\nPO Box 5078 Major Mackenzie P.O\nRichmond Hill, ON, Canada\nL4S 0B7\n\n- Thank you for helping me film:\nBenpai, Thenda, shimadagans, zuyadragon, STRX,  EnderRex1, Jonhy_chew01, m4v21, Lime, Manofdoom, Th0rQc, I6M, Zodus, RandomPanda, oAnalyst, CinnamonFury, SigmaZ, BobbyWasabi,  Quaaze, Veltso, PUGKING, fzjsvyd, CountCalculus, Rising128, A_Unkempt, peachiebeans, lostmaps, ADMPolaris, Precoixious\n\n\n Music Used:\n\n Otis McDonald - Scarlet Fire https://youtu.be/8yOskhDn468\n GetSix - Chasing the Dragon https://soundcloud.com/getsixofficial\n\n#overwatch #karq #overwatchtips' </summary>
    </meta>
    <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=fkM6nbxvchk/</link>
    <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/fkM6nbxvchk/sddefault.jpg</thumbnail>
</item>

<item>
    <title>Overwatch: How to Be a PRO Baptiste - Advanced Guide</title>
    <meta>
        <summary>b'Hero 30 is a fun and challenging new skilled support character that will test your aiming mechanics and quick decision making. In this Advanced Guide we breakdown the best usage of each of Baptiste\'s abilities as utilized by some of the best supports in the world; Jjonak, Ml7 and Custa who popped off when testing hero 30. Baptiste bends the classification of "Support" yet again in Overwatch and has massive value plays, aggro fragging potential and powerful ranged healing to make a big impact all over the battlefield and we hope this video helped you get a better grip on landing these high impact skills. If you enjoyed the video, please be sure to leave it a like and don\'t forget to subscribe! \n\nStreamers Featured: \nhttps://www.twitch.tv/jjonaklove\nhttps://www.twitch.tv/ml7_ow\nhttps://www.twitch.tv/custa\n\n\nOUR VARIETY STREAM! https://www.fb.gg/yogaming\n\nSubscribe here - http://bit.ly/2aN1OuO\n\nWe are YOUR OVERWATCH:\nPatreon - https://www.patreon.com/YourOverwatch\nTwitter - https://twitter.com/youroverwatchyt\n\nDiscord Server:\nhttps://discordapp.com/invite/youroverwatch\n\nFREEDO\'s personal channel for Overwatch esports talk and more!\nhttps://www.youtube.com/user/xfreeedo' </summary>
    </meta>
    <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Dbrt2dVsqAw/</link>
    <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/Dbrt2dVsqAw/sddefault.jpg</thumbnail>
</item>

<item>
    <title>7 Important Tips to Master Baptiste (Overwatch Guide)</title>
    <meta>
        <summary>b'7 Important Tips to Master Baptiste (Overwatch Guide) Tips and tricks to learn how to play or improve your skills with Baptiste easy and rank up in competitive season 15! Carry from bronze, silver, gold, platinum, diamond and masters. If played right Baptiste can be a deadly support hero pick! Goodluck\n\nIn this video we talk about: \nOverwatch Support Hero\nOverwatch New Hero\nOverwatch Tips\nOverwatch Guide 2019\n\nNEW DISCORD: Discord: https://discord.gg/UxEVpgt\n\n\n STAY CONNECTED! \n\n\nFollow Us on Social Media!\n Discord: https://discord.gg/UxEVpgt\n Twitter: https://twitter.com/Blizzard_Guides\n UG Twitter: http://Twitter.com/UltraGuides\n UG Discord: https://discord.gg/ultra\n Twitch: http://Twitch.tv/UltraGuides\n Instagram: https://www.instagram.com/overwatch.guides\n\nSources \ntwitch.tv/ml7_ow\ntwitch.tv/custa\n___\n\n\nThat just about does it for this video guys, if you liked 7 Important Tips to Master Baptiste (Overwatch Guide) , hit that like button, if you want to see more videos like this as they are made public, subscribe. If you want to enter in some sick giveaways, you can follow us on twitter @UltraGuides. If you wanna hang with me and the other UG members, you can join our Discord server.  Thank you so much for staying till the end of the video. Stay amazing, and we will see you, in the next one.' </summary>
    </meta>
    <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=jarwW_vNIrQ/</link>
    <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/jarwW_vNIrQ/sddefault.jpg</thumbnail>
</item>

<item>
    <title>Overwatch | PRO BAPTISTE GUIDE - New Hero Tips and Tricks Ft Ml7</title>
    <meta>
        <summary>b'Baptiste is the newest hero in the game and today we sit down with ML7 to give us a bunch of new tips and tricks to play him!\nML7 - https://www.twitch.tv/ml7_ow\n CHECK OUT THIS AWESOME HEADSET WE USE http://hyperx.gg/OWCMIX (sponsored)\n POWERED BY OMEN by HP, CHECK THEM OUT! http://bit.ly/OWC_OMEN (sponsored)\n__\nFollow us!\nTwitter: https://twitter.com/OWCentral\nTwitch - Mysca: http://www.twitch.tv/mysca\nTwitch - Ryan: http://www.twitch.tv/ryancentral\n__\n\nMusic: Epidemic Sound\n\nApproaching Nirvana - Super Happy Fun Time\nhttp://youtube.com/user/approachingnirvana\nApproaching Nirvana on iTunes: https://itunes.apple.com/us/artist/approaching-nirvana/id313583565\n__\nThanks for watching!\n\n#Overwatch' </summary>
    </meta>
    <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=SYWmJnLOToc/</link>
    <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/SYWmJnLOToc/sddefault.jpg</thumbnail>
</item>

<item>
    <title>mL7 | HOW TO PLAY SUPPORT (UNRANKED TO GM) BAPTISTE - EPISODE 1 #EDUCATIONAL</title>
    <meta>
        <summary>b"Ever since Baptiste joined the Overwatch universe as hero 30 a lot of controversy surrounded him - from the lore that presented him as a changed man to how his playstyle should be and how OP or garbage tier he is.\n\nHis origin story was quickly completed with more information about his background in the last Overwatch mini event - BAPTISTES REUNION CHALLENGE, in which we got to see how Baptiste evolved into the present day and even a hint at the potential hero 31.\n\nConsidering he is a new hero everyone wants to find out how to play him and even rank up with him. Well if you're wondering the same then you are on the right video.\n\n\nI decided to do an EDUCATIONAL UNRANKED TO GM CHALLENGE with Baptiste and try my best to give you the information you need in order to rank up. I chose to make this challenge because the most asked questions in Twitch chat are regarding ranking up in competitive play, so I wanted to give you tips, the thought process and show you what you should be aware of when you're playing Baptiste (and supports in general). \n\nThis guide is mostly focused on gameplay and giving tips and tricks to the viewers while playing.\n\n Check out my video with Karq - ONE BAPTISTE TIP AGAINST EVERY HERO\nVideo link: https://youtu.be/fkM6nbxvchk\n\n Check out 7 tips on HOW TO USE BAPTISTE ULTIMATE:\nVideo link: https://youtu.be/xkdUdFIL3_I\n\n\n UNRANKED TO GM BAPTISTE ONLY\n EPISODE 2 - https://youtu.be/5Er6p3SImMI\n EPISODE 3 - https://youtu.be/V86X7KetBf4\n\nHit the  to join the notification squad!\n\n mL7s Socials:\n Twitch: https://www.twitch.tv/mL7support\n Twitter: https://twitter.com/mL7support\n Instagram: https://www.instagram.com/mL7support\n Discord: https://discord.gg/mL7\n\n PO BOX\nMihai Lupascu\nPO BOX 111, Postal Office Number 5 (Liberty Boulevard Number 1), Bucharest, Sector 5, Romania, Postal Code 040128\n\n Edit & Thumbnail by Denn\nTwitter: https://twitter.com/dennied_\n\n\n Music by Ben Lepper - Light Rider (intro)\n Video Link: https://youtu.be/s6woPUtZ-hQ\n\n Music by: Dj Quads -  Dope (outro)\n Soundcloud - https://soundcloud.com/aka-dj-quads\n Instagram - https://www.instagram.com/djquads/\n Twitter - https://twitter.com/DjQuads" </summary>
    </meta>
    <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=VO9mXU5QbDs/</link>
    <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/VO9mXU5QbDs/sddefault.jpg</thumbnail>
</item>

<item>
    <title>5 Tips EVERY BAPTISTE MUST KNOW - Gameplay Tricks to go SUPPORT GOD | Overwatch Guide</title>
    <meta>
        <summary>b" Join NOW! https://ow.gameleap.com/gameleap25 -25% OFF to Learn from Top 500 Pros and carry your games!\n Join us on DISCORD! https://discord.gg/wnz7dYh\n\nIn this Overwatch gameplay guide, pro Grandmaster coach Maniac covers 5 tips and tricks to boost your Baptiste gameplay! Follow these tips to maximize your Baptiste gameplay. Learn to master Overwatch's newest support in no time!\n\n#overwatch #gameleap #baptiste\n\nThanks for watching. If you have any questions or want to reach us, please send an email at support@game-leap.com and we will get back to you shortly." </summary>
    </meta>
    <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=J0GV9u5ElKY/</link>
    <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/J0GV9u5ElKY/sddefault.jpg</thumbnail>
</item>

