  <thumbnail>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PiDiaries/wow/master/sprays/bas.png</thumbnail>
<fanart>https://d1u1mce87gyfbn.cloudfront.net/media/screenshot/bastion-screenshot-004.jpg</fanart>
  <summary>Repair protocols and the ability to transform between stationary Assault, mobile Recon and devastating Tank configurations provide Bastion with a high probability of victory.
  
  Once a frontline combatant in the devastating Omnic Crisis, this curious Bastion unit now explores the world, fascinated by nature but wary of a fearful humanity.

Originally created for peacekeeping purposes, Bastion robot units possessed the unique ability to rapidly reconfigure themselves into an assault-cannon mode. But during the Omnic Crisis, they were turned against their human makers, forming the bulk of the omnics' rebel army. Following the resolution of the crisis, nearly all of them were destroyed or disassembled. To this day, Bastion units still symbolize the horrors of the conflict.

One unique Bastion unit, severely damaged in the final battles of the war, was left forgotten for over a decade. It lay dormant, exposed to the elements and rusting while nature slowly reclaimed it. Overgrown with vines and roots and nested upon by small animals, the robot sat inert, seemingly unaware of the passing of time. That was until one fateful day, when it unexpectedly reactivated. With its combat programming all but lost, it instead displayed an intense curiosity about the natural world and its inhabitants. This inquisitive Bastion unit set out to explore its surroundings and discover its purpose on a war-ravaged planet.

Though "Bastion" appears to be gentle—even harmless, at times—its core combat programming takes over when the unit senses danger, utilizing its entire arsenal to eliminate anything it perceives as a threat. This has led to instances of conflict with the few humans it has encountered, and has driven it to avoid populated areas in favor of the wild, uncharted regions of the world.Once a frontline combatant in the devastating Omnic Crisis, this curious Bastion unit now explores the world, fascinated by nature but wary of a fearful humanity.

Originally created for peacekeeping purposes, Bastion robot units possessed the unique ability to rapidly reconfigure themselves into an assault-cannon mode. But during the Omnic Crisis, they were turned against their human makers, forming the bulk of the omnics' rebel army. Following the resolution of the crisis, nearly all of them were destroyed or disassembled. To this day, Bastion units still symbolize the horrors of the conflict.

One unique Bastion unit, severely damaged in the final battles of the war, was left forgotten for over a decade. It lay dormant, exposed to the elements and rusting while nature slowly reclaimed it. Overgrown with vines and roots and nested upon by small animals, the robot sat inert, seemingly unaware of the passing of time. That was until one fateful day, when it unexpectedly reactivated. With its combat programming all but lost, it instead displayed an intense curiosity about the natural world and its inhabitants. This inquisitive Bastion unit set out to explore its surroundings and discover its purpose on a war-ravaged planet.

Though "Bastion" appears to be gentle—even harmless, at times—its core combat programming takes over when the unit senses danger, utilizing its entire arsenal to eliminate anything it perceives as a threat. This has led to instances of conflict with the few humans it has encountered, and has driven it to avoid populated areas in favor of the wild, uncharted regions of the world.
</summary>

################################################################################
<item>
  <title>Bastion Ability Overview</title>
  <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch/L4D1C7JU7ts</link>
  <thumbnail></thumbnail>
  <summary>Once a frontline combatant in the devastating Omnic Crisis, the curious battle automaton known as "Bastion" now explores the world, fascinated by nature but wary of a fearful humanity. Though Bastion appears to be gentle—even harmless, at times—its core combat programming takes over when the unit senses danger, utilizing its entire arsenal to eliminate anything it perceives as a threat.

Repair protocols, remote-controlled mines, and the ability to transform from an automatic rifle-wielding, mobile assault mode into a stationary siege cannon all provide Bastion with a high degree of effectiveness on the battlefield.</summary>
</item>


<item>
  <title>Overwatch - Bastion Guide - Boo Boo Doo De Doo (Tips and Advice)</title>
  <link>https://youtube.com/watch/HeY18xbRU5w</link>
  <thumbnail></thumbnail>
  <summary>This Bastion guide will show you how to effectively use him in both Scout and Sentry mode. He's all about constant repositioning. Don't forget the SURPRISE BASTION tactic too :p
  </summary>
</item>

<item>
  <title>Overwatch | Master Bastion - Tips and Tricks (ft KolorBlind)</title>
  <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch/vUv1M02Zg_8</link>
  <thumbnail></thumbnail>
</item>

<item>
  <title>Overwatch Coaching - Bastion - PLATINUM 2656 SR - [OverAnalyzed]</title>
  <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch/k7h91NVWkl0</link>
  <thumbnail>Overwatch coaching! Welcome to OverAnalyzed! In this series, we as a community help our fellow players with tips and advice on how to become better players!</thumbnail>
</item>
