################################################################################
<thumbnail>https://vignette.wikia.nocookie.net/overwatch/images/0/0e/Doomfist_portrait.png</thumbnail>
<fanart>https://techraptor.net/wp-content/uploads/2017/07/Doomfist-Numbani-Uppercut-Highlight-Intro.jpg</fanart>


################################################################################

<item>
  <title>Overwatch - PRO GUIDE! The BEST DOOMFIST in the WORLD! (Advanced Guide)</title>
  <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch/8WTPg489tsw</link>
  <thumbnail></thumbnail>
  <summary>Welcome to Overwatch Pro Guides - a brand new series focusing on ultra high level tips and advice from the BEST players in the World. Today we look at Doomfist. In this guide, the best Doomfist player in the World in competitive gives us advanceded Doomfist tips, tricks and advice! Links to ChipSa's channels below.

</summary>
</item>

<item>
  <title>Overwatch: Doomfist MAXIMUM Damage Combos - Advanced Guide</title>
  <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch/_54is1616xw</link>
  <summary>In this Overwatch advanced guide we break down how to combo your way to victory using Doomfist. These combos are hard even at their base level but mastering them is the best way to do maximum damage. Let us know what you think and be sure to drop a Like & Subscribe if you enjoyed!
  </summary>
  <item>


<item>
  <title>Overwatch: How to be a PRO DOOMFIST - Seagull & Tviq - Advanced Guide</title>
  <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch/QtbZ9MfouBk</link>
  <summary>Doomfist is a brand new hero in Overwatch Gameplay but his strengths have been quickly actualized by the best players in the world who show where he is most lethal. With a rocket punch looming every 4 seconds during the midfight, swarming heroes that fight in the scrum are always at risk to crowd control and potentially a one hit kill from the massive gauntlet. A lot is yet to be learned about Doomfist, and we're sure much is to change, but this guide is designed to teach you to take advantage of the skills the pros have developed thus far. Keep strong and Doomfist on! GL HF! -F</summary>
  <item></item>
