################################################################################
  <thumbnail>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PiDiaries/wow/master/sprays/dva.png</thumbnail>
  <fanart>https://d1u1mce87gyfbn.cloudfront.net/media/screenshot/dva-screenshot-001.jpg</fanart>



################################################################################
<item>
  <title>D.Va Ability Overview </title>
  <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch/jN3TISLTVyc</link>
  <thumbnail>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PiDiaries/wow/master/sprays/dva.png</thumbnail>
  <fanart>https://d1u1mce87gyfbn.cloudfront.net/media/screenshot/dva-screenshot-001.jpg</fanart>
  <summary>D.Va is a former professional gamer who pilots a state-of-the-art mech in defense of her homeland, charged with protecting South Korea from a colossal omnic monstrosity that periodically rises from the sea. Seeing her new mission as a game, D.Va fearlessly charges into battle alongside the rest of her MEKA unit, ready to spring to her nation’s defense at a moment’s notice. 

D.Va's mech is armed with two short-range Fusion Cannons and Boosters that can propel her over enemies and obstacles.  D.Va can also protect herself and her allies by activating her mech’s Defense Matrix to deflect incoming projectiles. If necessary, D.Va can eject from her mech and set its reactor to explode, dealing massive damage to nearby opponents while she calls down a new battle suit.</summary>
</item>

<item>
  <title>Overwatch - D.Va Guide - I Play To Win! (Tips and Advice)</title>
  <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch/52rT4Hux1ik</link>
  <summary>D.Va is an ultra mobile, high health, backfield distruption tank. She excels at rapidly moving behind the enemy's lines and causing maximum disruption. In this guide video I give advice and tips on how best to use D.Va
  </summary>
</item>




<item>
  <title>Overwatch - D.Va Tips and Advice - Bright PINK Battering RAM!</title>
  <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch/R8-S6KLBdhY</link>
  <thumbnail>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PiDiaries/wow/master/sprays/dva.png</thumbnail>
  <fanart>https://d1u1mce87gyfbn.cloudfront.net/media/screenshot/dva-screenshot-001.jpg</fanart>
  <summary>D.Va tips and advice! D.Va is the latest tank hero to hit the Overwatch Beta. She has amazing movement abilities coupled with deadly close range damage. She’s excellent for diving into the backfield and shutting down enemy supports and isolating enemies and forcing them away!
</summary>
</item>

<item>
  <title>Overwatch In Depth: D.Va Guide</title>
  <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch/RcHmP0jpQOw</link>
   <thumbnail>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PiDiaries/wow/master/sprays/dva.png</thumbnail>
  <fanart>https://d1u1mce87gyfbn.cloudfront.net/media/screenshot/dva-screenshot-001.jpg</fanart>
 <summary>D.Va is one of the tankiest tanks in Overwatch despite her recent nerfs. This D.Va guide will cover her damage on the mech shotguns, compare it to the pistol damage, explain how the defense matrix works, and share some little known secrets about the hero!</summary>
</item>

<item>
  <title>Overwatch: How to Be a PRO D.Va - Advanced Guide</title>
  <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch/2jnSvdwPGdY</link>
    <thumbnail>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PiDiaries/wow/master/sprays/dva.png</thumbnail>
  <fanart>https://d1u1mce87gyfbn.cloudfront.net/media/screenshot/dva-screenshot-001.jpg</fanart>
<summary>D. Va is a hero is the current overwatch meta and nV Mickie shows us why. In this guide FREEDO breaks down Mickie's general playstyle, crowd control skills and Self Destruct placements that make him a force to be reckoned with. Let us know what you think and be sure to drop a Like & Subscribe if you enjoyed!</summary>
</item>
