###################################################################################
<dir>
  <title></title>
  <link></link>
  <thumbnail></thumbnail>
  <fanart></fanart>
<summary></summary>
</dir>

################################################################################

<dir>
  <title>Ana</title>
  <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PiDiaries/wow/master/Overwatchleague/heroguides/ana.xml</link>
  <thumbnail>https://vignette.wikia.nocookie.net/overwatch/images/f/fd/Ana_portrait.png</thumbnail>
  <fanart>http://assets1.ignimgs.com/thumbs/neon/2016/07/12/f5595d47b8b0f498c6dc20018d5bbafd-1468375207/neon_0001_1280w.jpg</fanart>
<summary>Ana is one of the heroes in Overwatch. She is a former army sniper who has recently come out of hiding and rejoined the battle in order to protect her loved ones.

Ana’s versatile arsenal allows her to affect heroes all over the battlefield. Her Biotic Rifle rounds and Biotic Grenades heal allies and damage or impair enemies; her sidearm tranquilizes key targets, and Nano Boost gives one of her comrades a considerable increase in power.
</summary>
</dir>

<dir>
  <title>Bastion</title>
  <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PiDiaries/wow/master/Overwatchleague/heroguides/ana.xml</link>
  <thumbnail>https://vignette.wikia.nocookie.net/overwatch/images/6/6a/Bastion_portrait.png</thumbnail>
  <fanart>http://7wallpapers.net/wp-content/uploads/7_Overwatch-Bastion.jpg</fanart>
<summary>Bastion is one of the heroes in Overwatch. It is an omnic wanderer formerly built to be a war combatant, who is now travelling to satisfy its curiosity about nature and leave its horrifying past behind.

Repair protocols and the ability to transform between stationary Sentry, mobile Recon and devastating Tank configurations provide Bastion with a high probability of victory.
</summary>
</dir>

<dir>
  <title>Doomfist</title>
  <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PiDiaries/wow/master/Overwatchleague/heroguides/doomfist.xml</link>
  <thumbnail>https://vignette.wikia.nocookie.net/overwatch/images/0/0e/Doomfist_portrait.png</thumbnail>
  <fanart>https://techraptor.net/wp-content/uploads/2017/07/Doomfist-Numbani-Uppercut-Highlight-Intro.jpg</fanart>
<summary>Doomfist is one of the heroes of Overwatch. He is a zealous and cunning criminal combatant who wants to drown the world in a future of conflict to "strengthen" humanity.

Doomfist’s cybernetics make him a highly-mobile, powerful frontline fighter. In addition to dealing ranged damage with his Hand Cannon, Doomfist can slam the ground, knock enemies into the air and off balance, or charge into the fray with his Rocket Punch. When facing a tightly packed group, Doomfist leaps out of view, then crashes down to earth with a spectacular Meteor Strike.
</summary>
</dir>

<dir>
  <title>D.Va</title>
  <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PiDiaries/wow/master/Overwatchleague/heroguides/dva.xml</link>
  <thumbnail>https://vignette.wikia.nocookie.net/overwatch/images/d/dc/Dva_portrait.png</thumbnail>
  <fanart>http://7wallpapers.net/wp-content/uploads/18_Overwatch-D.Va_.jpg</fanart>
  <summary>D.Va is one of the heroes in Overwatch. She is a former professional gamer and a mech pilot who is participating in her country's special force to combat a colossal omnic's devastating invasion.

D.Va’s mech is nimble and powerful—its twin Fusion Cannons blast away with autofire at short range, and she can use its Boosters to barrel over enemies and obstacles, or deflect attacks with her projectile-dismantling Defense Matrix or blast her enemies with her Micro Missiles.
</summary>
</dir>
