###################################################################################

################################################################################
<item>
  <title>1 TIP for EVERY HERO Series</title>
  <link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/playlist/PLgRMcvKNkYFyD7RyWlNmvYF0NWcKei5z7/</link>
  <thumbnail></thumbnail>
  <summary> </summary>
</item>



<item>
  <title>Overwatch League GOD MODE Moments</title>
  <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch/ORcZDB_GXIc</link>
  <thumbnail>https://yt3.ggpht.com/-Nt2qu4F8b8Y/AAAAAAAAAAI/AAAAAAAAAAA/oPBO6AtT8RE/s288-mo-c-c0xffffffff-rj-k-no/photo.jpg</thumbnail>
  <summary> </summary>
</item>


<dir>
  <title>Ana</title>
  <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PiDiaries/wow/master/Overwatchleague/heroguides/ana.xml</link>
  <thumbnail>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PiDiaries/wow/master/sprays/ana.png</thumbnail>
  <fanart>http://7wallpapers.net/wp-content/uploads/2_Overwatch-Ana.jpg</fanart>
  <summary>Ana is one of the heroes in Overwatch. She is a former army sniper who has recently come out of hiding and rejoined the battle in order to protect her loved ones.

    Ana’s versatile arsenal allows her to affect heroes all over the battlefield. Her Biotic Rifle rounds and Biotic Grenades heal allies and damage or impair enemies; her sidearm tranquilizes key targets, and Nano Boost gives one of her comrades a considerable increase in power.
  </summary>
</dir>

<dir>
  <title>Ashe</title>
  <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PiDiaries/wow/master/Overwatchleague/heroguides/ashe.xml</link>
  <thumbnail>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PiDiaries/wow/master/sprays/ashe.png</thumbnail>
  <fanart></fanart>
  <summary></summary>
</dir>

<dir>
  <title>Bastion</title>
  <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PiDiaries/wow/master/Overwatchleague/heroguides/bastion.xml</link>
  <thumbnail>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PiDiaries/wow/master/sprays/bas.png</thumbnail>
  <fanart>http://7wallpapers.net/wp-content/uploads/7_Overwatch-Bastion.jpg</fanart>
  <summary>Bastion is one of the heroes in Overwatch. It is an omnic wanderer formerly built to be a war combatant, who is now travelling to satisfy its curiosity about nature and leave its horrifying past behind.

    Repair protocols and the ability to transform between stationary Sentry, mobile Recon and devastating Tank configurations provide Bastion with a high probability of victory.
  </summary>
</dir>

<dir>
  <title>Brigitte</title>
  <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PiDiaries/wow/master/Overwatchleague/heroguides/brigette.xml</link>
  <thumbnail>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PiDiaries/wow/master/sprays/Brigitte_Cute.png</thumbnail>
  <fanart>hhttps://i2.wp.com/www.sogogames.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/02/3358141-image1.png</fanart>
  <summary>Brigitte is one of the support heroes of Overwatch. She is a skilled metalsmith and mechanic, who accompanies Reinhardt as he wanders across Europe. She is the youngest daughter of Torbjörn and his wife Ingrid.
  </summary>
</dir>

<dir>
  <title>Doomfist</title>
  <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PiDiaries/wow/master/Overwatchleague/heroguides/doomfist.xml</link>
  <thumbnail>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PiDiaries/wow/master/sprays/Doomspray_cute.png</thumbnail>
  <fanart>https://techraptor.net/wp-content/uploads/2017/07/Doomfist-Numbani-Uppercut-Highlight-Intro.jpg</fanart>
  <summary>Doomfist is one of the heroes of Overwatch. He is a zealous and cunning criminal combatant who wants to drown the world in a future of conflict to "strengthen" humanity.

    Doomfist’s cybernetics make him a highly-mobile, powerful frontline fighter. In addition to dealing ranged damage with his Hand Cannon, Doomfist can slam the ground, knock enemies into the air and off balance, or charge into the fray with his Rocket Punch. When facing a tightly packed group, Doomfist leaps out of view, then crashes down to earth with a spectacular Meteor Strike.
  </summary>
</dir>

<dir>
  <title>D.Va</title>
  <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PiDiaries/wow/master/Overwatchleague/heroguides/dva.xml</link>
  <thumbnail>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PiDiaries/wow/master/sprays/dva.png</thumbnail>
  <fanart>http://7wallpapers.net/wp-content/uploads/18_Overwatch-D.Va_.jpg</fanart>
  <summary>D.Va is one of the heroes in Overwatch. She is a former professional gamer and a mech pilot who is participating in her country's special force to combat a colossal omnic's devastating invasion.

    D.Va’s mech is nimble and powerful—its twin Fusion Cannons blast away with autofire at short range, and she can use its Boosters to barrel over enemies and obstacles, or deflect attacks with her projectile-dismantling Defense Matrix or blast her enemies with her Micro Missiles.
  </summary>
</dir>

<dir>
  <title>Genji</title>
  <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PiDiaries/wow/master/Overwatchleague/heroguides/genji.xml</link>
  <thumbnail>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PiDiaries/wow/master/sprays/genji.png</thumbnail>
  <fanart>http://7wallpapers.net/wp-content/uploads/1_Overwatch-Genji.jpg</fanart>
  <summary>Genji is an offense hero in Overwatch. He is a cyborg ninja who has freed himself from his criminal past and the war with his cybernetic body.

    Genji flings precise and deadly Shuriken at his targets and uses his technologically-advanced wakizashi to deflect projectiles or deliver a Swift Strike that cuts down enemies.
  </summary>
</dir>


<dir>
  <title>Hanzo</title>
  <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PiDiaries/wow/master/Overwatchleague/heroguides/hanzo.xml</link>
  <thumbnail>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PiDiaries/wow/master/sprays/hanzo.png</thumbnail>
  <fanart>http://7wallpapers.net/wp-content/uploads/6_Overwatch-Hanzo.jpg</fanart>
  <summary>Hanzo is one of the heroes in Overwatch. He is a mercenary archer who is on the path of redemption to restore his honor and atone for the atrocity he once committed as the heir of a syndicate.

    Hanzo’s versatile arrows can reveal his enemies or fragment to strike multiple targets. He can scale walls to fire his bow from on high, or summon titanic spirit dragons.
  </summary>
</dir>

<dir>
  <title>Junkrat</title>
  <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PiDiaries/wow/master/Overwatchleague/heroguides/junkrat.xml</link>
  <thumbnail>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PiDiaries/wow/master/sprays/junk.png</thumbnail>
  <fanart>http://7wallpapers.net/wp-content/uploads/8_Overwatch-Junkrat.jpg</fanart>
  <summary>Junkrat is one of the heroes in Overwatch. He is a demolitionist and an international criminal who is being targeted by law-keepers, bounty hunters and other criminals world-wide for the treasure in his possession.

    Junkrat’s area-denying traps include a custom designed Frag Launcher that lobs bouncing grenades, Concussion Mines that send enemies flying, and Steel Traps that stop foes dead in their tracks and make them vulnerable to your attacks.
  </summary>
</dir>

<dir>
  <title>Lucio</title>
  <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PiDiaries/wow/master/Overwatchleague/heroguides/lucio.xml</link>
  <thumbnail>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PiDiaries/wow/master/sprays/lucio.png</thumbnail>
  <fanart>http://7wallpapers.net/wp-content/uploads/14_Overwatch-Lucio.jpg</fanart>
  <summary>Lúcio is one of the heroes in Overwatch. He is an international musician who uses his music to obliterate the authoritarian control and inspire social change.

    On the battlefield, Lúcio’s cutting-edge Sonic Amplifier buffets enemies with projectiles and knocks foes back with blasts of sound. His songs can both heal his team or boost their movement speed, and he can switch between tracks on the fly.


  </summary>
</dir>

<dir>
  <title>McCree</title>
  <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PiDiaries/wow/master/Overwatchleague/heroguides/mccree.xml</link>
  <thumbnail>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PiDiaries/wow/master/sprays/mccree.png</thumbnail>
  <fanart>http://7wallpapers.net/wp-content/uploads/6_Overwatch-McCree.jpg</fanart>
  <summary>McCree is one of the heroes in Overwatch. He is an outlaw gunslinger and former gang member who fights for the principle of righteousness.

    Using his Peacekeeper, McCree takes out targets with deadeye precision and dives out of danger with eagle-like speed.
  </summary>
</dir>

<dir>
  <title>Mei</title>
  <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PiDiaries/wow/master/Overwatchleague/heroguides/mei.xml</link>
  <thumbnail>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PiDiaries/wow/master/sprays/mei.png</thumbnail>
  <fanart>http://7wallpapers.net/wp-content/uploads/1_Overwatch-Mei.jpg</fanart>
  <summary>Mei is one of the heroes in Overwatch. She is a climatologist who is on her own adventure to preserve the environment and ecosystem after waking up from a decade-long cryostasis sleep.

    Mei’s weather-altering devices slow opponents and protect locations. Her Endothermic Blaster unleashes damaging icicles and frost streams, and she can Cryo-Freeze herself to guard against counterattacks or obstruct the opposing team's movements with an Ice Wall.
  </summary>
</dir>

<dir>
  <title>Mercy</title>
  <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PiDiaries/wow/master/Overwatchleague/heroguides/mercy.xml</link>
  <thumbnail>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PiDiaries/wow/master/sprays/mercy.png</thumbnail>
  <fanart>http://7wallpapers.net/wp-content/uploads/2_Overwatch-Mercy.jpg</fanart>
  <summary>Mercy is one of the heroes in Overwatch. She is a nanobiologist and a field medic who always stays at the frontline of wars and crises around the world to heal the wounded and imperiled.

    Mercy’s Valkyrie Suit helps keep her close to teammates like a guardian angel so Mercy can heal, resurrecting or strengthening them with the beams emanating from her Caduceus Staff.
  </summary>
</dir>

<dir>
  <title>Moira</title>
  <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PiDiaries/wow/master/Overwatchleague/heroguides/moira.xml</link>
  <thumbnail>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PiDiaries/wow/master/sprays/Moira_Cute.png</thumbnail>
  <fanart>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/X9k6RLtfSSE/maxresdefault.jpg</fanart>
  <summary></summary>
</dir>

<dir>
  <title>Orisa</title>
  <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PiDiaries/wow/master/Overwatchleague/heroguides/Orisa.xml</link>
  <thumbnail>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PiDiaries/wow/master/sprays/Orisa_cute.png</thumbnail>
  <fanart>https://assets.vg247.com/current/2017/03/overwatch_orisa_origins_art.jpg</fanart>
  <summary>Orisa is one of the heroes in Overwatch. She is a guardian omnic who has currently existed for only a month and has already taken the role of her city's protector.

    Orisa serves as the central anchor of her team, and defends her teammates from the frontline with a protective barrier. She can attack from long range, fortify her own defenses, launch graviton charges to slow and move enemies, and deploy a Supercharger to boost the damage output of multiple allies at once.
  </summary>
</dir>

<dir>
  <title>Pharah</title>
  <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PiDiaries/wow/master/Overwatchleague/heroguides/pharah.xml</link>
  <thumbnail>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PiDiaries/wow/master/sprays/pharah.png</thumbnail>
  <fanart>http://7wallpapers.net/wp-content/uploads/6_Overwatch-Pharah.jpg</fanart>
  <summary>Pharah is one of the heroes in Overwatch. She is a security captain who yearns to protect the world's peace, like the heroes in her past.

    Soaring through the air in her combat armor, and armed with a launcher that lays down high-explosive rockets, Pharah is a force to be reckoned with.
  </summary>
</dir>

<dir>
  <title>Reaper</title>
  <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PiDiaries/wow/master/Overwatchleague/heroguides/reaper.xml</link>
  <thumbnail>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PiDiaries/wow/master/sprays/reaper.png</thumbnail>
  <fanart>http://7wallpapers.net/wp-content/uploads/15_Overwatch-Reaper.jpg</fanart>
  <summary>Reaper is one of the heroes in Overwatch. He is a wraith-like terrorist who sets out to kill his former comrades to feed his desire for revenge. His Hellfire Shotguns, the ghostly ability to become immune to damage, and the power to step between shadows make Reaper one of the deadliest beings on Earth.
  </summary>
</dir>

<dir>
  <title>Reinhardt</title>
  <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PiDiaries/wow/master/Overwatchleague/heroguides/reinhardt.xml</link>
  <thumbnail>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PiDiaries/wow/master/sprays/rein.png</thumbnail>
  <fanart>http://7wallpapers.net/wp-content/uploads/7_Overwatch-Reinhardt.jpg</fanart>
  <summary>Reinhardt is one of the heroes in Overwatch. He is a wandering knight who continues to fight for justice and defend the innocence undeterred by the toll of his age.

    Clad in powered armor and swinging his hammer, Reinhardt leads a rocket-propelled charge across the battleground and defends his squadmates with a massive energy barrier.
  </summary>
</dir>

<dir>
  <title>Roadhog</title>
  <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PiDiaries/wow/master/Overwatchleague/heroguides/roadhog.xml</link>
  <thumbnail>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PiDiaries/wow/master/sprays/hog.png</thumbnail>
  <fanart>http://7wallpapers.net/wp-content/uploads/19_Overwatch-Roadhog.jpg</fanart>
  <summary>Roadhog is one of the heroes in Overwatch. He is a bodyguard and an international criminal who is infamous for being an unforgiving cutthroat with a destructive and cruel nature.

    Roadhog uses his signature Chain Hook to pull his enemies close before shredding them with blasts from his Scrap Gun. He’s hardy enough to withstand tremendous damage, and can recover his health with a short breather.
  </summary>
</dir>



<dir>
  <title>Soldier: 76</title>
  <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PiDiaries/wow/master/Overwatchleague/heroguides/76.xml</link>
  <thumbnail>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PiDiaries/wow/master/sprays/soldier.png</thumbnail>
  <fanart>http://7wallpapers.net/wp-content/uploads/14_Soldier-76.jpg</fanart>
  <summary>Soldier: 76 is one of the heroes in Overwatch. He is a vigilante who aims to bring the enemies who brought down his former organization to the light of justice.

    Armed with cutting-edge weaponry, including an experimental pulse rifle that’s capable of firing spirals of high-powered Helix Rockets, Soldier: 76 has the speed and support know-how of a highly trained soldier.
  </summary>
</dir>


<dir>
  <title>Sombra</title>
  <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PiDiaries/wow/master/Overwatchleague/heroguides/sombra.xml</link>
  <thumbnail>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PiDiaries/wow/master/sprays/sombra.png</thumbnail>
  <fanart>http://www.newhdwallpapers.in/wp-content/uploads/2016/12/Game-Sombra-Overwatch-1080p.jpg</fanart>
  <summary>Sombra is one of the heroes in Overwatch. She is a hacker who has hidden within the shadows to find a global conspiracy that she once encountered.

    In game, stealth and debilitating attacks make Sombra a powerful infiltrator. Her hacking can disrupt her enemies, ensuring they're easier to take out, while her EMP provides the upper hand against multiple foes at once. Sombra’s ability to Translocate and camouflage herself makes her a hard target to pin down.
  </summary>
</dir>


<dir>
  <title>Symmetra</title>
  <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PiDiaries/wow/master/Overwatchleague/heroguides/Symmetra.xml</link>
  <thumbnail>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PiDiaries/wow/master/sprays/sym.png</thumbnail>
  <fanart>http://7wallpapers.net/wp-content/uploads/12_Overwatch-Symmetra.jpg</fanart>
  <summary>Symmetra is one of the heroes in Overwatch. She is a light-bending architech who weaves her construction in order and perfection to create a better world.

    Symmetra utilizes her light-bending Photon Projector to dispatch adversaries, shield her associates, construct teleportation pads and deploy particle-blasting Sentry Turrets.
  </summary>
</dir>

<dir>
  <title>Torbjorn</title>
  <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PiDiaries/wow/master/Overwatchleague/heroguides/torbjorn.xml</link>
  <thumbnail>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PiDiaries/wow/master/sprays/torb.png</thumbnail>
  <fanart>http://7wallpapers.net/wp-content/uploads/1_Overwatch-Torbjorn.jpg</fanart>
  <summary>Torbjörn is one of the heroes in Overwatch. He is an engineer specializing in advanced weapon design and is determined to keep his inventions from falling into the wrong hands.

    Torbjörn’s extensive arsenal includes a rivet gun and hammer, as well as a personal forge that he can use to build upgrade-able turrets and dole out protective armor packs.
  </summary>
</dir>

<dir>
  <title>Tracer</title>
  <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PiDiaries/wow/master/Overwatchleague/heroguides/tracer.xml</link>
  <thumbnail>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PiDiaries/wow/master/sprays/tracer.png</thumbnail>
  <fanart>http://7wallpapers.net/wp-content/uploads/2_Overwatch-Tracer.jpg</fanart>
  <summary>Tracer is one of the heroes in Overwatch. She is a time-jumping adventurer who is always willing to fight for the virtuous in the face of her life-threatening chronal disassociation condition.

    Toting twin pulse pistols, energy-based time bombs, and rapid-fire banter, Tracer is able to "blink" through space and rewind her personal timeline as she battles to right wrongs the world over.
  </summary>
</dir>

<dir>
  <title>Widowmaker</title>
  <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PiDiaries/wow/master/Overwatchleague/heroguides/widowmaker.xml</link>
  <thumbnail>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PiDiaries/wow/master/sprays/widow.png</thumbnail>
  <fanart>http://7wallpapers.net/wp-content/uploads/4_Overwatch-Widowmaker.jpg</fanart>
  <summary>Widowmaker is one of the heroes in Overwatch. She is an assassin who possesses no emotion except for the satisfaction of her targets' elimination.

    Widowmaker equips herself with whatever it takes to eliminate her targets, including mines that dispense poisonous gas, a visor that grants her squad infra-sight, and a powerful sniper rifle that can fire in fully-automatic mode.
  </summary>
</dir>

<dir>
  <title>Winston</title>
  <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PiDiaries/wow/master/Overwatchleague/heroguides/winston.xml</link>
  <thumbnail>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PiDiaries/wow/master/sprays/winston.png</thumbnail>
  <fanart>http://7wallpapers.net/wp-content/uploads/17_Overwatch-Winston.jpg</fanart>
  <summary>Winston is one of the heroes in Overwatch. He is a scientist and fighter who possesses the strength and intellect to venture beyond the limit of humanity.

    Winston wields impressive inventions—a jump pack, an electricity-blasting Tesla Cannon, a portable barrier projector and more—with literal gorilla strength.
  </summary>
</dir>

<dir>
  <title>Wrecking Ball - Hammond</title>
  <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PiDiaries/wow/master/Overwatchleague/heroguides/wreck.xml</link>
  <thumbnail>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PiDiaries/wow/master/sprays/hammond.png</thumbnail>
  <fanart></fanart>
  <summary></summary>
</dir>

<dir>
  <title>Zarya</title>
  <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PiDiaries/wow/master/Overwatchleague/heroguides/zarya.xml</link>
  <thumbnail>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PiDiaries/wow/master/sprays/zarya.png</thumbnail>
  <fanart>http://7wallpapers.net/wp-content/uploads/17_Overwatch-Zarya.jpg</fanart>
  <summary>Zarya is one of the heroes in Overwatch. She is a former weightlifting athlete who had sacrificed her fame and fortune to serve her country and her people in times of need.

    Deploying powerful personal barriers that convert incoming damage into energy for her massive Particle Cannon, Zarya is an invaluable asset on the front lines of any battle.
  </summary>
</dir>

<dir>
  <title>Zenyatta</title>
  <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PiDiaries/wow/master/Overwatchleague/heroguides/zenyatta.xml</link>
  <thumbnail>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PiDiaries/wow/master/sprays/zen.png</thumbnail>
  <fanart>http://7wallpapers.net/wp-content/uploads/1_Overwatch-Zenyatta.jpg</fanart>
  <summary>Zenyatta is one of the heroes in Overwatch. He is an omnic guru who wants to prove his purpose of mending the problems between humans and omnics through interpersonal connection and engagement.

    Zenyatta calls upon orbs of harmony and discord to heal his teammates and weaken his opponents, all while pursuing a transcendent state of immunity to damage.
  </summary>
</dir>
