#################################################################################
  <thumbnail>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PiDiaries/wow/master/sprays/junk.png</thumbnail>
  <fanart>https://d1u1mce87gyfbn.cloudfront.net/media/screenshot/junkrat-screenshot-002.jpg</fanart>
  <summary>Junkrat’s area-denying armaments include a Frag Launcher that lobs bouncing grenades, Concussion Mines that send enemies flying, and Steel Traps that stop foes dead in their tracks.
   Junkrat is an explosives-obsessed freak who lives to cause chaos and destruction.

The attack on the Australian omnium's fusion core forever altered the landscape of the Outback. After the detonation, the area was transformed into a harsh, irradiated wasteland, littered with debris and the twisted fragments of the ruined facility, and unlivable to most.

But there were some who survived. Calling themselves the Junkers, they scavenged the husk of the omnium and formed a lawless, cutthroat society in its shadow. Junkrat was one of them, eking out a living reclaiming metal and components from the ruins. Like many others, he was affected by the lingering radiation. This touch of madness made him ideal for handling dangerous explosives, a love which he turned into an obsession.

He came to notoriety when he discovered an extremely valuable secret in the bones of the omnium. Though few knew the nature of what he found, he was nonetheless pursued by bounty hunters, gangs, and opportunists wherever he went, until he made a deal with the Junker enforcer Roadhog, who grudgingly agreed to be his personal bodyguard in exchange for a fifty-fifty share of the spoils.

Now, with Roadhog in tow, Junkrat has left the Outback, and embarked upon an international crime spree leaving nothing but havoc and bedlam in his wake.
</summary>

################################################################################
<item>
  <title>Overwatch - Junkrat Guide - Anyone Want Some BBQ?! (Tips and Advice)</title>
  <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch/Yg0XzmK-dUU</link>
  <thumbnail></thumbnail>
  <summary>Junkrat, everyone's favourite deranged explosive addict! This Junkrat guide video will give you tips and advice on how to play him. From his Concussion Mine to Steel trap, Junkrat has a whole host of tools at his disposal! Oh and don’t forget, he leaves a nice explosive present behind after he dies :D
  </summary>
</item>
