<item>
    <title>Mei Ability Overview | Overwatch</title>
    <meta>
        <summary>b"Our world is worth fighting for: http://blizz.ly/MeetMei \n\nWhile investigating unexplained climate phenomena from Watchpoint: Antarctica, Mei and her fellow scientists were forced to enter cryostasis to survive a catastrophic polar storm. Emerging years later, Mei found that many of the issues had worsened, and she was more determined than ever to track down the causes of the threats to the planet's ecosystem. \n\nOn her adventures, Mei employs her weather-altering inventions to slow opponents and protect locations. She can use her Endothermic Blaster to freeze enemies, launch damaging ice shards, and create Ice Walls that can obstruct movement and block incoming fire. In a life-threatening emergency, she can enter Cryo-Freeze to protect herself from harm or transform the battlefield with her drone, unleashing a Blizzard in the middle of a group of enemies, freezing them solid.\n\nPre-Purchase Now: http://blizz.ly/BuyOverwatch \nSign-up for Beta: http://bit.ly/JoinOverwatch \nLike Us on Facebook: http://www.facebook.com/playoverwatch \nFollow Us on Twitter: http://www.twitter.com/playoverwatch" </summary>
    </meta>
    <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=J4hB88uMY8k/</link>
    <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/J4hB88uMY8k/sddefault.jpg</thumbnail>
</item>

<item>
    <title>Overwatch - Mei Guide - Sorry, Sorry, Sorry! (Tips and Advice)</title>
    <meta>
        <summary>b"Mei is Bae. Did I just say that? :D Mei is an insanely durable brawler/disruption hero. This lady can stand toe to toe with practically any hero, she also has fantastic crowd control abilities such as her Ice walls and freeze attack! Mei really is bae. This video gives some solid Mei tips and advice.\n\n PATREON CAMPAIGN! http://www.patreon.com/unitlost\n Steam Curator Page http://store.steampowered.com/curator/2666675/\n SUBSCRIBE! https://www.youtube.com/subscription_center?add_user=unitlosttube\n http://www.unitlost.com - Join our AWESOME community forums!\n T-shirts! http://unitlost.spreadshirt.co.uk/\n Sty's Twitter https://twitter.com/unitlostgaming\n Kiri's Twitter https://twitter.com/kirioth\n Live Stream http://www.twitch.tv/unitlost" </summary>
    </meta>
    <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Tu1uNtZ0o5Q/</link>
    <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/Tu1uNtZ0o5Q/sddefault.jpg</thumbnail>
</item>

<item>
    <title>MEI TIPS and TRICKS (Season 12) | Overwatch Guide</title>
    <meta>
        <summary>b' Join NOW! https://ow.gameleap.com/ - Learn from Top 500 Pros and carry your games!\n\nThis Overwatch guide covers 4 tips and tricks for Mei, current in Season 11! Tilt your enemies with perfect Ice Walls and EZ emotes.\n\nThanks for watching. If you have any questions or want to reach us, please send an email at support@game-leap.com and we will get back to you shortly.' </summary>
    </meta>
    <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Z-oacUZNL84/</link>
    <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/Z-oacUZNL84/sddefault.jpg</thumbnail>
</item>

<item>
    <title>STUCK IN PLAT -  Mei Gameplay Tips and Tricks| Overwatch Guide</title>
    <meta>
        <summary>b' Join NOW! https://ow.gameleap.com/ - Learn from Top 500 Pros and carry your games!\n\nArtorigold coaches a Plat Mei on how to improve in this stuck in plat series, mei gameplay tips and tricks Overwatch Guide\n\nThanks for watching. If you have any questions or want to reach us, please send an email at support@game-leap.com and we will get back to you shortly.' </summary>
    </meta>
    <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=QEZefI0ndnI/</link>
    <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/QEZefI0ndnI/sddefault.jpg</thumbnail>
</item>

<item>
    <title>JARDIO - GRANDMASTER MEI GAMEPLAY TIPS | How To Improve As Mei Guide - Overwatch Season 7</title>
    <meta>
        <summary>b"Today we are back again trying a top 500 tip Mei video because I think its fun and people just love Mei it seems. Today we are talking about how the grandmaster Mei player can carry his competitive games in season 7 overwatch competitive ranked mode guide for overwatch season 7 placement matches and overwatch season 7 changes. Going over some Mei season 7 tips and guide or whatever you want to call it. I hope that these tips can help to have you guys learn how to improve as Mei and hope this works as a mini Mei guide tip trick thing for all that want to improve as her. Anyways, thanks! \n\n\n\n\nMore GM Gameplay Tip Videos Here! : https://www.youtube.com/playlist?list=PLefC4eOMnbRF5Xm7uCjfU73bh0ybup9Df\n\n\n\nGameplay: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=2pvRs0A_YTU\nThumbnail:https://img00.deviantart.net/7438/i/2016/166/8/d/overwatch__mei_by_xephrosart-da6ayto.jpg\n-----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------\n\n\n\n======================================================================\n\nTIPS I WROTE DOWN FROM THE VIDEO:\n--Mei doesnt need a shield comp to push on offense, she works well with zarya/hog/dva\n-spam iciles always, if you know where somebody may be just spam it at head height. there is no negative to this\n-the second you get a pick, GO IN, try to ice wall block someone for a kill or just walk up and freeze people\n-he plays really close to walls, mei in the open kind sucks and is super luck based, but next to walls is consistant\n-you can go in without your abilities, but if you do stay next to a tank\n-at far range if the enemy doesnt know where you are go for headshots, but if its a 1v1 go for neckshots\n-use ice wall to get on high ground, and then drop down ult\n-call out when you will use ice wall, and if you split up at least 2 of the enemy team GO HAM\n-many times on offense he hides behind the enemy, mei can catch people out easily with freeze/icicle combos\n-if he is next to his team he tries to freeze people, but in most 1v1 he just goes for icicles\n-most his shots seem to be tracking the enemy, then flicking to where he thinks they will go\n\n-even on defense you dont need a shield tank, you just need your team to dive when you wlal people off\n-Spam your ice from high ground, projectile are just better there\n-cryofreze yourself when you get below 1/4th hp, dont risk it for a kill\n-on defense when he is going for a far kill he often just icicles towards their main body so he doesnt miss\n-guess where the opponent is PROBABLY going to go when shooting, not where they are\n-its nice on defense to play mei with a more consistant dps like mccree/soldier, offense it doesnt matter as much\n-hiding next to walls to catch people off is classic but works\n-you can jump and look up a bit to make your ult shoot a bit further.\n-if you are winning a fight, dont waste your ult fora f re last kills. Its meis only good thing in teamfights\n-try to spook away the enemy flankers, keep tying to freeze/wall them. doesnt matter if you kill them...\n-he keeps hiding behind enemies to try to spawn camp a bit... and it works kinda\n-when stalling, dont ult until you have already used your e. if you are only one left ult after you cryfreze\n-even if you cant freeze an enemy tank, slowing them down to make them an easy target is worth your time\n\n======================================================================\n\n\n\n\n\nHow GRANDMASTER Players DESTORY with Mei - Overwatch Top 500 PRO Tricks Overwatch - 20 TricksMei Grandmasters ABUSE That You Don't! Some tips and tricks to master Mei! Overwatch - 7 OP Tips and Tricks Grandmaster Players use every game! Mei overwatch, Mei guide top 500 tips and tricks  Mei master gameplay, how Mei is played, JARDIO gameplay Mei overwatch competitive esports vod grandmaster Mei tricks grandmaster top 500 Mei, overwatch top 700 Mei esports vod Mei esports gameplay, grandmaster Mei tricks top 500 tricks tips, how to play Mei, Mei season 7, overwatch competitive season 7 Mei, Mei season 7 offense, Mei season 7 defense, overwatch season 7 Mei guide       overwatch,Mei tricks,Tricks Mei Grandmasters ABUSE That You Don't,Tricks Mei Grandmasters ABUSE That You Don't overwatch,overwatch Tricks Mei Grandmasters ABUSE That You Don't,tricks grandmasters abuse that you dont,overwatch tricks grandmasters abuse that you dont,grandmaster tricks overwatch,Mei grandmaster,Mei top 500 trick,How GRANDMASTER Players DESTROY with Mei,Mei season 7 competitive,Mei vod,grandmaster, Mei JARDIO, JARDIO Mei, best Mei, strongest Mei, best Mei player, overwatch JARDIO\n\n\n\nTitle:GRANDMASTER Mei GAMEPLAY TIPS | How To Improve As Mei Guide - Overwatch Season 7 Competitive Tricks" </summary>
    </meta>
    <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=LATwQvyZiLg/</link>
    <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/LATwQvyZiLg/sddefault.jpg</thumbnail>
</item>

<item>
    <title>Overwatch Advanced Mei Guide - Devastating Ice Wall Tips</title>
    <meta>
        <summary>b'Mei is quickly becoming one of my favorite heroes in overwatch, this advanced guide will show you how to get the true potential out of her ice wall ability and decimate the enemy team.\nSubscribe here: https://www.youtube.com/c/youroverwatch?sub_confirmation=1\n\nWe are YOUR OVERWATCH:\nTwitch - https://www.twitch.tv/youroverwatch \nTwitter - https://twitter.com/youroverwatchyt\nSubscribe - http://bit.ly/2aN1OuO' </summary>
    </meta>
    <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=y62J39_UWVQ/</link>
    <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/y62J39_UWVQ/sddefault.jpg</thumbnail>
</item>

<item>
    <title>1 MEI TIP for EVERY HERO ft. Jardio</title>
    <meta>
        <summary>b'Rise and Shine! Mei is one of the least played heroes in competitive so Jardio is here to change that. He shares with you 1 Mei tip vs every hero because he is arguably the #1 and best Mei in the high competitive ladder.\n\nFOLLOW JARDIO:\n\nhttps://twitch.tv/jardio\nhttps://www.youtube.com/user/Jardio97\n\n\n\nTwitch  https://twitch.tv/KarQ (Stream 5x weekly)\nMerch  https://teespring.com/stores/karq  \nDiscord  https://discord.gg/karq\nTwitter  https://twitter.com/KarQGames\nInstagram  http://instagram.com/KarQGames\nFacebook  https://www.facebook.com/KarQGames/\n\n\n Music Used:\n\n Otis McDonald - Scarlet Fire https://youtu.be/8yOskhDn468\n .. - Himmel\n- https://youtu.be/e2onUH7L4tU\n- https://soundcloud.com/himmeltengoku/remix-accompaniment-verfc-aquatrax-4ever' </summary>
    </meta>
    <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=DSOmqK70osY/</link>
    <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/DSOmqK70osY/sddefault.jpg</thumbnail>
</item>

<item>
    <title>Overwatch Advanced Mei Guide - Game Saving Ultimate Tips</title>
    <meta>
        <summary>b'Mei is quickly becoming one of my favorite heroes in overwatch, this advanced guide will show you how to get the true potential out of her ultimate blizzard ability and decimate the enemy team.\nICE WALL GUIDE https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=y62J39_UWVQ\nSubscribe here: https://www.youtube.com/c/youroverwatch?sub_confirmation=1\nWe are YOUR OVERWATCH:\nTwitch - https://www.twitch.tv/youroverwatch \nTwitter - https://twitter.com/youroverwatchyt\nSubscribe - http://bit.ly/2aN1OuO' </summary>
    </meta>
    <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=8bINNCDr2zY/</link>
    <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/8bINNCDr2zY/sddefault.jpg</thumbnail>
</item>

<item>
    <title>Overwatch In Depth: Mei Guide</title>
    <meta>
        <summary>b'Second Channel: http://www.youtube.com/drift0rplays\nSombra In Depth: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=dkK-itKSdGA\nPlease forgive me for playing Mei. Normally I don\'t try to tilt people off the face of the earth but I had for In Depth. Mei has some interesting stats but not really trumps her intangible and powerful wall.\nMy Twitter: http://www.twitter.com/drift0r\n\nSecond Channel: http://www.youtube.com/c/drift0rplays\nTwitter: http://www.twitter.com/drift0r\n\nI only use ASTRO Headsets. This link gives you 5% off in checkout: http://bit.ly/1NIzdQi\n\nDrift0r Scuf Controller: http://scufgaming.com/shop/scufone/driftor-scuf-one/\nUse coupon code "DRFT" for 5% off!\n\nDrift0r Hoodies & Shirts: http://www.coregamewear.com/drift0r\n\nMy gaming Router is the Netduma R1: http://www.netduma.com/\nUse code "DRFT" for $10 off!\n\nAll console gameplay captured with Elgato HD60 Pro: http://e.lga.to/DriftorAmazon' </summary>
    </meta>
    <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=7iY5emWDnh0/</link>
    <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/7iY5emWDnh0/sddefault.jpg</thumbnail>
</item>

<item>
    <title>[4K 60] The Most Comprehensive Mei Guide - Aim, Movement, Strategy</title>
    <meta>
        <summary>b'Everything you need to know to become a Mei main. Since Ana\'s no longer viable, Mei\'s the next best hero to play, so be sure to try her out as learning her will improve your aim in anticipation for whenever Ana *is* viable again.\n\nAlthough Mei is niche, there\'s a lot of fun to be had just shooting popsicles at people, especially at range. Her popsicles are similar to Ana\'s sleep darts. If you have any questions, feel free to ask and I\'ll answer.\n\nMy aim is ameizingly consistent, so the highlights aren\'t just "good clips" that I cherry picked out of the games. Feel free to watch me on stream if you don\'t believe me :P\n\nTwitch: http://Twitch.tv/zStella' </summary>
    </meta>
    <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=oKB94zsPoyM/</link>
    <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/oKB94zsPoyM/sddefault.jpg</thumbnail>
</item>

<item>
    <title>MEI - Overwatch One Trick Guide</title>
    <meta>
        <summary>b"Hey Mei, I don't like you.\n\nTwitter - https://twitter.com/BrickyOrchid8\nTwitch - http://www.twitch.tv/brickyorchid8\nBigBrickPlays - https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCHcODW8jrSHWw7Na0dC6qcA\nInstagram - BrickyOrchid8\n\nIronside Computers | Click here to customize your own PC -  http://ironsidecomputers.com\n\nLF Gaming Chairs - https://lfgaming.com/shop/?ref=11\n\nP.O. Box\nBrickyOrchid8\n22365 El Toro Road.\nLake Forest, CA 92630\n#338\n\nAll P.O BOX items sent will be opened every other week!" </summary>
    </meta>
    <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=aLrwzfqhlEs/</link>
    <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/aLrwzfqhlEs/sddefault.jpg</thumbnail>
</item>

<item>
    <title>Overwatch - How to Mei (Tips, Tricks & Counters) & Achievements/Trophies</title>
    <meta>
        <summary>b'Overwatch - How to Mei (Tips, Tricks & Counters) & Achievements/Trophies\n\nIce Blocked - Block 1200 damage with a single use of Mei\'s Ice Wall in Quick or Competitive Play\nCold Snap - Freeze 4 enemies at once with Mei in Quick or Competitive Play\n\nOverwatch Playlist:\nhttps://www.youtube.com/playlist?list=PLBmi6vaTfD_cVrZE9V8HnAWPBzetl-XSK\nSubscribe:\nhttp://www.youtube.com/subscription_center?add_user=Maka91Productions\n\nSupport Maka91Productions on Patreon -- https://www.patreon.com/maka91productions\nShoutout to herron giggles -- http://herrongamers.com/jaci/\nCheck out @DocCupCake84 -- https://twitter.com/DocCupCake84\nAdditional Credits: Kevin "Nighthawk673" Hollenbeck, Carlseh, MclovinLegend & CultGamerAlliance' </summary>
    </meta>
    <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=5kC0o7xyZUs/</link>
    <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/5kC0o7xyZUs/sddefault.jpg</thumbnail>
</item>

<item>
    <title>Let's Git Gud | Mei  Gameplay - Guide & Tips</title>
    <meta>
        <summary>b"A review of Mei gameplay with tips and tricks\nOur Discord server: https://discord.gg/UJzwMS4\nOther VoD Reviews:\nhttps://www.youtube.com/playlist?list=PLRxsC0vIWul2iy4rDTt0R-zg7TD5plHt2\nSubmit your own VoD for review: \ntrilby1227@gmail.com\nSupport me on Patreon:\nhttps://www.patreon.com/user?u=5667329\nMy Let's Play Channel:\nhttps://www.youtube.com/channel/UCdPBXrNmPEqTgsZCrsme81g" </summary>
    </meta>
    <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=LVzsNdjzWks/</link>
    <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/LVzsNdjzWks/sddefault.jpg</thumbnail>
</item>

<item>
    <title>Let's Git Gud | Mei Gameplay - Guide & Tips</title>
    <meta>
        <summary>b"A review of Mei gameplay with tips and tricks. \nOther VoD Reviews:\nhttps://www.youtube.com/playlist?list=PLRxsC0vIWul2iy4rDTt0R-zg7TD5plHt2\nSubmit your own VoD for review: \ntrilby1227@gmail.com\nSupport me on Patreon:\nhttps://www.patreon.com/user?u=5667329\nMy Let's Play Channel:\nhttps://www.youtube.com/channel/UCdPBXrNmPEqTgsZCrsme81g" </summary>
    </meta>
    <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=XPWSGmPTg6M/</link>
    <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/XPWSGmPTg6M/sddefault.jpg</thumbnail>
</item>

<item>
    <title>Overwatch - Mei Guide "Complete Hero Breakdown"</title>
    <meta>
        <summary>b'Join the community at http://overwatch.gamepedia.com\n\nMei has some of the best crowd control in Overwatch, and is a menacing force on the battlefield.  \n\nFollow us so you dont miss our next video! https://www.twitch.tv/curse\n\nFollow Curse: \nhttps://twitter.com/cursenetwork\nhttps://www.facebook.com/CurseNetwork\n\nFollow our Hosts:\nMitch"Dash" D http://twitter.com/dashstarwars \n\nThanks for watching! Enjoy the game.' </summary>
    </meta>
    <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=YVbv35hDeRE/</link>
    <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/YVbv35hDeRE/sddefault.jpg</thumbnail>
</item>

<item>
    <title>Let's Git Gud | Mei Gameplay - Guide & Tips</title>
    <meta>
        <summary>b"A review of Mei gameplay with tips and tricks. \nOur Discord server: https://discord.gg/UJzwMS4\nOther VoD Reviews:\nhttps://www.youtube.com/playlist?list=PLRxsC0vIWul2iy4rDTt0R-zg7TD5plHt2\nSubmit your own VoD for review: \ntrilby1227@gmail.com\nSupport me on Patreon:\nhttps://www.patreon.com/user?u=5667329\nMy Let's Play Channel:\nhttps://www.youtube.com/channel/UCdPBXrNmPEqTgsZCrsme81g" </summary>
    </meta>
    <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=bejpEjH1EOo/</link>
    <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/bejpEjH1EOo/sddefault.jpg</thumbnail>
</item>

<item>
    <title>Overwatch: FULL Mei Guide - Mei Is Bae | Useful Tips,Tricks And Advices</title>
    <meta>
        <summary>b'Guide for Mei - Useful tips,tricks and advices,basically everything you need to know about Mei and her skills,how to use them and how to be a better player in general with Mei.\n\nI hope you will enjoy the video!\n\nAlso one BIG thanks to my friends DinkyDoo and Zoid for helping me make this video by being my test subject for some parts of the video! \n\nAND at the end of the VIDEO is my new OUTRO,check it OUT!\n\nIf you wanna subscribe and help me grow the channel you can do it right here: http://bit.ly/25wOsFf\n\nIf you have a comment,leave it down below in the comment section,I will answer it as soon as i can!\n\nFollow me on: \nTwitter: https://twitter.com/NeshTv\nTwitch: http://www.twitch.tv/neshtv\n\nBuy games cheap on: \nhttps://www.g2a.com/r/neshtv' </summary>
    </meta>
    <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=1QRnKxeDYtk/</link>
    <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/1QRnKxeDYtk/sddefault.jpg</thumbnail>
</item>

<item>
    <title>Mei-king A Murderer: The Complete Guide to Playing Attack Mei</title>
    <meta>
        <summary>b"This is a guide to playing Mei as an offensive character rather than a defensive one. I give an overview of what offensive Mei players should be doing, advanced tips and tricks that people might not know about, and hero matchups that Mei needs to be on the lookout for.\n__________________________________________________________________\n\nInterested in private coaching or VOD reviews? Check me out at https://www.patreon.com/MindFuzz and http://sandbox.gg/ \n\nCome hang out in my Discord! https://discord.gg/wAxkBzG\n\nI stream 4 times a week at https://twitch.tv/inyrmindfuzz\n\nIntro song: Defkon - Raindrops\nOutro song: Mia Doi Todd - My Room Is White (Flying Lotus Remix) \nChannel graphics by @Zarythe\n\nDon't forget to like and subscribe!" </summary>
    </meta>
    <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=oYTU7g59vuE/</link>
    <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/oYTU7g59vuE/sddefault.jpg</thumbnail>
</item>

<item>
    <title>RYUJEHONG - How PROS Use MEI In Overwatch League - Season 8 Competitive Mei Guide / Tips / Rank Up</title>
    <meta>
        <summary>b"Today im talking about how pros use Mei in the overwatch league and give some quick tips to players trying to learn how to play Mei in overwatch competitive season 8 ranked, this is a mini guide video on positioning and where to be and also how to deal with some of the most problematic heroes in this season. Enjoy\n\n\n\n\nPlaylist: https://www.youtube.com/playlist?list=PLefC4eOMnbRF5Xm7uCjfU73bh0ybup9Df\n\n\nthumbnail: in game\n\n\nGameplays:\nOverwatch League : https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=blHkXAYuQSc\nBackground gameplay : https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=BpD5tUlyuf4\n\n------------------------------------------------------------------------------------\n\n\n\n\n\n\nAnyways, hope you enjoy blizzards new hit!'overwatch,overwatch,joe king,Overwatch Season 8 Placements,overwatch season 8,overwatch season 8 meta,overwatch season 8 tips,overwatch season 8 changes,overwatch season 8 competitive,overwatch season 8 start,overwatch season 8 update,overwatch season 8 guide,overwatch season 8 start date,season 8,season 8 overwatch,overwatch s8,season 8 guide,how to get to diamond overwatch season 8,overwatch placements,overwatch placement matches,overwatch placement tips,placements, how to climb to diamond, how to get to diamond season 8, how to climb out of bronze, bronze to silver, silver to gold, gold to platinum, platinum to diamond, diamond to masters, masters to grandmasters season 8,overwatch,joe king,overwatch league,overwatch esports,overwatch league analysis,overwatch league highlights,overwatch league vods,overwatch season 8,how to rank up overwatch season 8,overwatch league skins,overwatch league teams,overwatch league games,overwatch league gameplay,overwatch league houston outlaws,overwatch league full match,houston outlaws,overwatch esports 2018,overwatch esports highlights,overwatch league live,overwatch league tips,league,ow\n\nVideo Title: RYUJEHONG - How PROS Use MEI In Overwatch League - Season 8 Competitive Mei Guide / Tips / Rank Up" </summary>
    </meta>
    <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=E98yV3ZoONQ/</link>
    <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/E98yV3ZoONQ/sddefault.jpg</thumbnail>
</item>

<item>
    <title>Overwatch | Noob Mei - Tips and Guide</title>
    <meta>
        <summary>b'FOLLOW ME HERE:\n Twitter:https://twitter.com/ReaperFlawless\n Patreon: https://www.patreon.com/FlawlessReaper\nTwitch: https://www.twitch.tv/flawlesssreaper\nDonate: https://www.paypal.me/FlawlessReaperYT\n\n Music \nTitle:\nArtist:\nMusic courtesy of \n\n Join The Team: \n ..Not Later.. NOW \nSubscribe:https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCUx7PsWtnt8fsav0IjcEOgQ' </summary>
    </meta>
    <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=mwzuc2oygwo/</link>
    <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/mwzuc2oygwo/sddefault.jpg</thumbnail>
</item>

<item>
    <title>Overwatch In-Depth Mei Guide: Tips, Tricks, Strategy, and Being An Effective TEAM Player!</title>
    <meta>
        <summary>b"Hello everyone! In this in-depth guide, I go over one of the heroes in the game that has the capability of being either very beneficial, or harmful to your team composition.  In the right hands, Mei can make the enemy team rip their hair out.  But, with her infamous ice wall, players from both sides of the team experience its effects, whether positive, or negative.  This is why it is important to understand how Mei really works on a deeper level, and how to use her to work with your team!\n\nIn this video, I will first go over the possible times that you can pick Mei, according to your team composition. Then, I will introduce her abilities, the most effective way to use them to benefit your team overall, how to MINIMIZE the chances of your abilities affecting your team NEGATIVELY, and also some tips and tricks you can do with each and every one of them.  Lastly, I will go into detail who Mei is effective against, her hero counters, and how to deal with them (when possible).  \n\nHere is a timeline to help you maneuver through the video easily (if needed):\n\nIntro: 0:00\nWhen to pick Mei: 0:27\n\nMECHANICS:\nPrimary attack: 01:24\nAlternate fire: 01:47\nTIP#1: 02:34\nTIP#2: 03:27\nTIP#3: 03:36\nTIP#4: 04:40\nCryo-Freeze: 04:47\nTIP#4: 05:23\nBlizzard: 06:25\nICE WALL: 07:09\nTIP#5: 07:36\nTIP#6: 08:13\nTIP#7: 08:52\nTIP#8: 10:02\nTIP#9: 10:36\nTIP#10: 11:33\n\nWHO MEI IS EFFECTIVE AGAINST: 12:39\nMEI'S COUNTERS: 14:14\nReaper: 14:31\nJunkrat: 14:59\nPharah: 15:51\nZarya: 16:19\nMei: 17:03\nWidowMaker:  17:22\n\nI hope this guide helps some of you guys out there! Mei can be quite a complicated hero to play effectively! However, if you can work with your team and play with a team-focused mindset, Mei can be very deadly, and a HUGE contributor to your team strategy.  \n\nIf you have any questions, just ask in the comment section below, and I will answer them as soon as possible! Thanks :)\n\nFor some Mei gameplay hilarity:\nhttps://www.youtube.com/watch?v=MYmH_hGhctc\n\n\nFeel free to follow me on twitch at:\nhttps://www.twitch.tv/d1bz\n\nJoin my discord server to interact :D!!\nhttps://discord.gg/pMX84ve\n\nBe A Part Of The Community!\nhttp://www.gamereplays.org/overwatch/\n\nFor more Overwatch guides: \nhttps://www.youtube.com/playlist?list=PL6yGIGBXYUlaTLhiW-_4dG2XFyVh9fslR\n\nFollow me on facebook:\nhttps://www.facebook.com/D1bzGaming/\n\nFollow my twitter:\nhttps://twitter.com/DibzGaming" </summary>
    </meta>
    <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=fDoudYocVws/</link>
    <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/fDoudYocVws/sddefault.jpg</thumbnail>
</item>

<item>
    <title>How GRANDMASTER Players DESTROY With MEI | JARDIO - Overwatch Season 7 Competitive Top 500</title>
    <meta>
        <summary>b'----------------------------------------------------------------\nThis video was sponsored by Guilded. Find out more about the best Overwatch LFG around, plus a chance at a $50 Blizzard Card giveaway here: https://www.guilded.gg/JoeKingYT\n----------------------------------------------------------------\n\n\nToday we are back again trying a top 500 tip mei video because I think its fun and people just love mei it seems. Today we are talking about how the grandmaster mei player can carry his competitive games in season 7 overwatch competitive ranked mode. Going over some mei season 6 tips and guide or whatever you want to call it. thanks! \n\n\n\n\nMore Videos! : https://www.youtube.com/playlist?list=PLefC4eOMnbRF5Xm7uCjfU73bh0ybup9Df\n\n\n\nGameplay: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=tDs9aE4xJko\nThumbnail:https://pre00.deviantart.net/9b75/th/pre/f/2016/146/e/6/e635af45b51f50d60d8c52606587dd62-da3usgx.png\n-----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------\n\n\n\n\n\n\nWhat is overwatch?: Well overwatch is Blizzards new take on the fps genre. In this game you choose a hero or "Class" to take on enemies, push payloads, and take control points. The point of the game is to beat the other team over and it is indeed a whole bunch of fun to play. The game includes 26 heroes so far and Is a blast to play. In this video I mostly go over playing it in a commentary type of manner, and these types of videos will usually be overwatch live commentaries or overwatch group commentaries. As well expect a few guides of this game in the future and some box openings as well. Anyways, hope you enjoy blizzards new hit!\'\n\nWho is JoeKing aka me. Im a overwatch youtuber that likes to talk about character updates, how to get better, and the competitive community. Trying to help you get better at overwatch and entertain at the same time hopefully. How GRANDMASTER Players DESTORY with mei - Overwatch Top 500 PRO Tricks Overwatch - 20 Tricksmei Grandmasters ABUSE That You Don\'t! Some tips and tricks to master mei! Overwatch - 7 OP Tips and Tricks Grandmaster Players use every game! mei overwatch, mei guide top 500 tips and tricks  mei master gameplay, how mei is played, shadowburn gameplay mei overwatch competitive esports vod grandmaster mei tricks grandmaster top 500 mei, overwatch top 600 mei esports vod mei esports gameplay, grandmaster mei tricks top 500 tricks tips, how to play mei, mei season 6, overwatch competitive season 6 mei, mei season 6 offense, mei season 6 defense, overwatch season 6 mei guide       overwatch,mei tricks,Tricks mei Grandmasters ABUSE That You Don\'t,Tricks mei Grandmasters ABUSE That You Don\'t overwatch,overwatch Tricks mei Grandmasters ABUSE That You Don\'t,tricks grandmasters abuse that you dont,overwatch tricks grandmasters abuse that you dont,grandmaster tricks overwatch,mei grandmaster,mei top 500 trick,How GRANDMASTER Players DESTROY with mei,mei season 6 competitive,mei vod,grandmaster, mei gale, gale mei, best mei, strongest mei, best mei player, overwatch galeadelade\n\n\n\nTitle:How GRANDMASTER Players DESTROY With mei | JARDIO - Overwatch Season 6 Competitive Top 500' </summary>
    </meta>
    <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=L2jpbrcxABE/</link>
    <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/L2jpbrcxABE/sddefault.jpg</thumbnail>
</item>

<item>
    <title>Overwatch Quick TIPS & TRICKS for Mei (Strategy Guide Tutorial)</title>
    <meta>
        <summary>b'This video runs down some Overwatch Quick TIPS & TRICKS for the character/hero known as Mei. Throughout the video, I discuss each tip in great detail, revealing how to best go about utilizing them and then showcase a number of gameplay clips to act as visual examples. The following TIPS and TRICKS are mentioned:\n\n*TIP ONE*\nBunny Hop - Continuously jump up and down while engaging an enemy opponent in combat. This not only makes you harder to hit but especially makes landing a "Head Shot" much more difficult. Mitigating as much incoming damage as possible in-turn increasing your chance of survival.\n\n*TIP TWO*\nIce Ladder - Many players make the mistake of simply just using Mei\'s "Ice Wall" ability to barricade entrances or specific pathways. In fact, you can actually use this skill in order to better traverse each map\'s environment, break field of view in close quarters combat, or help fellow teammates achieve very unique defensive positions.\n\n*TIP THREE*\nIce Bluff - Instead of only using Mei\'s "Cryo-Freeze" ability as a last resort survival tactic, implement it into your gameplay as an offensive maneuver. Bluff enemy opponents into thinking you are leaving yourself vulnerable to stun abilities (McCree, Roadhog, Reinhardt). Right before your opponents use them, pop into your "Cryo-Freeze." Once the ability has been blocked, immediately pop out and begin attacking.\n\nIf you enjoyed these Overwatch Quick TIPS & TRICKS for Mei then feel free to: Comment / Share / Thumbs Up / Subscribe\n\n*OPERATION SUPPLY DROP*\nhttps://fundraise.operationsupplydrop.org/thuglyfegaming\n\n*SOCIAL NETWORKS*\nInstagram - http://www.instagram.com/thuglyfegaming\nFacebook - http://www.facebook.com/thuglyfegaming\nTwitter - http://www.twitter.com/thuglyfegaming\nTwitch - http://www.twitch.tv/thuglyfegaming/profile\n\nI here VERIFY that I have PURCHASED and OWN receipt proof for the USAGE RIGHTS to all MUSIC and SOUND content used within this video. The following files were used:\n\nwww.pond5.com - "Old School Hip Hop Instrumental 7 (Vintage Sound)" - Payments made out to Pond5 - Contributing Artist: Carlsbro' </summary>
    </meta>
    <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=t6khtSrGNHk/</link>
    <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/t6khtSrGNHk/sddefault.jpg</thumbnail>
</item>

<item>
    <title>1 MEI TIP for EVERY HERO! Including MOIRA! ☝🏼 | A Comprehensive Mei Guide!</title>
    <meta>
        <summary>b'CLICK THAT LITTLE \'HD\' BUTTON! You want to see every trick in detail!\n\nHey everyone! This video is inspired by KarQs own one tip series, with my own personal experience and knowledge combined! I fully credit KarQ for this format of video - I am only implementing the layout, but not the content!\n\n*To address the similarity between KarQ and my video:\n\nYes, I am aware that our videos are very similar. When his video was released, I was equally dumbfounded and worried that he had actually stolen my content. I published my video two months (Nov. 2017) before his (Jan. 2018), and even before publishing, the video was in works long before then. \n\nTo find out what happened, I personally messaged him on his Facebook page, and I kindly asked him if he had, in fact, taken inspiration from my video but chose to not credit me. He was very responsive and willing to solve the situation at hand. He told me that it was purely coincidental, and he made sure with Jardio that he didn\'t copy my script. He was very friendly to me during the whole ordeal, and he even left a comment (pinned) on my video to show he had watched it.\n\nI know a lot of people will not read this explanation, but that is the truth and that is what happened. I, myself, was so grateful he even replied to my message, and even more so that he was willing to help me - a random OW YouTuber with only a few subs (compared to his 100K+). By accusing either of us that we copied one another is tarnishing his and my name falsely, so please be aware of that before pointing fingers at either of us.\n\nTL;DR: Neither of us copied each other, it was a coincidence.\n\nIf you feel like I\'ve left out a crucial piece of information, do feel free to tell me in the comments! I\'ll gladly accept any constructive criticism, but open hate towards me/others, spam, or any other disruptive comments of the sort will be deleted from the comments section. \n\nIf the video is hard to listen, I have implemented closed captions (CC)! Just click on it in the bottom-right corner of the video!\n\nI would like to also credit my good friend ClydeTheGamer11! He\'s the one who was with me in the video to demonstrate and film each tip!\n\nClyde\'s Video (@4:50) was downloaded and used with the permission from the creator himself.\n\nThank you for reading up to this far, and I hope to make more videos!\n\nSONG(s):\n- BGM is from this video: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=rlVx2Byjjh8\n1) Somar - My Window (Feat. EQNX & Joseph Jacobs)\n2) Player Dave - Can\'t Remember\n3) Aso - Waiting\n\n- TO BE CONTINUED MEME SONG: "Roundabout" by Yes.\n\n- END CREDITS SONG: \n1) "the girl i havent met" by kudasai.' </summary>
    </meta>
    <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=KMGfTXasL6Y/</link>
    <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/KMGfTXasL6Y/sddefault.jpg</thumbnail>
</item>

<item>
    <title>Overwatch : Mei Guide For Console Players. Also Review! (PS4 XBOX ONE)</title>
    <meta>
        <summary>b'UNPROFESSIONAL THOUGHTS AND FEELINGS ABOUT MEI!!!\n\nOverall She is extremely useful having high damage potential and arguably the best utility in the game. She is also very easy to pick up but also has room for improvement and mastery for high skill players. She is in my opinion the BEST COUNTER TO HEALERS.  5 OUT OF 5 STARS' </summary>
    </meta>
    <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=nA0_SuAsBpg/</link>
    <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/nA0_SuAsBpg/sddefault.jpg</thumbnail>
</item>

<item>
    <title>Overwatch | Mei - Quick Start Guide</title>
    <meta>
        <summary>b"It's time to take a look at Overwatch's cute yet ice-cold killer's playstyle. We provide you with our best tips and tricks for playing Mei in this quick start guide!\n__\n\n Send in your own clips: http://goo.gl/forms/JsizriSpRL\n__\n\nFollow us!\nTwitch: http://www.twitch.tv/overwatchcentral\nTwitter: https://twitter.com/OWCentral\nGoogle+ https://plus.google.com/+OverwatchCentral\n__\n\nMusic: Epidemic Sound\n\nApproaching Nirvana - Super Happy Fun Time\nhttp://youtube.com/user/approachingnirvana\nApproaching Nirvana on iTunes: https://itunes.apple.com/us/artist/approaching-nirvana/id313583565\n__\n\nThanks for watching! #Overwatch" </summary>
    </meta>
    <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=a6kfkRqrY7g/</link>
    <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/a6kfkRqrY7g/sddefault.jpg</thumbnail>
</item>

<item>
    <title>Mei - Advanced Ice Wall Movement Guide</title>
    <meta>
        <summary>b"Overwatch Mei Ice wall movement guide. I cover most maps in this guide, hopefully it will give you some quick tips on how to best use Mei's Ice Wall to navigate the maps. If you have any other tips, then leave them in the comments below! \n\n PATREON CAMPAIGN! http://www.patreon.com/unitlost\n Twitter https://twitter.com/unitlostgaming\n Live Stream http://www.twitch.tv/unitlost\n http://www.unitlost.com - Join our AWESOME community forums!" </summary>
    </meta>
    <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=1cQ6avqijZI/</link>
    <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/1cQ6avqijZI/sddefault.jpg</thumbnail>
</item>

<item>
    <title>Overwatch Guide | How to Counter Mei! (Tips and Tricks)</title>
    <meta>
        <summary>b"Today in Overwatch I want to cover how to counter the infamous Mei, with some tips and tricks that may help you avoid getting killed by her over and over again. The public mindset currently is that she is too strong/OP/anti-fun/etc -hopefully this helps!\n\n*Edits: Mei's HP is 250, not 200 -sorry\n\nOh yes, I forgot to type out the damage models for Mccree's Peacekeeper vs Mei's Right Click. Here it is:\nPeacekeeper: 35-70 dmg per shot (2RPS)\nMei's Endothermic Blaster (Right Click): 22-75 dmg per shot (1.8 RPS)\nSimilar damage models, but McCree may have an advantage given it's hit scan.\n\nMore info on the competitive meta (as well as the pub v pro comparison) http://www.planetoverwatch.org/11-overwatch-hero-meta-report-the-grand-beta-review\n\nMUSIC:\nTheFatRat - Windfall\n\n\n\n\n\n*Channel Banner and Logo made by Tomographic (HIT HIM UP IF YOU WANT AWESOME ARTWORK DONE!)\nhttps://twitter.com/ItsTomographic\nhttps://www.youtube.com/channel/UCOt5hVyS2-nbcJ3_FP41Ajg" </summary>
    </meta>
    <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=qB6o7k1ucBk/</link>
    <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/qB6o7k1ucBk/sddefault.jpg</thumbnail>
</item>

<item>
    <title>Defense Tips & Stategy Mei Advanced Guide |Overwatch</title>
    <meta>
        <summary>b'In this video I give you some tips on playing on defense, as well as my thoughts on when to pick Mei in those unique situations outside of defense, namely control and attack maps in general.\n\nThanks for watching.\n\nPrevious Videos:\n\nZoning Tips & Strategy Mei Advanced Guide\nhttps://youtu.be/Vpc50ZhAWPU\n\nZenyatta Advanced Guides:\n\nhttps://www.youtube.com/playlist?list=PLUhHb6fMUud8djyo_B5XzFx1ykZLMEcNz\n\nWinston Advanced Guides:\n\nhttps://www.youtube.com/playlist?list=PLUhHb6fMUud_QuSrbeod2IVDfxzltVR_k' </summary>
    </meta>
    <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ljcJmXj8Gac/</link>
    <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/ljcJmXj8Gac/sddefault.jpg</thumbnail>
</item>

<item>
    <title>Mei Tips And Tricks | An Overwatch Hero Guide</title>
    <meta>
        <summary>b"Subscribe today and join the Watch!!!\n\nWhat's up guys? Today we go over the in's and out's of everyone's favorite irritation, Mei! :) Mei is an awesome asset for any defense composition and can be devastating when played correctly. In this video I go over her abilities and how to make them work for you. Thanks and always and enjoy your watch!" </summary>
    </meta>
    <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=FEo2HfCVyzI/</link>
    <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/FEo2HfCVyzI/sddefault.jpg</thumbnail>
</item>

