<item>
    <title>Mercy Ability Overview | Overwatch</title>
    <meta>
        <summary>b'Heroes never die: http://bit.ly/MeetMercy\n\nA guardian angel to those who come under her care, Dr. Angela Ziegler ("Mercy") is a peerless healer, brilliant scientist, and staunch advocate for peace. Though she spends most of her time caring for the broken and dispossessed in crisis areas around the world, Mercy can be counted on to don her Valkyrie swift-response suit whenever innocents are imperiled.\n\nMercy is a formidable frontline medic, capable of healing and strengthening her allies, and even resurrecting them when theyve fallen on the battlefield. \n\nSign Up for Beta: http://bit.ly/JoinOverwatch \nLike Us on Facebook: http://www.facebook.com/playoverwatch \nFollow Us on Twitter: http://www.twitter.com/playoverwatch' </summary>
    </meta>
    <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=-l-ytDZWVFI/</link>
    <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/-l-ytDZWVFI/sddefault.jpg</thumbnail>
</item>

<item>
    <title>Overwatch - Mercy Guide - It's Nice To Be Appreciated! (Tips and Advice)</title>
    <meta>
        <summary>b'I love Mercy! Shes awesome and YOU should play her! This Mercy guide video will give you tips and advice on how to play her. By playing Mercy you can dramatically swing the tide of games and bring your team back from the brink of defeat!\n\n PATREON CAMPAIGN! http://www.patreon.com/unitlost\n Twitter https://twitter.com/unitlostgaming\n Live Stream http://www.twitch.tv/unitlost\n http://www.unitlost.com - Join our AWESOME community forums!' </summary>
    </meta>
    <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=po7_nti09Kw/</link>
    <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/po7_nti09Kw/sddefault.jpg</thumbnail>
</item>

<item>
    <title>The ONLY Mercy guide you need (post nerfs)</title>
    <meta>
        <summary>b'Mercy is still a very solid healer and you guys should appreciate her more. Here are some tips to help you improve your overall Mercy gameplay :)\n\n SUBSCRIBE: http://bit.ly/2bGVMJZ\nTwitch: https://www.twitch.tv/hoshizoraow\n Discord: https://discord.gg/discord\nTwitter : https://twitter.com/hoshizoraOCE\n Facebook : https://facebook.com/hoshizoraOCE\n\n MUSIC\n"Fractures" - Illenium\n"Departure" - Phaura\n\n Thumbnail by: Hellyon White (https://www.artstation.com/artwork/ZOwO1)' </summary>
    </meta>
    <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=k2f_L0KyNGI/</link>
    <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/k2f_L0KyNGI/sddefault.jpg</thumbnail>
</item>

<item>
    <title>MERCY Tips and Tricks (Season 12) | Overwatch Guide</title>
    <meta>
        <summary>b' Join NOW! https://ow.gameleap.com/ - Learn from Top 500 Pros and carry your games!\n\nThis Overwatch Mercy guide will cover 4 tips and tricks for Mercy!\n\nThanks for watching. Want to reach us? Please send an email to support@game-leap.com and we will get back to you shortly.' </summary>
    </meta>
    <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=3jcVaJv4R0o/</link>
    <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/3jcVaJv4R0o/sddefault.jpg</thumbnail>
</item>

<item>
    <title>1 MERCY TIP for EVERY HERO ft. EeveeA</title>
    <meta>
        <summary>b'The dust has settled after all the Mercy nerfs and we can all agree that she is still a very strong support choice (as evident in OWL). Here is 1 MERCY TIP vs EVERY HERO with the 3000+ hour Mercy enthusiast, EeveeA! \n\n EeveeA Socials:\n- https://twitch.tv/eeveea_ (DAILY STREAMS!)\n- https://www.youtube.com/eeveea\n- https://twitter.com/eeveea_\n\n THUMBNAIL ARTIST: Lilakey\n- https://www.instagram.com/lilakey/\n- https://twitter.com/lilamuffin2 \n\n\n\n KARQ SOCIALS:\n\nTwitch  https://twitch.tv/KarQ (Stream 5x weekly)\nMerch  https://teespring.com/stores/karq\nDiscord  https://discord.gg/karq\nTwitter  https://twitter.com/KarQGames\nInstagram  http://instagram.com/KarQGames\nFacebook  https://www.facebook.com/KarQGames/\n\n- Thank you Katmayla, Steak8oz, Endwalker for helping me film!\n\n\n Music Used:\n\nTitle: New Horizons by Protostar\nListen on Spotify: https://open.spotify.com/track/697vKkzIgwsiA5xqzJ5Sqb\niTunes Download Link: https://geo.itunes.apple.com/us/album/new-horizons-single/1358485423?uo=4&app=music&at=1000lK3L&ct=LFV_57f7745674b8b06501b9c63e4050de17\niTunes Download Link: https://geo.itunes.apple.com/us/album/new-horizons-single/1358485423?uo=4&app=itunes&at=1000lK3L&ct=LFV_57f7745674b8b06501b9c63e4050de17' </summary>
    </meta>
    <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Y-8esZ2pbkY/</link>
    <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/Y-8esZ2pbkY/sddefault.jpg</thumbnail>
</item>

<item>
    <title>Overwatch | Master Mercy - Tips and Tricks (ft EeveeA)</title>
    <meta>
        <summary>b'Eevee is on Twitch GO FOLLOW:: https://www.twitch.tv/eeveea_tm\nAnother Master guide and we talk about playing Mercy at a Grandmaster level. Our Master is EeveeA!\n\n\n\n__\n\n Need a new headset? Buy this one and support us! http://hyperx.gg/StingerOWC [AD]\n\n Send in your own clips: http://goo.gl/forms/JsizriSpRL\n__\n\nFollow us!\nTwitch: http://www.twitch.tv/overwatchcentral\nTwitter: https://twitter.com/OWCentral\nGoogle+: https://plus.google.com/+OverwatchCentral\n__\n\nMusic: Epidemic Sound\n\nApproaching Nirvana - Super Happy Fun Time\nhttp://youtube.com/user/approachingnirvana\nApproaching Nirvana on iTunes: https://itunes.apple.com/us/artist/approaching-nirvana/id313583565\n__\n\nThanks for watching! #Overwatch' </summary>
    </meta>
    <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=KPUh39KbXjA/</link>
    <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/KPUh39KbXjA/sddefault.jpg</thumbnail>
</item>

<item>
    <title>HOW TO PLAY MERCY FROM AN OVERWATCH PRO | LA VALIANT CUSTA</title>
    <meta>
        <summary>b'Scott "Custa" Kennedy offers his insider tips on how to be a boss playing #Mercy in our first installment of educational tutorials called "Climbing the Ladder." #Overwatch #HowTo \n\nFollow Los Angeles Valiant on social media:\n\nFacebook: https://www.facebook.com/LAValiant \n\nInstagram: https://www.instagram.com/LAValiant \n\nYouTube: https://www.youtube.com/LAValiant \n\nDiscord: https://discordapp.com/invite/RsJMuBZ \n\nReddit: https://www.reddit.com/r/LAValiant/ \n\nTumblr: https://lavaliant.tumblr.com/ \n\nTwitch: https://www.twitch.tv/lavaliant \n\nSnapchat: LAValiant' </summary>
    </meta>
    <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=H13lMSY9SlE/</link>
    <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/H13lMSY9SlE/sddefault.jpg</thumbnail>
</item>

<item>
    <title>Overwatch: MERCY GUIDE to the PERFECT RESURRECT</title>
    <meta>
        <summary>b" Join NOW! https://ow.gameleap.com/ - Learn from Top 500 Pros and carry your games!\n\nThis Mercy guide, from our GameLeap Overwatch site, covers how to use Mercy's Resurrect PERFECTLY. While more advanced for a Mercy guide, these tips are useful for Mercy players of all ranks!\n\nThanks for watching. If you have any questions or want to reach us, please send an email at support@game-leap.com and we will get back to you shortly." </summary>
    </meta>
    <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=vJjsLiHx0Gg/</link>
    <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/vJjsLiHx0Gg/sddefault.jpg</thumbnail>
</item>

<item>
    <title>Overwatch Pro Tips: Neptuno explains Battle Mercy, Special Settings, and Who to Rez</title>
    <meta>
        <summary>b"Check out the Upcomer app for OWL news, schedules, and rankings: http://blitz.gg/upcomer\n\nIn this episode of Pro Tips, we talk to Philadelphia Fusion's Neptuno about his legendary Battle Mercy, how to read the screen like a pro, priority targets to resurrect and heal, and more. Stay tuned for more OWL pro guides.\n\n--\nWant more?\n\nSubscribe to our YouTube channel: http://bltz.gg/owsubscribe\n\nJoin us on Discord: http://blitz.gg/discord\n\nLike us on Facebook: http://geni.us/ytblitzfb\n\nFollow us on Twitter: http://geni.us/ytblitztw\n\nFollow us on Instagram: http://geni.us/ytblitzig\n\n--\nEditor: Kurt Hogarth\nLead Producer: Matt Mersel (https://twitter.com/MattMersel)\nInterview: Joshua Lee (https://twitter.com/PiscatorJosh)" </summary>
    </meta>
    <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=LkRDf8K8gpA/</link>
    <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/LkRDf8K8gpA/sddefault.jpg</thumbnail>
</item>

<item>
    <title>A 21 Minute GrandMaster Guide To Mercy 2.0</title>
    <meta>
        <summary>b'I also made a video about the August 2018 nerfs (and other mini guides for any other out of date parts): https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=VR2EvCrx2oo\n\nTwitter: http://www.twitter.com/niandra_\nMercy art: http://www.twitter.com/MaschaDraws\n\nCheck out my game:\nWebsite: http://www.letsplaymanager.com\nTwitter: http://www.twitter.com/LetsPlayManager\nDiscord: https://discordapp.com/invite/WnsJ2Fb' </summary>
    </meta>
    <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=aCNP2EINz2g/</link>
    <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/aCNP2EINz2g/sddefault.jpg</thumbnail>
</item>

<item>
    <title>Overwatch Coaching - MERCY MAIN PAIN! - [OverAnalyzed]</title>
    <meta>
        <summary>b'JOIN THE UNIT LOST DISCORD http://discord.gg/unitlost\nOverwatch Mercy coaching! Season 8 Mercy tips and advice! Welcome to OverAnalyzed! In this series, we as a community help our fellow players with tips and advice on how to become better players! Good Aim, Bad Positioning t-shirt! http://bit.ly/ulstore\n\n HyperX - CHECK THEM OUT! http://hyperx.gg/AlphaUnitLost [AD]\n UNIT LOST STORE! http://bit.ly/ulstore\n Discord JOIN NOW! http://discord.gg/unitlost  \n PATREON CAMPAIGN! http://www.patreon.com/unitlost\n Twitter https://twitter.com/unitlostgaming\n Live Stream http://www.twitch.tv/unitlost\n http://www.unitlost.com - Join our AWESOME community forums!' </summary>
    </meta>
    <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=qXKJz2cFuEk/</link>
    <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/qXKJz2cFuEk/sddefault.jpg</thumbnail>
</item>

<item>
    <title>Tips On Playing Nerfed Mercy | August 2018</title>
    <meta>
        <summary>b"Hey guys! Just wanted to make a real quick video based on how I've changed my Mercy playstyle in the last week or so.\n\nTwitter: http://www.twitter.com/Niandra_\nTwitch: http://www.twitch.tv/niandra_\nDiscord for my game/youtube: https://discordapp.com/invite/WnsJ2Fb\nMercy art: http://www.twitter.com/MaschaDraws\n\nCheck out my game:\nWebsite: http://www.letsplaymanager.com\nTwitter: http://www.twitter.com/letsplaymanager" </summary>
    </meta>
    <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=VR2EvCrx2oo/</link>
    <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/VR2EvCrx2oo/sddefault.jpg</thumbnail>
</item>

<item>
    <title>VALE - GRANDMASTER MERCY NERF GAMEPLAY TIPS | How To Improve As Mercy Guide - Overwatch Season 7</title>
    <meta>
        <summary>b"----------------------------------------------------------------\nJOIN A SCRIM THIS FRIDAY OR SATURDAY HERE : https://www.guilded.gg/matchmaking\n----------------------------------------------------------------\n\n\nToday we are back again trying a top 500 tip Mercy video because I think its fun and people just love Mercy it seems. Today we are talking about how the grandmaster Mercy player can carry his competitive games in season 7 overwatch competitive ranked mode guide for overwatch season 7 placement matches and overwatch season 7 changes. Going over some Mercy season 7 tips and guide or whatever you want to call it. I hope that these tips can help to have you guys learn how to improve as Mercy and hope this works as a mini Mercy guide tip trick thing for all that want to improve as her. Anyways, thanks! \n\n\n\n\nMore Videos! : https://www.youtube.com/playlist?list=PLefC4eOMnbRF5Xm7uCjfU73bh0ybup9Df\n\n\n\nGameplay: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=1zPEngoixrw\nThumbnail: https://orig00.deviantart.net/e699/f/2017/033/9/6/mercy_overwatch_ctiahao_by_ctiahao-daxmpcp.png\n-----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------\n\n\n\n======================================================================\n\nTIPS I WROTE DOWN FROM THE VIDEO:\n-mercy is MUCH worse vs dive/deathball comps now, but not much worse vs slow push comps\n-every support player i've ever seen looks at their teammates most played heroes\n-Ask teammates to shield you while ressing, you can get your zarya a lot of charge with this strat\n-consistantly use and cancel your flying to get barely in range of healing while still moving a lot\n-his team kinda gets stomped first point, but on second point he consitantly heals and stays alive\n-if your team is doing badly, tell them to all backup adn group, resetting can win games\n-try to heal right around corners, make it hard for someone like hanzo to one shot you\n-when ulting stay around corners more than just high up in the air, hitscan can wreck you there\n\n-his team got stomped on the first offense, but stomps on their own first offense. Dont think youll do wors\n-ask for a pharah if they have a spam comp, dont always fly right next to her or else you may get sniped\n-phrarh gives you infinte more mobility, even if she doesnt get a lot of kills she lets you get a lot of healing\n-Your ult is extremely importat now vs dive, make sure to tell your team it is up\n-if they have no hiscan just try to fly up to where you have the most vision possible\n-you can win games off of small consitant pushes, even if you cant get one big push all the time\n-damage boosting a nano visor makes soldier broken, if you arent doing anything else then go for it\n-if your team is down one in a fight but you think you may win with a res, just go for it, use his hp to get ult\n-you can beat soldier ult by hidng around walls and using your super far range healing, problem is genji ult\n\n-on offense you can go for more cheesy resses because you get more chances, dont do this on defense\n-winston bubble gives you a safe palce to res\n-Sometimes you may pop off but your team just cant finish the kills... just get used to dealing with it\n\n-your damamge boost priotity is soldier than reinhardt (charging rein ult early can mean a won fight)\n-You can kidna awkwardly res while falling, this makes it harder for people to kill you\n-you can solo heal with sym easily, just damage boost a lot less\n-ult at the start of teamfights especially if you are the solo healer, even if you dont use both resses its gud\n-if it is safer to heal then res, just heal. And go for the res later\n\n\n\n\n======================================================================\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\nWho is JoeKing aka me. Im a overwatch youtuber that likes to talk about character updates, how to get better, and the competitive community. Trying to help you get better at overwatch and entertain at the same time hopefully. How GRANDMASTER Players DESTORY with Mercy - Overwatch Top 500 PRO Tricks Overwatch - 20 TricksMercy Grandmasters ABUSE That You Don't! Some tips and tricks to master Mercy! Overwatch - 7 OP Tips and Tricks Grandmaster Players use every game! Mercy overwatch, Mercy guide top 500 tips and tricks  Mercy master gameplay, how Mercy is played, shadowburn gameplay Mercy overwatch competitive esports vod grandmaster Mercy tricks grandmaster top 500 Mercy, overwatch top 700 Mercy esports vod Mercy esports gameplay, grandmaster Mercy tricks top 500 tricks tips, how to play Mercy, Mercy season 7, overwatch competitive season 7 Mercy, Mercy season 7 offense, Mercy season 7 defense, overwatch season 7 Mercy guide       overwatch,Mercy tricks,Tricks Mercy Grandmasters ABUSE That You Don't,Tricks Mercy Grandmasters ABUSE That You Don't overwatch,overwatch Tricks Mercy Grandmasters ABUSE That You Don't,\n\n\n\nTitle:GRANDMASTER Mercy GAMEPLAY TIPS | How To Improve As Mercy Guide - Overwatch Season 7 Competitive Tricks" </summary>
    </meta>
    <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Zyus2G26_oo/</link>
    <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/Zyus2G26_oo/sddefault.jpg</thumbnail>
</item>

<item>
    <title>PRO MERCY COACHING | POSITIONING GUIDE & PRIORITIZATION TIPS | Overwatch</title>
    <meta>
        <summary>b"If you're interested in coaching, please check out my Patreon and/or send me an email at Coaching.SciKni@Gmail.com ;)\n\nI'll post my schedule each week over on Twitter so make sure to follow me @SciKni and over on Twitch to stay up to date!\n\nSong: LAKEY INSPIRED - Chill Day (Vlog No Copyright Music)\nMusic provided by Vlog No Copyright Music.\nVideo Link: https://youtu.be/vtHGESuQ22s\n\nJoin the community Discord!\nhttps://discord.gg/BeE7cgZ\n\nSupport me on Patreon for behind the scenes access and COACHING!\nhttps://www.patreon.com/SciKni\n\nFollow me on Twitch to see the action LIVE!\nhttps://www.twitch.tv/scikni\n\nFollow on Twitter for more updates and news!\nhttps://twitter.com/SciKni" </summary>
    </meta>
    <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=0tCHDrzuF4M/</link>
    <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/0tCHDrzuF4M/sddefault.jpg</thumbnail>
</item>

<item>
    <title>Overwatch | Top 5 Tips For New Mercy - ft EeveeA</title>
    <meta>
        <summary>b'Twitch - https://www.twitch.tv/EeveeA_\nTwitter - https://twitter.com/EeveeA_\nMercy 2.0 can be difficult to get your head around. EeveeA gives us 5 tips to help us get started\n Need a new mouse? Check this one out! http://hyperx.gg/PulsefireOWC?track=YouTube \n__\n\nFollow us!\nTwitch: http://www.twitch.tv/overwatchcentral\nTwitter: https://twitter.com/OWCentral\nGoogle+: https://plus.google.com/+OverwatchCentral\n__\n\nMusic: Epidemic Sound\n\nApproaching Nirvana - Super Happy Fun Time\nhttp://youtube.com/user/approachingnirvana\nApproaching Nirvana on iTunes: https://itunes.apple.com/us/artist/approaching-nirvana/id313583565\n__\n\nThanks for watching! #Overwatch' </summary>
    </meta>
    <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=JEUVImWBG1c/</link>
    <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/JEUVImWBG1c/sddefault.jpg</thumbnail>
</item>

<item>
    <title>How GRANDMASTER PLAYERS Use MERCY In Overwatch League - Overwatch Season 8 Competitive Guide Tips</title>
    <meta>
        <summary>b"Today im talking about how pros use Mercy in the overwatch league and give some quick tips to players trying to learn how to play Mercy in overwatch competitive season 8 ranked, this is a mini guide video on positioning and where to be and also how to deal with some of the most problematic heroes in this season. Enjoy\n\n\n\n\nPlaylist: https://www.youtube.com/playlist?list=PLefC4eOMnbRF5Xm7uCjfU73bh0ybup9Df\n\n\nthumbnail: in game\n\n\nGameplays:\nOverwatch League : https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=BPuzdUXJ72Y\nBackground gameplay : me before I hit masters\n------------------------------------------------------------------------------------\n\n\n\n\n\n\nAnyways, hope you enjoy blizzards new hit!'overwatch,overwatch,joe king,Overwatch Season 8 Placements,overwatch season 8,overwatch season 8 meta,overwatch season 8 tips,overwatch season 8 changes,overwatch season 8 competitive,overwatch season 8 start,overwatch season 8 update,overwatch season 8 guide,overwatch season 8 start date,season 8,season 8 overwatch,overwatch s8,season 8 guide,how to get to diamond overwatch season 8,overwatch placements,overwatch placement matches,overwatch placement tips,placements, how to climb to diamond, how to get to diamond season 8, how to climb out of bronze, bronze to silver, silver to gold, gold to platinum, platinum to diamond, diamond to masters, masters to grandmasters season 8,overwatch,joe king,overwatch league,overwatch esports,overwatch league analysis,overwatch league highlights,overwatch league vods,overwatch season 8,how to rank up overwatch season 8,overwatch league skins,overwatch league teams,overwatch league games,overwatch league gameplay,overwatch league houston outlaws,overwatch league full match,houston outlaws,overwatch esports 2018,overwatch esports highlights,overwatch league live,overwatch league tips,league,owoverwatch,overwatch season 8 Mercy,overwatch season 8 Mercy guide,Mercy season 8 tips,Mercy season 8 guide,Mercy gameplay,Mercy grandmaster,grandmaster Mercy,Mercy season 8,overwatch Mercy tips,master Mercy guide,overwatch Mercy season 8,grandmaster Mercy tips,grandmaster Mercy gameplay,pro Mercy gameplay,Mercy guide,how to improve as Mercy,Mercy,Mercy overwatch league,overwatch league Mercy,ow league Mercy,ow league tips,overwatch league tips,mercyoverwatch,overwatch season 8 Mercy,overwatch season 8 Mercy guide,Mercy season 8 tips,Mercy season 8 guide,Mercy gameplay,Mercy grandmaster,grandmaster Mercy,Mercy season 8,overwatch Mercy tips,master Mercy guide,overwatch Mercy season 8,grandmaster Mercy tips,grandmaster Mercy gameplay,pro Mercy gameplay,Mercy guide,how to improve as Mercy,Mercy,Mercy overwatch league,overwatch league Mercy,ow league Mercy,ow league tips,overwatch league tips,mercy\n\nVideo Title: Soon - How PROS Use Mercy In Overwatch League - Season 8 Competitive Mercy Guide / Tips / Rank Up" </summary>
    </meta>
    <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=fmlYhhe9YWA/</link>
    <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/fmlYhhe9YWA/sddefault.jpg</thumbnail>
</item>

<item>
    <title>Overwatch: How To Play Mercy Guide (Beginner Tips, Abilities & Mechanics)</title>
    <meta>
        <summary>b'This Mercy beginner guide is designed to teach you the abilities, mechanics, and tips to help you better play Mercy in Overwatch. This hero starter guide was designed for beginners or those wanting more basic tips.\n\nIf you liked the video, please leave a like and if you want to see more content, please subscribe and follow me on Facebook and Twitter.\n\nSubscribe:https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCYzCvF2KO2ms9hADC9hS4og?sub_confirmation=1\n\nFacebook: https://www.facebook.com/RealToastGaming\n\nTwitter: https://www.twitter.com/RealToastGaming' </summary>
    </meta>
    <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=LhPd7y8sZPA/</link>
    <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/LhPd7y8sZPA/sddefault.jpg</thumbnail>
</item>

<item>
    <title>VALE MERCY GUIDE! 12K HEAL! [ OVERWATCH SEASON 12 TOP 500 ]</title>
    <meta>
        <summary>b"VALE MERCY GUIDE! 12K HEAL! [ OVERWATCH SEASON 12 TOP 500 ]\n\n Please subscribe to the author's channel: \nVale Twitch: https://twitch.tv/vale\n\nVale plays Moira on Oasis. In this Overwatch replay and gets 12k healing done. \nHow to play Mercy overwatch? Vale as Mercy. Pro replays overwatch. Mercy gameplay.  \n\nOverwatch footage with permission by Blizzard Entertainment:\nhttp://us.blizzard.com/en-us/company/...\n\nIf you want the removal of videos that you own the copyright, which can be accessed via this page, please contact me.\ng1bs0n5342@gmail.com\n\nOverwatch footage with permission by Blizzard Entertainment:\nhttp://us.blizzard.com/en-us/company/...\n\nEverything is licensed under Creative Commons: By Attribution 4.0\nhttps://creativecommons.org/licenses/...\n\nSubscribe for more pro Overwatch footage: https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCtlrxuJybARbBueAGSheVqg\n#Vale #Moira #Overwatch" </summary>
    </meta>
    <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=lZnm-B5C51U/</link>
    <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/lZnm-B5C51U/sddefault.jpg</thumbnail>
</item>

<item>
    <title>[Overwatch] Grandmaster Mercy Guide and Tips (Hanamura) - Hoshizora</title>
    <meta>
        <summary>b'Thoughts of a Mercy on Hanamura. Hope this helps!\n\n Help me reach 6000 subscribers : http://bit.ly/2bGVMJZ\n New gaming videos each week!\n\nYou can follow me here at these places!\nTwitter : https://twitter.com/hoshizoraOCE\nFacebook : https://facebook.com/hoshizoraOCE\n\n MUSIC\n"Wasted Youth (Noah. Remix)" - Fletcher\n"Hostage (Catching Flies Remix)" - Klangstof' </summary>
    </meta>
    <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=pUuFydZoCDI/</link>
    <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/pUuFydZoCDI/sddefault.jpg</thumbnail>
</item>

<item>
    <title>How to play Mercy in Season 12</title>
    <meta>
        <summary>b'One day, things will be as fun as Season 2/3.\n\nMercy video playlist: https://www.youtube.com/playlist?list=PLeYuv6nbJ7uGIH-fP-Ktc7MTsto9vBdjq\n\n  Support me on Patreon? https://www.patreon.com/DulcetRefrain\n\nDiscord server: https://discord.gg/arVvBYS\n\n Credits \n\nMusic: Nitro Fun - New Game\nInterview source: https://venturebeat.com/2017/11/03/overwatch-lead-jeff-kaplan-on-moira-mercys-troubles-and-fixing-toxicity/\nPatch notes: https://us.forums.blizzard.com/en/overwatch/t/upcoming-balance-changes-for-support-heroes/163703' </summary>
    </meta>
    <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=WDryOG-GIFY/</link>
    <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/WDryOG-GIFY/sddefault.jpg</thumbnail>
</item>

