<item>
    <title>[NEW HERO NOW AVAILABLE] Introducing Moira | Overwatch</title>
    <meta>
        <summary>b'Meet Moiraa Talon geneticist as brilliant as she is ambitious. \n\nLearn more about Moira: http://blizz.ly/Moira\nWatch her trailer: https://youtu.be/6ETybQd4uRE\n\nLike us on Facebook: http://www.facebook.com/playoverwatch\nFollow us on Twitter: http://www.twitter.com/playoverwatch\nFollow us on Instagram: https://www.instagram.com/playoverwatch' </summary>
    </meta>
    <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=8tLopqeL9s8/</link>
    <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/8tLopqeL9s8/sddefault.jpg</thumbnail>
</item>

<item>
    <title>[NEW HERO NOW AVAILABLE] Moira Origin Story | Overwatch</title>
    <meta>
        <summary>b"Unravel the secrets surrounding Talon's shadowy scientist: Moira.\n\nLearn more about Moira: http://blizz.ly/Moira\nWatch her trailer: https://youtu.be/8tLopqeL9s8 \n\nLike us on Facebook: http://www.facebook.com/playoverwatch\nFollow us on Twitter: http://www.twitter.com/playoverwatch\nFollow us on Instagram: https://www.instagram.com/playoverwatch" </summary>
    </meta>
    <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=6ETybQd4uRE/</link>
    <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/6ETybQd4uRE/sddefault.jpg</thumbnail>
</item>

<item>
    <title>Overwatch | PRO MOIRA GUIDE ft Dallas Fuel CUSTAA</title>
    <meta>
        <summary>b"Custa Twitch: https://www.twitch.tv/custaa\nCusta Twitter: https://twitter.com/custaaOW\nWhilst Moira is a very new hero, it's going to be Custa's job at Dallas Fuel to master her. Today we go over some in depth tips and scenarios with one of the most upcoming Moira players out there.\n CHECK OUT THE HYPERX CLOUD ALPHA http://hyperx.gg/AlphaOverwatchCentral \n__\nFollow us!\nTwitter: https://twitter.com/OWCentral\nTwitch - Mysca: http://www.twitch.tv/mysca_\nTwitch - Ryan: http://www.twitch.tv/ryancentral_\n__\n\nMusic: Epidemic Sound\n\nApproaching Nirvana - Super Happy Fun Time\nhttp://youtube.com/user/approachingnirvana\nApproaching Nirvana on iTunes: https://itunes.apple.com/us/artist/approaching-nirvana/id313583565\n__\n\nThanks for watching! #Overwatch" </summary>
    </meta>
    <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=-QJ28RijUGg/</link>
    <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/-QJ28RijUGg/sddefault.jpg</thumbnail>
</item>

<item>
    <title>CUSTA - GRANDMASTER MOIRA GAMEPLAY TIPS | How To Improve As Moira Guide - Overwatch Season 7</title>
    <meta>
        <summary>b"Today we are back again trying a top 500 tip Moira video because I think its fun and people just love Moira it seems. Today we are talking about how the grandmaster Moira player can carry his competitive games in season 7 overwatch competitive ranked mode guide for overwatch season 7 placement matches and overwatch season 7 changes. Going over some Moira season 7 tips and guide or whatever you want to call it. I hope that these tips can help to have you guys learn how to improve as Moira and hope this works as a mini Moira guide tip trick thing for all that want to improve as her. Anyways, thanks! \n\n\n\n\nMore GM Gameplay Tip Videos Here! : https://www.youtube.com/playlist?list=PLefC4eOMnbRF5Xm7uCjfU73bh0ybup9Df\n\n\n\nGameplay: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=SHwT0LtCW1U\nThumbnail:https://pbs.twimg.com/media/DNvQmOxW0AEpElo.jpg\n-----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------\n-remember you have a healing orb, dont damage orb unless you have a guarenteed kill with it or both teams poking\n-have your damage beam held at all times, even if you get a tick of damage thats a bit more healing you can do\n-always shoot your healing orb before you ult, it makes you never die\n-while ulting, focus healing or killing the enemy mercy. Dont go for others\n-vs hitscan comps, try to have your team group up so you can just outheal the damage\n-dont always try to top people off with your healing, getting a kill can stop more damage than healing will give\n-the second you start taking big damage, just e heal and shift out. dont risk your life at all\n-when your team is down a man, just spam your damage orb to try to get your ult before your teammates get back\n-dont waste your ult to try to heal through multiple enemy ults\n-you can ult early and focus on a nanoed person or genji ult\n-he stays pretty far back behind his team, there is no point in getting close\n-when somebody gets hooked or soemthing, go for a healing orb spam healing before they actually get moved. \n-if the enemy has a flanker , just spam your right click at them. you will never kill them but you stop the damage\n-ulting at the start of the fight allows for your teammates to go in almost risk free, nice way to engage\n\n-defense for moira is harder, you need to go for more damage than you would think\n-he goes for a lot of damage orbs on defense to try to get an early ult to stop a teamwipe\n-he lets the other support top people off and heal him up, not using his healing orb unles he needs to\n-if you are half hp in a fight and think you may be able to win, just ult. Its not an ult you need to save\n-throw a damage orb into zarya ult and then ult if you have no other combos, otherwise, dont waste it\n-he ults a full hp mercy and can kill her. If the enemy mercy doesnt have ult, she is dead\n-you dont really want to ult until you get low on healing, try to use most of the bar and then ult\n-your ult esentually fully charges your ult from the damage it doesn, keep in mind that extra leaing\n-you can jump on point to stall for some time, then back off and heal\n-Just try to keep yourself alive, and dont overextend to suck people to death\n\n\n======================================================================\n\nTIPS I WROTE DOWN FROM THE VIDEO:\n-\n\n\n======================================================================\n\n\n\n\n\nHow GRANDMASTER Players DESTORY with Moira - Overwatch Top 500 PRO Tricks Overwatch - 20 TricksMoira Grandmasters ABUSE That You Don't! Some tips and tricks to master Moira! Overwatch - 7 OP Tips and Tricks Grandmaster Players use every game! Moira overwatch, Moira guide top 500 tips and tricks  Moira master gameplay, how Moira is played, CUSTA gameplay Moira overwatch competitive esports vod grandmaster Moira tricks grandmaster top 500 Moira, overwatch top 700 Moira esports vod Moira esports gameplay, grandmaster Moira tricks top 500 tricks tips, how to play Moira, Moira season 7, overwatch competitive season 7 Moira, Moira season 7 offense, Moira season 7 defense, overwatch season 7 Moira guide       overwatch,Moira tricks,Tricks Moira Grandmasters ABUSE That You Don't,Tricks Moira Grandmasters ABUSE That You Don't overwatch,overwatch Tricks Moira Grandmasters ABUSE That You Don't,tricks grandmasters abuse that you dont,overwatch tricks grandmasters abuse that you dont,grandmaster tricks overwatch,Moira grandmaster,Moira top 500 trick,How GRANDMASTER Players DESTROY with Moira,Moira season 7 competitive,Moira vod,grandmaster, Moira CUSTA, CUSTA Moira, best Moira, strongest Moira, best Moira player, overwatch CUSTA\n\n\n\nTitle:GRANDMASTER Moira GAMEPLAY TIPS | How To Improve As Moira Guide - Overwatch Season 7 Competitive Tricks" </summary>
    </meta>
    <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=iCoy9nBgpjY/</link>
    <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/iCoy9nBgpjY/sddefault.jpg</thumbnail>
</item>

<item>
    <title>Advanced Moira Guide by Top 500 Moira Main</title>
    <meta>
        <summary>b"Follow me on twitch: https://www.twitch.tv/tesla_ow\n\nI decided to finally compile all the videos I've been collecting for the past year or so into a formal Moira guide. I have recently become consistent with Moira around 4300 and feel I have a lot to teach about the strategies I use in competitive play.\n\nSensitivity: 800 DPI 3.5 In-game 38 Scoped\n\nTime Marks:\n1:02 Character Overview\n1:41 Moira's Role\n2:15 Healing\n4:12 Combination Healing\n5:22 Damage\n6:35 Combination Damage\n7:41 Self Sustain\n8:23 Melee\n9:10 Crouch and Strafe\n9:41 Shields\n10:21 Orb Usage\n12:12 Healing Orb\n12:57 Damage Orb\n13:52 Early Damage Orbs\n14:56 Fade\n15:54 Fade Mechanics\n17:31 Offensive Coalescence\n18:29 Defensive Coalescence\n19:03 Hybrid Coalescence\n20:12 Importance of Aim\n22:35 Target Prioritization\n23:08 Positioning\n24:21 Team Composition\n26:08 Healer Pairing\n28:20 Animation Cancels\n29:25 Suboptimal Pairing\n30:32 End Game Statistics\n32:23 Hero Matchups\n\nThe song used during the captions is a keyboard solo by Cory Henry from the song Snarky Puppy - Lingus (We Like It Here):\n\nhttps://www.youtube.com/watch?v=L_XJ_s5IsQc\n\nThumbnail art:\nCharaspower: Moira Overwatch\n\nhttps://charaspower.com/poster-pop-culture/moira-overwatch-oeuvres-charaspower/" </summary>
    </meta>
    <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Fyx4FWnzbS0/</link>
    <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/Fyx4FWnzbS0/sddefault.jpg</thumbnail>
</item>

<item>
    <title>Top 5 Best Moira Tips to Rank Up FAST | Beginner to Advanced - Overwatch Guide</title>
    <meta>
        <summary>b'Top 5 Best Moira Tips to Rank Up FAST | Beginner to Advanced - Overwatch Guide. Learn how to play moira easy, abilities and ultimate tips. Bronze, silver, gold,platinum.diamond and masters players will find this guide most helpful.\n\n\n\nIn this video we talk about: \nOverwatch Moira\nOverwatch Moira Guide\nOverwatch Moira Tips\nOverwatch Moira Rank Up\n\n\n\n STAY CONNECTED! \n\n\nFollow Us on Social Media!\n Twitter: http://Twitter.com/UltraGuides\n Discord: https://discord.gg/ultra\n Twitch: http://Twitch.tv/UltraGuides\n\n\nSources :\nhttps://clips.twitch.tv/SarcasticLazyNightingaleMVGame\nhttps://clips.twitch.tv/CredulousTenderJackalNotLikeThis\nhttps://clips.twitch.tv/FrailArborealWheelFloof\nhttps://clips.twitch.tv/JoyousInnocentStarPrimeMe\nhttps://clips.twitch.tv/ZealousSavageBaconNononoCat\nhttps://www.twitch.tv/videos/212213562\nhttps://www.youtube.com/watch?v=dJWaD5gnQ1o\nhttps://www.twitch.tv/custa\nhttps://www.twitch.tv/michael3dtv\nhttps://www.youtube.com/watch?v=8enl0bwOijI\n\n___\n\n\nThat just about does it for this video guys, if you liked Top 5 Best Moira Tips to Rank Up FAST | Beginner to Advanced - Overwatch Guide , hit that like button, if you want to see more videos like this as they are made public, subscribe. If you want to enter in some sick giveaways, you can follow us on twitter @UltraGuides. If you wanna hang with me and the other UG members, you can join our Discord server.  Thank you so much for staying till the end of the video. Stay amazing, and we will see you, in the next one.' </summary>
    </meta>
    <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=bZI_Vyvp38U/</link>
    <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/bZI_Vyvp38U/sddefault.jpg</thumbnail>
</item>

<item>
    <title>MOIRA Tips and Tricks (Season 12) | Overwatch Guide</title>
    <meta>
        <summary>b" Join NOW! https://ow.gameleap.com/ - Learn from Top 500 Pros and carry your games!\n\nIn this guide, we'll be covering the top 5 pro Moira tips and tricks to instantly improve your gameplay on the scientist of Talon!\n\nThanks for watching. If you have any questions or want to reach us, please send an email at support@game-leap.com and we will get back to you shortly." </summary>
    </meta>
    <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=7osDCnV7pKQ/</link>
    <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/7osDCnV7pKQ/sddefault.jpg</thumbnail>
</item>

<item>
    <title>Overwatch | How The Pros Play MOIRA - A Korean MUST PICK?!</title>
    <meta>
        <summary>b"Moira is having a huge rise in popularity in the pro scene. We go over why and how she's being used and why the Korean's are playing her an absolute tonne!\n CHECK OUT THIS AWESOME RGB KEYBOARD WE USE http://hyperx.gg/RGBOWC \n__\nFollow us!\nTwitter: https://twitter.com/OWCentral\nTwitch - Mysca: http://www.twitch.tv/mysca_\nTwitch - Ryan: http://www.twitch.tv/ryancentral_\n__\n\nMusic: Epidemic Sound\n\nApproaching Nirvana - Super Happy Fun Time\nhttp://youtube.com/user/approachingnirvana\nApproaching Nirvana on iTunes: https://itunes.apple.com/us/artist/approaching-nirvana/id313583565\n__\n\nThanks for watching! #Overwatch" </summary>
    </meta>
    <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=9JUlDVSUryo/</link>
    <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/9JUlDVSUryo/sddefault.jpg</thumbnail>
</item>

<item>
    <title>Overwatch: BEST Moira Playstyle - Advanced Guide</title>
    <meta>
        <summary>b"Since Moira released in Overwatch you guys have wanted a guide, well i took some time to analyze and learn moira so i could make an advanced tips video talking about her best, current playstyle! Let us know what you think and be sure to drop a Like & Subscribe if you enjoyed!\nSubscribe here - http://bit.ly/2aN1OuO\n\nRazer makes the best equipment, check out here! http://rzr.to/lnvvm\n\nWe are YOUR OVERWATCH:\nDestiny Channel: https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCb4Jomiox07xosU843EYTiw\nPatreon - https://www.patreon.com/YourOverwatch\nTwitter - https://twitter.com/youroverwatchyt\nTwitch - https://www.twitch.tv/youroverwatch \n\nDiscord Server:\nhttps://discordapp.com/invite/youroverwatch\n\nFREEDO's personal channel for Overwatch esports talk and more!\nhttps://www.youtube.com/user/xfreeedo" </summary>
    </meta>
    <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=jqqciZm65-Y/</link>
    <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/jqqciZm65-Y/sddefault.jpg</thumbnail>
</item>

<item>
    <title>Overwatch Moira Guide : Basic In-Depth Guide for Ability Usage and Team Tips | OverwatchDojo</title>
    <meta>
        <summary>b"--~--\nWhat can Moira do and how to play her? No fancy shenanigans here, we are going through the basics and show you different usages for her abilities, and the best ways to participate in team play. Made by our top500 support coach so you can be sure that the info here is coming from the best source.\n\nImprove your Overwatch game with video training materials from Overwatchdojo. If you want to know how to get better at Overwatch, Blizzard's flagship game, Overwatch Dojo not only has weekly videos, but you can also join the dojo discord to find friends and training partners: http://overwatchdojo.com/discord. Owdojo is a place for players dedicated to training and improvement!\n\nIf you like what we are doing, please SUBSCRIBE and give a thumbs up! You can also follow us on different social media platforms:\n\nJoin our Discord: https://discordapp.com/invite/Dd8Fw2a\nPledge on Patreon: https://www.patreon.com/overwatchdojo\n\nAccelerate your improvement with private coaching from our GM and Top500 team: https://www.patreon.com/overwatchdojo\n\nWebsite: http://overwatchdojo.com\nFacebook: https://www.facebook.com/overwatchdojo/\nTwitter: https://twitter.com/owdojo\n---\nOutro Music: Jim Yosef - Forces (feat. Ivan Jamile & Kdo Rebelle) https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ZWOA6lQiETk\nGraphics by: http://ambruskrisztian.hu\nEditing by: Taun_Taun777 www.kordellballard.com and https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCM6sbFpqdJ8aKlXryMPFeeA" </summary>
    </meta>
    <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=b9ylQd684zQ/</link>
    <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/b9ylQd684zQ/sddefault.jpg</thumbnail>
</item>

<item>
    <title>Overwatch: BEST Moira Playstyle - Everything You NEED to Know!</title>
    <meta>
        <summary>b"Moira should be coming out any day now and with some practice on the PTR with her Overwatch Gameplay we have some tips for you to hit the ground running with her cool ability set! Be undivable, dodge abilities with fade burst heal like Ana used to, Moira has some serious power if you wield it right, so much that some think it'll get a nerf, but I don't think a significant one is on the horizon yet, so get ready for the Moira Meta with this advanced guide! \n\nSubscribe here - http://bit.ly/2aN1OuO\n\nRazer makes the best equipment, check out here! http://rzr.to/lnvvm\n\nWe are YOUR OVERWATCH:\nDestiny Channel: https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCb4Jomiox07xosU843EYTiw\nPatreon - https://www.patreon.com/YourOverwatch\nTwitter - https://twitter.com/youroverwatchyt\nTwitch - https://www.twitch.tv/youroverwatch \n\nDiscord Server:\nhttps://discordapp.com/invite/youroverwatch\n\nFREEDO's personal channel for Overwatch esports talk and more!\nhttps://www.youtube.com/user/xfreeedo" </summary>
    </meta>
    <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=likgcHYkWxg/</link>
    <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/likgcHYkWxg/sddefault.jpg</thumbnail>
</item>

<item>
    <title>Overwatch | The Pro MOIRA Playstyle - How Custa Plays Moira (First Tournament Gameplay)</title>
    <meta>
        <summary>b"Custa showed us how Moira can be played in the Hulktastic cup we saw this weekend. Let's go over the good bits of the new hero but also the problems too!\nCusta Twitch: https://www.twitch.tv/custaa\n CHECK OUT THE HYPERX CLOUD ALPHA http://hyperx.gg/AlphaOverwatchCentral \n__\nFollow us!\nTwitter: https://twitter.com/OWCentral\nTwitch - Mysca: http://www.twitch.tv/mysca_\nTwitch - Ryan: http://www.twitch.tv/ryancentral_\n__\n\nMusic: Epidemic Sound\n\nApproaching Nirvana - Super Happy Fun Time\nhttp://youtube.com/user/approachingnirvana\nApproaching Nirvana on iTunes: https://itunes.apple.com/us/artist/approaching-nirvana/id313583565\n__\n\nThanks for watching! #Overwatch" </summary>
    </meta>
    <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=OFP2-XAtXiI/</link>
    <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/OFP2-XAtXiI/sddefault.jpg</thumbnail>
</item>

<item>
    <title>Overwatch | 10 COMMON MISTAKES MOIRA PLAYERS MAKE</title>
    <meta>
        <summary>b'Moira released in comp today so we wanted to go over some common mistakes you may be making playing the new hero.\n CHECK OUT THE HYPERX CLOUD ALPHA http://hyperx.gg/AlphaOverwatchCentral \n__\nFollow us!\nTwitter: https://twitter.com/OWCentral\nTwitch - Mysca: http://www.twitch.tv/mysca_\nTwitch - Ryan: http://www.twitch.tv/ryancentral_\n__\n\nMusic: Epidemic Sound\n\nApproaching Nirvana - Super Happy Fun Time\nhttp://youtube.com/user/approachingnirvana\nApproaching Nirvana on iTunes: https://itunes.apple.com/us/artist/approaching-nirvana/id313583565\n__\n\nThanks for watching! #Overwatch' </summary>
    </meta>
    <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=PloTitkBmCY/</link>
    <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/PloTitkBmCY/sddefault.jpg</thumbnail>
</item>

<item>
    <title>Moira - Overwatch One Trick Guide</title>
    <meta>
        <summary>b'Hey Overwatch give me that fat Moira SUCC\n\nTwitter - https://twitter.com/BrickyOrchid8\nTwitch - http://www.twitch.tv/brickyorchid8\nBigBrickPlays - https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCHcODW8jrSHWw7Na0dC6qcA\nInstagram - BrickyOrchid8\n\nIronside Computers | Click here to customize your own PC -  http://ironsidecomputers.com\n\nLF Gaming Chairs - https://lfgaming.com/shop/?ref=11\n\nP.O. Box\nBrickyOrchid8\n22365 El Toro Road.\nLake Forest, CA 92630\n#338\n\nAll P.O BOX items sent will be opened every other week!' </summary>
    </meta>
    <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=5z5g8uNc3SM/</link>
    <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/5z5g8uNc3SM/sddefault.jpg</thumbnail>
</item>

<item>
    <title>Moira orbs from spawn: A trigonometry guide on the best angles</title>
    <meta>
        <summary>b"Guide on some of the angles I have found with Moira's orbs when running back from spawn. If you have found any more yourself I would be interested in seeing your discoveries, feel free to get in touch on here, or by my Twitter/Twitch below.\n\nI hope to make more videos like this if it peaks an interest so any support/critisism is greatly appreciated\n\nwww.twitch.tv/grizzle85\nTwitter: @Grizzle85Live\n\nMusic: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=q_hwqbhdQLI&t=" </summary>
    </meta>
    <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=c5cZbt3AV7c/</link>
    <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/c5cZbt3AV7c/sddefault.jpg</thumbnail>
</item>

<item>
    <title>100+ USEFUL MOIRA FADE JUMPS on EVERY MAP</title>
    <meta>
        <summary>b'The Moira vertical jump - done by jumping off of knee to shoulder height objects in the game can give you insane vertical mobility when using her fade ability. This is also called the "Fade Tech" jump. It\'s a little bit of an advanced trick, but mastering this will increase her mobility and raise her skill cap. You can find a ton more at https://reddit.com/r/Moirarollouts\n\nHere are time stamps for some USEFUL and PRACTICAL jumps on every map in the game.\n\n2CP (Assault) Maps\n\nHanamura - 1:01 \nHorizon Lunar Colony - 1:27\nTemple of Anubis - 1:37\nVolskaya Industries - 2:03\n\nHybrid Maps\n\nBlizzard World - 2:54\nEichenwalde - 3:31\nHollywood - 3:56\nKing\'s Row - 4:18\nNumbani - 4:42\n\nEscort (Payload) Maps\n\nDorado - 5:18\nJunkertown - 5:53\nRoute 66 - 6:17\nWatchpoint: Gibraltar - 6:53\n\nControl (KOTH) Maps\n\nIllios - 7:18\nLijiang Tower - 7:51\nNepal - 8:25\nOasis - 9:05\n\nTwitch  https://twitch.tv/KarQ (Stream 5x weekly)\nMerch  https://teespring.com/stores/karq  \nDiscord  https://discord.gg/karq\nTwitter  https://twitter.com/KarQGames\nInstagram  http://instagram.com/KarQGames\nFacebook  https://www.facebook.com/KarQGames/\n\n Music Used:\n\n Joakim Karud - Longing https://soundcloud.com/joakimkarud\n Defqwop ft. Strix - Heart Afire https://youtu.be/gJeh_dLjPN4 \n Cartoon ft. Jri Pootsmann - I Remember U https://youtu.be/3wjb3HtD32c' </summary>
    </meta>
    <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=te1vV4F6YDQ/</link>
    <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/te1vV4F6YDQ/sddefault.jpg</thumbnail>
</item>

