<item>
    <title>[NEW HERO - AVAILABLE ] Orisa Origin Story | Overwatch</title>
    <meta>
        <summary>b'Catch up with robotics prodigy Efi Oladele and meet her newest creation: Orisa!\n\nLearn more about Orisa : http://blizz.ly/Orisa \nRead the PTR patch notes: http://blizz.ly/2mQ0WqI\n\nBegin Your Watch: http://blizz.ly/BuyOverwatch\nLike Us on Facebook: http://www.facebook.com/playoverwatch\nFollow Us on Twitter: http://www.twitter.com/playoverwatch\nFollow us on Instagram: https://www.instagram.com/playoverwatch' </summary>
    </meta>
    <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Lvm0of3iDUU/</link>
    <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/Lvm0of3iDUU/sddefault.jpg</thumbnail>
</item>

<item>
    <title>Overwatch: Queen of CHEESE Comp - Orisa Advanced Guide</title>
    <meta>
        <summary>b"Orisa Overwatch Gameplay fits comfortably into the slow rez meta we're currently in. Her kit can feel unimpactful if you're unsure what her strengths are, but when focused she can be a serious maintank threat that can really throw the enemy off. Albeit a odd and different maintank style, one that fits better in the backline, with these tactics you can comfortably hold positioning and really be a nuisance to dislodge on either attack or defense depending on the map. If you found the guide helpful, be sure to leave a like! \n\nSubscribe here - http://bit.ly/2aN1OuO\n\nRazer makes the best equipment, check out here! http://rzr.to/lnvvm\n\nWe are YOUR OVERWATCH:\nDestiny Channel: https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCb4Jomiox07xosU843EYTiw\nPatreon - https://www.patreon.com/YourOverwatch\nTwitter - https://twitter.com/youroverwatchyt\nTwitch - https://www.twitch.tv/youroverwatch \n\nDiscord Server:\nhttps://discordapp.com/invite/youroverwatch\n\nFREEDO's personal channel for Overwatch esports talk and more!\nhttps://www.youtube.com/user/xfreeedo" </summary>
    </meta>
    <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=phZPdeisyIs/</link>
    <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/phZPdeisyIs/sddefault.jpg</thumbnail>
</item>

<item>
    <title>How to Play Orisa: In-Depth Overwatch Guide</title>
    <meta>
        <summary>b'1. 0:36 Fusion Driver (Primary Fire)\n2. 2:18 Fortify\n3. 3:51 Protective Barrier\n4. 8:16 Supercharger\n5. 11:26 Halt! (Alternate Fire)\n6. 16:59 Positioning\n7. 19:28 Target Selection\n8. 21:00 Gameplay Loop\n\nHow to Submit Zarya/Orisa Vods: https://goo.gl/uL9SSH\nWatch Live or Subscribe on Twitch at https://twitch.tv/CANAS1AN.\nGet updates on Twitter at https://twitter.com/CANAS1AN\nJoin the Discord to chat about games: https://discord.gg/4z8zDeB\nSubscribe on Youtube to see videos right away.\n\nThanks for watching!\n\nIf you would like to support my Youtube and Twitch content beyond subscribing and following, here is a link to my donation page. https://twitch.streamlabs.com/canas1an' </summary>
    </meta>
    <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=va5T-2F2Yo8/</link>
    <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/va5T-2F2Yo8/sddefault.jpg</thumbnail>
</item>

<item>
    <title>1 ORISA TIP for EVERY HERO ft. EvilToaster</title>
    <meta>
        <summary>b'Today we have the deep and soothing voice of EvilToaster giving us 1 ORISA tip against all 26 heroes. The man has dedicated 500+ hours on her, even before her buffs a few seasons back.\n\nEVILTOASTER Socials:\n\n- https://www.twitch.tv/eviltoaster\n\n\n\n KARQ SOCIALS:\n\nTwitch  https://twitch.tv/KarQ (Stream 5x weekly)\nDiscord  https://discord.gg/karq\nTwitter  https://twitter.com/KarQGames\nInstagram  http://instagram.com/KarQGames\nFacebook  https://www.facebook.com/KarQGames/\n\n- Thank you WestoT, Stonefors, Katmayla for helping me film!\n\n\n Music Used:\n\n Otis McDonald - Scarlet Fire https://youtu.be/8yOskhDn468\n Title: Virtuality by Rameses B\niTunes Download Link: https://itunes.apple.com/us/album/virtuality-single/id1200463118\nVideo Link: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=8j5bRbdUMf0\nListen on Spotify: https://open.spotify.com/album/4wEjN20VAiZLtx8EsLkuqT' </summary>
    </meta>
    <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=yXsgYr60_RQ/</link>
    <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/yXsgYr60_RQ/sddefault.jpg</thumbnail>
</item>

<item>
    <title>Orisa - From Beginner to Advanced in 20 Steps</title>
    <meta>
        <summary>b"Hello everyone, took me a while to make this one but these insights pretty much cover everything you need to know regarding how to improve your Orisa game including how to play against her.\n\nThe tips 1-10 are going to be building your fundamentals\nThe tips 11-20 are going to be advanced, building on top of the foundation that you acquire from the first ones.\nAnd the tips 16-20 are going to be focus on positioning, which is essential, those are the tips that will keep you going and continue to provide value throughout the match.\n\n+ the only crucial thing that i would like to add to the mechanics of Orisa is this:\n\nTry throwing your Halt a bit up/vertical, so when a fast opponent (e.g. Lucio, Genji, Tracer, Sombra) is cought with your Halt - they will not reach the floor alive, because it allows you to easily land all the shots as they are falling down. This completely nullifies any of the speed they have due to them being stuck mid-air and unable to dodge your bullets this way.\n\nAnyways, let's get to it. Enjoy and let me know if you found it useful\n\nCheck out the latest video:\n1 Guide To Rule Them All - https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=MJuWQ1yYC0A\n\n[Coaching]:\nIf you want to get coached 1 on 1 I am an Overwatch coach at gamersensei and you can book a lesson with me anytime here\nhttps://www.gamersensei.com/senseis/gorthax \n+ Use this promo code - gorthax. You will get 5$ discount for your first lesson with me!\n\nClick here to subscribe! - http://bit.ly/2ioY7Kk\n\nConnect with me on social media:\nTumblr - https://www.tumblr.com/blog/gorthax\nVK - https://vk.com/gorthax\nTWITTER - https://twitter.com/Gorthaks\nFACEBOOK - https://www.facebook.com/GorthaxGroup/\nTwitch - https://www.twitch.tv/gorthaxs" </summary>
    </meta>
    <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=JvKmmXmR1io/</link>
    <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/JvKmmXmR1io/sddefault.jpg</thumbnail>
</item>

<item>
    <title>Overwatch: How to Be a PRO Orisa - Halt Combos Advanced Guide</title>
    <meta>
        <summary>b"Orisa is a legit main tank playstyle after her last buff to enabling her turret playstyle, but a lot of the success comes from utilzing halt to either crowd control the enemy, or better yet, set up for cool combo's for your team to capitalize on. Halt + Hook was a very powerful force for South Korea, the crowd control Orisa-game on maps with environmental kills is key as well - and even more can be done to combo abilities with halt, even at longer ranges. If you enjoyed the video and found it useful, be sure to leave it a like! \n\nSubscribe here - http://bit.ly/2aN1OuO\n\nRazer makes the best equipment, check out here! http://rzr.to/lnvvm\n\nWe are YOUR OVERWATCH:\nDestiny Channel: https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCb4Jomiox07xosU843EYTiw\nPatreon - https://www.patreon.com/YourOverwatch\nTwitter - https://twitter.com/youroverwatchyt\nTwitch - https://www.twitch.tv/youroverwatch \n\nDiscord Server:\nhttps://discordapp.com/invite/youroverwatch\n\nFREEDO's personal channel for Overwatch esports talk and more!\nhttps://www.youtube.com/user/xfreeedo" </summary>
    </meta>
    <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=YjP0vTFtP_Y/</link>
    <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/YjP0vTFtP_Y/sddefault.jpg</thumbnail>
</item>

<item>
    <title>Overwatch - Orisa Survival Guide (Tips and Advice!)</title>
    <meta>
        <summary>b"Orisa is the newest tank hero to hit Overwatch. In this video we'll discuss best practices when using Orisa!\n\n HyperX - CHECK THEM OUT! http://hyperx.gg/UnitLost [AD]\n PATREON CAMPAIGN! http://www.patreon.com/unitlost\n Twitter https://twitter.com/unitlostgaming\n Live Stream http://www.twitch.tv/unitlost\n http://www.unitlost.com - Join our AWESOME community forums!\n\nSystem Specs\n\nIntel i7 6900K overclocked @ 4.6Ghz\nWater Loop Coolant: Mayhem Aurora Blue\nAdditional Static Pressure Fan: Corsair SP120 LED Blue High Static Pressure 120mm Fan\nStatic Pressure Fans: Corsair SP120 LED Blue High Static Pressure 120mm Fan - Twin Pack\n32GB Corsair 3000mhz Vengeance LPX DDR4 (4x8GB) \n2 x NVIDIA GeForce GTX 1080 Strix 8GB \nAsus ROG STRIX Intel X99 RGB LED GAMING ATX Motherboard\nWindows 10 Home (64-bit)\nIntel 400GB 750 PCIe SSD\n4TB S-ATAIII 6.0Gb/s \n4TB S-ATAIII 6.0Gb/s \nBlue Camo Vinyl\nCorsair Carbide 600C Windowed\nCase Fans: Corsair AF120 LED Blue Quiet Edition High Airflow 120mm Fan - Twin Pack\nAdditional Case Fan: Corsair AF120 LED Blue Quiet Edition High Airflow 120mm Fan\nBraided Cables: PSU Braided Extension Cable set Black\nPSU: 850W Corsair RMX Fully Modular" </summary>
    </meta>
    <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=I3dRDZzgC7Y/</link>
    <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/I3dRDZzgC7Y/sddefault.jpg</thumbnail>
</item>

<item>
    <title>ORISA - Overwatch One Trick Guide</title>
    <meta>
        <summary>b'CEASE YOUR GENJI PLAYING\n\nTwitter - https://twitter.com/BrickyOrchid8\nTwitch - http://www.twitch.tv/brickyorchid8\nBigBrickPlays - https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCHcODW8jrSHWw7Na0dC6qcA\nInstagram - BrickyOrchid8\n\nIronside Computers | Click here to customize your own PC -  http://ironsidecomputers.com\n\nLF Gaming Chairs - https://lfgaming.com/shop/?ref=11\n\nP.O. Box\nBrickyOrchid8\n22365 El Toro Road.\nLake Forest, CA 92630\n#338\n\nAll P.O BOX items sent will be opened every other week!' </summary>
    </meta>
    <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=N00Y4Sk2djA/</link>
    <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/N00Y4Sk2djA/sddefault.jpg</thumbnail>
</item>

<item>
    <title>How GRANDMASTER Players DESTROY With ORISA | MIRO - Overwatch Season 7 Competitive Guide</title>
    <meta>
        <summary>b'Today we are back again trying a top 500 tip Orisa video because I think its fun and people just love Orisa it seems. Today we are talking about how the grandmaster Orisa player can carry his competitive games in season 7 overwatch competitive ranked mode guide for overwatch season 7 placement matches and overwatch season 7 changes. Going over some Orisa season 7 tips and guide or whatever you want to call it. thanks! \n\n\n\n\nMore Videos! : https://www.youtube.com/playlist?list=PLefC4eOMnbRF5Xm7uCjfU73bh0ybup9Df\n\n\n\nGameplay: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Z7-vquGf8ww\nThumbnail: https://i.pinimg.com/736x/f8/38/7d/f8387dfa018ad1c59d108bb31b2663b1--wallpaper-overwatch-overwatch-fanart.jpg\n-----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------\n\n\n\n======================================================================\n\nTIPS I WROTE DOWN FROM THE VIDEO:\n-Orisa is finally meta, has one of the highest winrates in the game\n-She is broken in cheese comps and spam comps, but even works with hitscan comps well\n-always take high ground and spam from there\n-if shield goes down, tank for your dps with shift\n-Dva can spam well with your shield, and block burst that destroys your shield\n---The first point they do pretty terrible and dont get enough kills, but last point is a great hold\n-spam wth your shield around corners\n-When close up, use alt fire to get easier headshots\n-put your shield far ahead while pushing up, put it up for teammates not yourself\n-if you can kill a support in a fight shoot at them, otherwise just target the tanks\n-use your ult at the start of the fight, its a waste to use at any other time\n-shoot to where your targets neck will probably be once they move up\n-use alt fire to make so enemy can never abuse high ground vs you\n-combo your alt fire with junkrat mines for a billion ult charge for junkrat\n-stay as a frontline tank even if one guy sneaks onto the point, dont tunelvision\n\n-put your shield up early  to setup on, and tank shots for your bastion\n-junkrat cannot destroy your shield by himself, you can outspam him in they play slowly\n-shoot at the enemy orisa shield at all times when you cant hit anybody\n-callout when you are going for the minigrav so people can get the free picks\n-its hard for you to push out in the open, just keep trying to poke with teammates until you get a pick\n-always stay behind, next to, or on the point. He is never doing anything else\n-shoot at the enemy bastion first, you destroy bastion with your damage as you cant miss a shot\n-the second you get ressed put down a shield to save your mercy\n\n\n\n======================================================================\n\n\n\n\n\nWhat is overwatch?: Well overwatch is Blizzards new take on the fps genre. In this game you choose a hero or "Class" to take on enemies, push payloads, and take control points. The point of the game is to beat the other team over and it is indeed a whole bunch of fun to play. The game includes 27 heroes so far and Is a blast to play. In this video I mostly go over playing it in a commentary type of manner, and these types of videos will usually be overwatch live commentaries or overwatch group commentaries. As well expect a few guides of this game in the future and some box openings as well. Anyways, hope you enjoy blizzards new hit!\'\n\nWho is JoeKing aka me. Im a overwatch youtuber that likes to talk about character updates, how to get better, and the competitive community. Trying to help you get better at overwatch and entertain at the same time hopefully. How GRANDMASTER Players DESTORY with Orisa - Overwatch Top 500 PRO Tricks Overwatch - 20 TricksOrisa Grandmasters ABUSE That You Don\'t! Some tips and tricks to master Orisa! Overwatch - 7 OP Tips and Tricks Grandmaster Players use every game! Orisa overwatch, Orisa guide top 500 tips and tricks  Orisa master gameplay, how Orisa is played, shadowburn gameplay Orisa overwatch competitive esports vod grandmaster Orisa tricks grandmaster top 500 Orisa, overwatch top 700 Orisa esports vod Orisa esports gameplay, grandmaster Orisa tricks top 500 tricks tips, how to play Orisa, Orisa season 7, overwatch competitive season 7 Orisa, Orisa season 7 offense, Orisa season 7 defense, overwatch season 7 Orisa guide       overwatch,Orisa tricks,Tricks Orisa Grandmasters ABUSE That You Don\'t,Tricks Orisa Grandmasters ABUSE That You Don\'t overwatch,overwatch Tricks Orisa Grandmasters ABUSE That You Don\'t,tricks grandmasters abuse that you dont,overwatch tricks grandmasters abuse that you dont,grandmaster tricks overwatch,Orisa grandmaster,Orisa top 500 trick,How GRANDMASTER Players DESTROY with Orisa,Orisa season 7 competitive,Orisa vod,grandmaster, Orisa seagull, seagull Orisa, best Orisa, strongest Orisa, best Orisa player, overwatch seagull\n\n\n\nTitle:How GRANDMASTER Players DESTROY With Orisa | MIRO - Overwatch Season 7 Competitive Guide Tips' </summary>
    </meta>
    <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=1LN5lFX06Qo/</link>
    <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/1LN5lFX06Qo/sddefault.jpg</thumbnail>
</item>

<item>
    <title>Overwatch Coaching - Orisa - BRONZE 1405 SR - [OverAnalyzed]</title>
    <meta>
        <summary>b'Overwatch Orisa coaching! Welcome to OverAnalyzed! In this series, we as a community help our fellow players with tips and advice on how to become better players!\n\nOrisa thumbnail art (amazing stuff!) http://b1tterrabbit.deviantart.com/art/Overwatch-Orisa-668416221\n\n\n UNIT LOST STORE! http://bit.ly/ulstore\n HyperX - CHECK THEM OUT! http://bit.ly/UnitLostFPS [AD]\n Discord JOIN NOW! http://discord.gg/unitlost  \n PATREON CAMPAIGN! http://www.patreon.com/unitlost\n Twitter https://twitter.com/unitlostgaming\n Live Stream http://www.twitch.tv/unitlost\n http://www.unitlost.com - Join our AWESOME community forums!\n\nSystem Specs\n\nIntel i7 6900K overclocked @ 4.6Ghz\nWater Loop Coolant: Mayhem Aurora Blue\nAdditional Static Pressure Fan: Corsair SP120 LED Blue High Static Pressure 120mm Fan\nStatic Pressure Fans: Corsair SP120 LED Blue High Static Pressure 120mm Fan - Twin Pack\n32GB Corsair 3000mhz Vengeance LPX DDR4 (4x8GB) \n2 x NVIDIA GeForce GTX 1080 Strix 8GB \nAsus ROG STRIX Intel X99 RGB LED GAMING ATX Motherboard\nWindows 10 Home (64-bit)\nIntel 400GB 750 PCIe SSD\n4TB S-ATAIII 6.0Gb/s \n4TB S-ATAIII 6.0Gb/s \nBlue Camo Vinyl\nCorsair Carbide 600C Windowed\nCase Fans: Corsair AF120 LED Blue Quiet Edition High Airflow 120mm Fan - Twin Pack\nAdditional Case Fan: Corsair AF120 LED Blue Quiet Edition High Airflow 120mm Fan\nBraided Cables: PSU Braided Extension Cable set Black\nPSU: 850W Corsair RMX Fully Modular' </summary>
    </meta>
    <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=XAlInY3FnKw/</link>
    <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/XAlInY3FnKw/sddefault.jpg</thumbnail>
</item>

<item>
    <title>Orisa Tips and Tricks | Fuel Pro Tips | Cocco</title>
    <meta>
        <summary>b'*Please help our videos reach everyone by adding close captions*\nhttp://www.youtube.com/timedtext_cs_panel?c=UCj4XSmDqIhRT4frKzRTMyrA&tab=2\n\n#DallasFuel #Burnblue\n\nDress like the Fuel:\nhttps://gear.blizzard.com/us/dallas-fuel\n\nFollow the Fuel:\nFacebook:\nhttp://facebook.com/TheDallasFuel\n\nInstagram:\nhttp://instagram.com/DallasFuel \n\nYouTube:\nhttp://youtube.com/DallasFuel' </summary>
    </meta>
    <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=_eDMALUJbIo/</link>
    <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/_eDMALUJbIo/sddefault.jpg</thumbnail>
</item>

<item>
    <title>Overwatch - Orisa Guide " Complete Hero Breakdown"</title>
    <meta>
        <summary>b'Join the community at http://overwatch.gamepedia.com\n\nOrisa is one of the most versatile tanks in Overwatch and an unforgettable force on the battlefield.\n\nFollow us so you dont miss our next video! https://www.twitch.tv/curse\n\nFollow Curse: \nhttps://twitter.com/cursenetwork\nhttps://www.facebook.com/CurseNetwork\n\nFollow our Hosts:\nMitch"Dash" D http://twitter.com/dashstarwars \n\nThanks for watching! Enjoy the game.' </summary>
    </meta>
    <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=0dJq7y7G9ZI/</link>
    <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/0dJq7y7G9ZI/sddefault.jpg</thumbnail>
</item>

<item>
    <title>OVERWATCH ORISA GUIDE #1: WHEN BARRIERS FAIL</title>
    <meta>
        <summary>b'Time for an Overwatch Orisa Guide! "When Barriers Fail" is a new twist on the usual guides that provide Orisa tips - this video focuses on adapting to mistakes and unpredictable moments in the game. Allowing inconsistent play to exist by mapping a plan that is modified as you go along helps build great instincts with this hero.\n\nToxic Coaching, The album. Now available on all digital platforms:\n\niTunes\n\nhttp://itunes.apple.com/album/id1341098540?ls=1&app=itunes\n\nApple Music\n\nhttp://itunes.apple.com/album/id/1341098540\n\nSpotify\n\nhttps://open.spotify.com/album/5BEEVde6IP6iUT31rCT78T\n\nAmazon Music\n\nhttps://www.amazon.com/dp/B079C7748Q/ref=cm_sw_r_cp_ep_dp_B1FDAbMFGNN60\n\n\nhttps://twitch.tv/ragtagg\n\nSupport me on Patreon: \n\nhttps://www.patreon.com/Ragtagg\n\nWant to support the most useless YouTuber in the world? Go get your noblechairs or sweet rigs here cuz I get stingy waitress tips if you do. Erm. Remember to turn off your ad block if you buy one because my tips get eaten from the referral! :\n\nhttps://www.overclockers.co.uk/gaming/gaming-chairs/noblechairs?tap_a=3815-35cbe9&tap_s=134467-8b1a06\n\nMY PC RIG:\n\nCase: Phanteks Evolv ATX with dank tempered glass side panel\nFully Watercooled loop Phanteks / EK Hardware\nMOBO: Asus ROG Crosshair VI Hero X370\nCPU: Ryzen 7 1800x 8 core 4.0ghz turbo\nGFX: Asus Strix OC GTX 1080 TI\nRAM: Team Group Vulcan 16gb 3000mhz\nPSU: Super Flower Leadex II 650W GOLD\nSSD: Samsung 960 EVO NVMe 500gb\nHDD: Seagate Baracuda 6TB\nMouse: Rival 700\nPad: Logitech G640\nKeyboard: Steel Series M800\nMonitor: Asus VG248QE 144HZ\nHeadphones: DT 770 PRO 32 Ohms' </summary>
    </meta>
    <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=HBuahZztMWI/</link>
    <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/HBuahZztMWI/sddefault.jpg</thumbnail>
</item>

<item>
    <title>Orisa - Overwatch Hero Guide</title>
    <meta>
        <summary>b'If safety is your primary concern, Orisa might be the perfect tank for you, and Joey has some tips on how to protect your teammates (and yourself!) with her.\n\nSubscribe to GameSpot! http://youtube.com/GameSpot?sub_confirmation=1\n\nCheck out more of our Overwatch Hero Guide!\nhttps://www.youtube.com/playlist?list=PLpg6WLs8kxGOwCOjDZVbCMuUCoLPPLW0V\n\nFind out about the Story of Overwatch:\nhttps://www.youtube.com/playlist?list=PLpg6WLs8kxGOjvBbzjWTtT0exaWsR58iB\n\nFollow Overwatch at GameSpot.com!\nhttp://www.gamespot.com/overwatch/\nOfficial Site - http://us.battle.net/overwatch/\n\nCheck out our review!\nWatch - https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=JF2nEfY_Thg\nRead - http://www.gamespot.com/reviews/overwatch-review/1900-6416439/\n\nVisit all of our channels:\nFeatures & Reviews - http://www.youtube.com/GameSpot\nVideo Game Trailers - http://www.youtube.com/GameSpotTrailers\nMovies, TV, & Comics - http://www.youtube.com/GameSpotUniverse\nGameplay & Guides - http://www.youtube.com/GameSpotGameplay\nMobile Gaming - http://www.youtube.com/GameSpotMobile\n\nLike  - http://www.facebook.com/GameSpot\nFollow - http://www.twitter.com/GameSpot\n\nhttp://www.gamespot.com' </summary>
    </meta>
    <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=HU5A7ezZanQ/</link>
    <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/HU5A7ezZanQ/sddefault.jpg</thumbnail>
</item>

<item>
    <title>#1 Orisa AceOFSpades - Beginners Guide To Orisa</title>
    <meta>
        <summary>b'https://www.twitch.tv/AceOFSpadesOW\nhttps://twitter.com/AceOFSpadesOW\nJoin my discord community for the latest updates!\nhttps://discord.gg/GfFWEVt' </summary>
    </meta>
    <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=TspvEn3ij6o/</link>
    <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/TspvEn3ij6o/sddefault.jpg</thumbnail>
</item>

<item>
    <title>Overwatch | Top 5 PRO Tips for Orisa - Win More Games! (ft EvilToaster)</title>
    <meta>
        <summary>b"Eviltoaster Twitch: https://www.twitch.tv/eviltoasterow\nEviltoaster Twitter: https://twitter.com/eviltoasterow\nOrisa's popularity has escalted a lot in season 6 so we decided to collaborate with one of the deadliest players on Overwatch's latest tank.\n CHECK OUT THE HYPERX CLOUD ALPHA http://hyperx.gg/AlphaOverwatchCentral \n__\nFollow us!\nTwitter: https://twitter.com/OWCentral\nTwitch - Mysca: http://www.twitch.tv/mysca_\nTwitch - Ryan: http://www.twitch.tv/ryancentral_\n__\n\nMusic: Epidemic Sound\n\nApproaching Nirvana - Super Happy Fun Time\nhttp://youtube.com/user/approachingnirvana\nApproaching Nirvana on iTunes: https://itunes.apple.com/us/artist/approaching-nirvana/id313583565\n__\n\nThanks for watching! #Overwatch" </summary>
    </meta>
    <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=9n5NxSusOeo/</link>
    <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/9n5NxSusOeo/sddefault.jpg</thumbnail>
</item>

<item>
    <title>Orisa: Advanced Halt Guide</title>
    <meta>
        <summary>b'Here is a quick advanced guide for maximizing your Orisa play.\n\n-----------------------------\n\nIf you liked this please make sure to subscribe to Nathanael Platier to get updated on new releases!' </summary>
    </meta>
    <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=FTpKppoyKF4/</link>
    <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/FTpKppoyKF4/sddefault.jpg</thumbnail>
</item>

<item>
    <title>7 Shield Barrier Tips and Tricks | Overwatch Advanced Orisa Guide</title>
    <meta>
        <summary>b'In this video we go over additional Shield Barrier Tips and Tricks for Orisa.' </summary>
    </meta>
    <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=DCvMtEVdV5o/</link>
    <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/DCvMtEVdV5o/sddefault.jpg</thumbnail>
</item>

<item>
    <title>Overwatch TOP 10 ORISA TIPS - Advanced Guide - The Omnic Tank</title>
    <meta>
        <summary>b'Overwatch Orisa Ultimate guide and top 10 tips\n Get COOL rewards and support the channel! https://www.patreon.com/blamethecontroller\n Check out more TOP 5, Tips, and Guides below \n\nHey! Hit that Like button and leave a comment!\n Subscribe - http://bit.ly/SubscribeBTC \n TwitchTV - http://www.twitch.tv/blamethecontroller\n Twitter - http://twitter.com/BlameTC\n Instagram - http://instagram.com/blamethecontroller\n Facebook - http://www.facebook.com/BlameTheController\n Discord Server - https://discord.gg/blamethecontroller\n\n\n  T-SHIRT  SHOP \nhttp://blamethecontroller.spreadshirt.com/\n\n\n Send me Fanmail\nBTC  \nP.O. Box 97\nSpring, TX 77383\n\n ORISA - LEGENDARY SKINS + MORE - https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=HtaOiie7Cn8\n ORISA - ABILITIES - https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=dhtbjdgJGAU\n ORISA OR15 SKIN + VOICELINES - https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=qQBRYzUqzIg\n ORISA GAMEPLAY part 1  https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=KnkHlTb__EA\n ORISA GAMEPLAY part 2 - https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=eeELoPHGJxM\n ORISA GAMEPLAY part 3 - https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=PEndmynm9eg\n ORISA GAMEPLAY part 4 - https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=hu18wgvMI5c\n\n\n\n TOP 5 TIPS and Tricks:  https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=3dEIQ6qrH1g\n TOP 5 TIPS for TEAMWORK: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=0pseL1QkMGs\n TOP 5 TIPS for HERO PICKS:  https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=RFTzCy6u11M\n TOP 5 TIPS for IMPROVING AIM: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=71fehVACdyc \n TOP 5 TIPS FOR CUSTOMIZATION: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ps8bZ_FjHBM\n\n TOP 5 Best Teams for 3v3 https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=2cYk-Gdeabc\n\n Sombra Top 10 Tips: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=BIW-gudOn18\n Overwatch Mythbusters - Sombra Teleporting: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=JWHmukikcSQ\n Overwatch Mythbusters - Sombra Invisibility: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=hHDYCIb70fQ\n Overwatch Mythbusters - Sombra Hack and EMP: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=b_y8X4ORSjM\n\n Reaper Trick on Oasis https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=vRfNETeikdU\n Symmetra Best Locations for Shield Generator Ultimates https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=nLSZ_ynuihQ' </summary>
    </meta>
    <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Ch_ZbAqjca8/</link>
    <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/Ch_ZbAqjca8/sddefault.jpg</thumbnail>
</item>

<item>
    <title>Overwatch Orisa Aim Tutorial Guide | How To Play Orisa Drills For Improvement OwDojo</title>
    <meta>
        <summary>b"--~--\nOrisa aiming guide + tips and tricks about her abilities. Learn how to land your shots with her, master your aim with these drills. We are going to show you how to practice controlling her abilities (the Halt! and barrier) in order to be the most effective in a team.\n\nOrisa has a high DPS for a tank, but she can go down quickly if handled incorrectly. By training your Orisa aim and drilling how to control other aspects of her play, you will be able to utilize her to the fullest potential. These are basic drills, exercises that you can do to build your basics with Orisa.\n\nDrill sheet: https://drive.google.com/open?id=0B6X5OZ2NG04pajY4NXhpU2tqVU0\n\nTimestamps:\n0:20 Birefly about Orisa's role in Overwatch\n0:51 STATIC DRILLS\n1:06 Tracking Warmup\n1:22 Tracking Advanced Moves\n1:43 Halt! Ability Control\n2:19 Peeking Practice\n2:43 DYNAMIC DRILLS\n3:02 Shoot From Standing\n3:21 Shooting Moving Bots\n3:40 Halt! and Barrier Placement\n4:17 Shooting From Top\n4:37 Advanced Training\n4:58 Join the dojo!\n\nIf you like what we are doing, please SUBSCRIBE and give a thumbs up! You can also follow us on different social media platforms:\n\nJoin our Discord: https://discordapp.com/invite/Dd8Fw2a\nPledge on Patreon: https://www.patreon.com/overwatchdojo\n\nSupport Overwatchdojo on Patreon: https://www.patreon.com/overwatchdojo\n\nWebsite: http://overwatchdojo.com\nFacebook: https://www.facebook.com/overwatchdojo/\nTwitter: https://twitter.com/owdojo\nThumblr: https://www.tumblr.com/blog/overwatchdojo\nGoogle+: https://plus.google.com/b/113411751621981370622/113411751621981370622\n---\nIntro Music: TheFatRat - Monody (feat. Laura Brehm) https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=nw5Mc5bpq-A\nOutro Music: Jim Yosef - Forces (feat. Ivan Jamile & Kdo Rebelle) https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ZWOA6lQiETk\nBackground music: https://youtu.be/DxdfDE-qSnM\nGraphics by: http://ambruskrisztian.hu" </summary>
    </meta>
    <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=5wO3NuE_ngI/</link>
    <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/5wO3NuE_ngI/sddefault.jpg</thumbnail>
</item>

<item>
    <title>Orisa Advanced Console Guide</title>
    <meta>
        <summary>b"For the basic info on Orisa's kit see my basic guide on her. \r\n\r\nWith so many guides for her out there I felt some assumed you understand every term and didn't really cover a few things a little more in depth. So I made my own! \r\n\r\nI hope this can help you improve your Orisa gameplay. \r\n\r\nPlease like and subscribe. I hope to make some more fun videos in the future." </summary>
    </meta>
    <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=N2LkCyF4OOk/</link>
    <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/N2LkCyF4OOk/sddefault.jpg</thumbnail>
</item>

<item>
    <title>Top 5 ORISA TECHNIQUES #3 - Overwatch</title>
    <meta>
        <summary>b"This time with a lot of Halt!\n\nOrisa Tech Playlist: https://www.youtube.com/playlist?list=PLo7v7DiLjvNQ7MsWKUR9WUDEIsvaNqvuQ\n\nMusic:\nOutro Music: Gutter Spin by Risuno\n\n_\n\nSponsor the channel!\nhttps://www.patreon.com/user?ty=h&u=365391\n\nJoin us on Discord!\nhttps://discord.gg/013TrfIYpypOZo3Cr\n\nI do not permit reuploading a translation of my content.\n\n-\n\nThis is included to optimize Youtube's bullshit algorithm:\nTerioth, Terioth Overwatch, Terioth Tips, Terioth Tricks, Terioth Guide, Overwatch, Orisa Overwatch, Orisa Tips, Orisa Tricks, Orisa Guide, Orisa In-depth, Orisa Strategy, Orisa How To, Orisa Gameplay, Orisa Tips Gameplay, Orisa Tricks Gameplay, Orisa Gameplay Guide, Orisa In-depth Gameplay, Orisa Strategy Gameplay, Orisa How To Gameplay, Orisa Beginners Guide, Orisa Ultimate, Orisa Play of the Game, Orisa PotG, Orisa Plays" </summary>
    </meta>
    <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=t8kiVgGN7uo/</link>
    <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/t8kiVgGN7uo/sddefault.jpg</thumbnail>
</item>

<item>
    <title>Overwatch | Top 10 Mistakes Orisa Players Make</title>
    <meta>
        <summary>b"With Orisa now in the competitive scene. We put together our top 10 mistakes that players make about Orisa. This includes playing her, playing against her and playing with one on your team. Overwatch's latest hero isn't the strongest pick in the game but she's definitely not the weakest so we wanted to highlight some misconceptions as well as give some tips to utilize the omnic.\n\n__\n\n Need a new headset? Buy this one and support us! http://hyperx.gg/StingerOWC [AD]\n\n Send in your own clips: http://goo.gl/forms/JsizriSpRL\n__\n\nFollow us!\nTwitch: http://www.twitch.tv/overwatchcentral\nTwitter: https://twitter.com/OWCentral\nGoogle+: https://plus.google.com/+OverwatchCentral\n__\n\nMusic: Epidemic Sound\n\nApproaching Nirvana - Super Happy Fun Time\nhttp://youtube.com/user/approachingnirvana\nApproaching Nirvana on iTunes: https://itunes.apple.com/us/artist/approaching-nirvana/id313583565\n__\n\nThanks for watching! #Overwatch" </summary>
    </meta>
    <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=S6y4Aa9FfSQ/</link>
    <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/S6y4Aa9FfSQ/sddefault.jpg</thumbnail>
</item>

<item>
    <title>How To Actually Play Orisa</title>
    <meta>
        <summary>b"Please enjoy this thoughtful and intriguing Orisa guide, stay tuned for more goodies coming soon\nAnimator's twitter: https://twitter.com/GummyDona\nMy own twitter: https://twitter.com/mikasacus\n\nTo add an extra word, don't be hung up about the month bit, it could be sooner, it could be a month, or it could be a month and a bit, really it depends on what kind of schedule blizzard adds to the game\n\nI think Jeff Kaplan is one of the most brilliant game developer minds alive today\n\nToday In Good Music: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Cs4qZ9SBubc\n\nMusic: (Legalities Below)\nCashmere - BADBADNOTGOOD\nIpanema Daydream - Bird Creek\nTalky Beat - Twin Musicom\nActually, Like - Twin Musicom\nSideways Samba - Audionautix \n\nTalky Beat by Twin Musicom is licensed under a Creative Commons Attribution license (https://creativecommons.org/licenses/by/4.0/)\nSource: http://www.twinmusicom.org/song/265/talky-beat\nArtist: http://www.twinmusicom.org\nSideways Samba by Audionautix is licensed under a Creative Commons Attribution license (https://creativecommons.org/licenses/by/4.0/)\nArtist: http://audionautix.com/\nActually, Like by Twin Musicom is licensed under a Creative Commons Attribution license (https://creativecommons.org/licenses/by/4.0/)\nArtist: http://www.twinmusicom.org/" </summary>
    </meta>
    <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=eYib3ORpIFM/</link>
    <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/eYib3ORpIFM/sddefault.jpg</thumbnail>
</item>

