###################################################################################
  <thumbnail>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PiDiaries/wow/master/sprays/pharah.png</thumbnail>
<fanart>https://d1u1mce87gyfbn.cloudfront.net/media/screenshot/pharah-screenshot-003.jpg</fanart>
  <summary>Soaring through the air in her combat armor, and armed with a launcher that lays down high-explosive rockets, Pharah is a force to be reckoned with.
  
 Fareeha Amari's commitment to duty runs in her blood. She comes from a long line of highly decorated soldiers and burns with the desire to serve with honor.

As a child, Fareeha dreamed of following in her mother's footsteps and joining the global peacekeeping force, Overwatch. She enlisted in the Egyptian army, and her dogged persistence and tactical prowess caused her to rise up through the officer ranks. She was a courageous leader and earned the loyalty of all who served under her. With her exemplary record, Fareeha was well placed to join the ranks of Overwatch, but before she had that opportunity, Overwatch was disbanded.

After leaving the army with a commendation for distinguished service, she was offered employment with Helix Security International, a private security firm contracted to defend the artificial intelligence research facility beneath the Giza Plateau. The top-secret facility was touted as vital to the safety of not only the region but countries across the globe. Fareeha gladly accepted the choice assignment and received training in the Raptora Mark VI, an experimental combat suit designed for rapid mobility and devastating firepower.

Under the call sign "Pharah," she works to safeguard the AI installation. Though she mourns Overwatch's passing, she still dreams of fighting the good fight and making a difference on a global scale.
 </summary>
###################################################################################
<item>
<title>Pharah Ability Overview</title>
<link>https://youtu.be/ks-mLJS0pe8</link>
<summary>Hailing from a long line of decorated soldiers, Fareeha Amari's commitment to duty and honor runs in her blood. Under the call sign "Pharah," Fareeha currently serves as a security chief for the private security firm Helix Security International, though she dreams of fighting the good fight and making a difference on a global scale. 

Soaring through the air in her Raptora Mark VI combat suit, and armed with a rocket launcher that fires concussive and high-explosive rockets, Pharah is a force to be reckoned with for any who would threaten those under her guard.
</summary>
</item>


<item>
  <title>Overwatch - Pharah Guide - Justice Rains From Above! (Tips and Advice)</title>
  <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch/cvXOFG045NQ</link>
  <thumbnail></thumbnail>
  <summary>Pharah excels at dealing high amounts of damage, she has a fairly high initial skill celling, but once you get used to using her abilities, justice will surely rain from above!
  </summary>
</item>
