<item>
    <title>Pharah Ability Overview | Overwatch</title>
    <meta>
        <summary>b'Protect the innocent: http://bit.ly/MeetPharah\n\nHailing from a long line of decorated soldiers, Fareeha Amari\'s commitment to duty and honor runs in her blood. Under the call sign "Pharah," Fareeha currently serves as a security chief for the private security firm Helix Security International, though she dreams of fighting the good fight and making a difference on a global scale. \n\nSoaring through the air in her Raptora Mark VI combat suit, and armed with a rocket launcher that fires concussive and high-explosive rockets, Pharah is a force to be reckoned with for any who would threaten those under her guard.\n\nSign Up for Beta: http://bit.ly/JoinOverwatch \nLike Us on Facebook: http://www.facebook.com/playoverwatch \nFollow Us on Twitter: http://www.twitter.com/playoverwatch' </summary>
    </meta>
    <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ks-mLJS0pe8/</link>
    <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/ks-mLJS0pe8/sddefault.jpg</thumbnail>
</item>

<item>
    <title>Overwatch - Pharah Guide - Justice Rains From Above! (Tips and Advice)</title>
    <meta>
        <summary>b'Pharah excels at dealing high amounts of damage, she has a fairly high initial skill celling, but once you get used to using her abilities, justice will surely rain from above!\n\n PATREON CAMPAIGN! http://www.patreon.com/unitlost\n Twitter https://twitter.com/unitlostgaming\n Live Stream http://www.twitch.tv/unitlost\n http://www.unitlost.com - Join our AWESOME community forums!' </summary>
    </meta>
    <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=cvXOFG045NQ/</link>
    <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/cvXOFG045NQ/sddefault.jpg</thumbnail>
</item>

<item>
    <title>5 Tips for Playing NEW BUFFED PHARAH (Overwatch Guide)</title>
    <meta>
        <summary>b'5 Tips for Playing NEW BUFFED PHARAH (Overwatch Guide) Tips and tricks to learn how to play or improve your skills with new Pharah changes easy and rank up in competitive season 12 & carry from bronze, silver, gold, platinum, diamond and masters. If played right Pharah can be a deadly DPS hero! Goodluck\n\nMore Guides: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=sGQkmrWUvoI&t=22s&list=PLsSYS03ynFoEoy_5fYcyq1WehB3elOg8D&index=3\n\n\nIn this video we talk about: \nOverwatch Pharah Guide\nOverwatch Tips and tricks\nOverwatch Guide 2018\nOverwatch DPS Hero\n\n\nNEW DISCORD: Discord: https://discord.gg/UxEVpgt\n\n\n STAY CONNECTED! \n\n\nFollow Us on Social Media!\n Discord: https://discord.gg/UxEVpgt\n Twitter: https://twitter.com/Blizzard_Guides\n UG Twitter: http://Twitter.com/UltraGuides\n UG Discord: https://discord.gg/ultra\n Twitch: http://Twitch.tv/UltraGuides\n Instagram: https://www.instagram.com/overwatch.guides\n\nSources \nhttp://Twitch.tv/Valkia\nhttp://youtu.be/ix8fUIzINV0\n___\n\n\nThat just about does it for this video guys, if you liked 5 Tips for Playing NEW BUFFED PHARAH (Overwatch Guide) , hit that like button, if you want to see more videos like this as they are made public, subscribe. If you want to enter in some sick giveaways, you can follow us on twitter @UltraGuides. If you wanna hang with me and the other UG members, you can join our Discord server.  Thank you so much for staying till the end of the video. Stay amazing, and we will see you, in the next one.' </summary>
    </meta>
    <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=C0BSOktf9r8/</link>
    <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/C0BSOktf9r8/sddefault.jpg</thumbnail>
</item>

<item>
    <title>Grand Master Pharah: Guide to playing Pharah Effectively & How to stay alive</title>
    <meta>
        <summary>b"[SUBSCRIBE FOR MORE OVERWATCH CONTENT]\n\nWelcome to my new guide to playing Pharah, now that I've reached top 500 and Grand Master I've learnt quite a few tips and tricks to playing pharah, staying alive, and how to approach team fights. This video will educate you in a way that you'll learn how to play pharah including how to engage the enemy, how to think a few steps ahead playing pharah, using concussive blast to stay alive and for the element of suprise. The ultimate guide on how to rank up with pharah :)\n\nLearn to hit direct shots: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=F6z3jmf9jDw&t=1s\n\nLearn Airshots: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Xn66u_Mugnc\n\nLive Stream: http://www.twitch.tv/valkia\n\nSee more about HyperX here: http://geni.us/Valkia\n\n////////////////////////////////\n\nDon't forget to subscribe to my channel for Overwatch tips, tricks and tutorials. My guides are easy to follow and make it easy for learning. If you're wanting to improve your gameplay for Pharah, Tracer, Widowmaker and other heroes, make sure to follow the step-by-step quick guides to help you get better at heroes. All new content from Overwatch will be posted by me, including skins, legendary skins from loot boxes, new heroes, settings including how to set a custom crosshair, change language and more.\n\nTips and Tricks playlist: https://www.youtube.com/playlist?list=PLCLdaElD3CIoR4VLK-L4h8rG_6wSt2qGx\n\n////////////////////////////////\n\nFollow Me:\n\nhttp://www.twitch.tv/valkia\nhttp://www.twitter.com/markpurdy1337\nhttp://www.facebook.com/valkiatv\n\nBusiness email valkiatv@gmail.com" </summary>
    </meta>
    <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=CUAOZouBn-w/</link>
    <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/CUAOZouBn-w/sddefault.jpg</thumbnail>
</item>

<item>
    <title>Quick Guide: How to rank up with Pharah || Valkia</title>
    <meta>
        <summary>b'The ultimate rank / climb guide with Pharah.\n\nWelcome to my long awaited guide on "How to rank up with Pharah" - this tutorial covers what you should think about when playing Pharah to ensure you can be beneficial to the team. The video on climbing will hopefully help Pharah players from bronze, gold all the way to Grandmaster. \n\nPharah Tutorial Playlist: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=CUAOZouBn-w&list=PLCLdaElD3CIo1PGIuvLoJfIAQ1N_XUYxD\n\nMovement Guide: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=fyl9vTXBN_w&index=13&list=PLCLdaElD3CIo1PGIuvLoJfIAQ1N_XUYxD\n\n\n////////////////////////////////\n\nFollow Me:\nJoin Discord here: http://www.discord.gg/valkia\nhttp://www.twitch.tv/valkia\nhttp://www.twitter.com/officialvalkia\nhttp://www.facebook.com/valkiatv\n\nBusiness email valkiatv@gmail.com\n\n////////////////////////////////\n\nDon\'t forget to subscribe to my channel for Overwatch tips, tricks and tutorials. My guides are easy to follow and make it easy for learning. If you\'re wanting to improve your gameplay for Pharah, Tracer, Widowmaker and other heroes, make sure to follow the step-by-step quick guides to help you get better at heroes. All new content from Overwatch will be posted by me, including skins, legendary skins from loot boxes, new heroes, settings including how to set a custom crosshair, change language and more.\n\nTips and Tricks playlist: https://www.youtube.com/playlist?list=PLCLdaElD3CIoR4VLK-L4h8rG_6wSt2qGx\n\n////////////////////////////////\n\nSponsors:\n\nHyperX http://geni.us/Valkia\nNoblechairs http://bit.ly/valkianoblechair\nMSI https://goo.gl/LHLtk4' </summary>
    </meta>
    <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Nv8uzygtUvY/</link>
    <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/Nv8uzygtUvY/sddefault.jpg</thumbnail>
</item>

<item>
    <title>The Ultimate Pharah Movement Guide: How to fly forever, fuel management & more</title>
    <meta>
        <summary>b"[SUBSCRIBE FOR MORE OVERWATCH CONTENT]\n\nWelcome to the ultimate movement guide for Pharah. This video contains some Pharah gameplay which shows concussive blast techniques, tips and tricks - speed movements, how to fly forever, how to engage the enemy, planning flanking routes, staying alive with Pharah including fuel management with visuals helping you to learn. Pharah is a great hero. I've been Top 500 and currently Grandmaster with Pharah and these tips can help you rank up.\n\nHow to deal with hitscans: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=nkP1H0ggylo\n\n////////////////////////////////\n\nWant to support me?\n\nIf you love my content, you can support me by either donating or subscribing on Twitch.\n\nSubscribe here:  https://secure.twitch.tv/products/valkia/ticket\nHow to link Twitch Prime: https://help.twitch.tv/customer/portal/articles/2572060-twitch-prime-guide\n\n\n\n////////////////////////////////\n\nFollow Me:\n\nJoin Discord here: http://www.discord.gg/valkia\nhttp://www.twitch.tv/valkia\nhttp://www.twitter.com/markpurdy1337\nhttp://www.facebook.com/valkiatv\n\nBusiness email valkiatv@gmail.com\n\n////////////////////////////////\n\nDon't forget to subscribe to my channel for Overwatch tips, tricks and tutorials. My guides are easy to follow and make it easy for learning. If you're wanting to improve your gameplay for Pharah, Tracer, Widowmaker and other heroes, make sure to follow the step-by-step quick guides to help you get better at heroes. All new content from Overwatch will be posted by me, including skins, legendary skins from loot boxes, new heroes, settings including how to set a custom crosshair, change language and more.\n\nTips and Tricks playlist: https://www.youtube.com/playlist?list=PLCLdaElD3CIoR4VLK-L4h8rG_6wSt2qGx" </summary>
    </meta>
    <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=fyl9vTXBN_w/</link>
    <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/fyl9vTXBN_w/sddefault.jpg</thumbnail>
</item>

<item>
    <title>Overwatch Advanced Pharah Guide: High Impact Damage</title>
    <meta>
        <summary>b'In this Overwatch advanced guide, freedo gives tips on getting high impact damage with pharah. We believe this hero may become meta when the PTR Patch drops (hopefully this week).\nSubscribe here: https://www.youtube.com/c/youroverwatch?sub_confirmation=1\n\nWe are YOUR OVERWATCH:\nTwitch - https://www.twitch.tv/youroverwatch \nTwitter - https://twitter.com/youroverwatchyt\nSubscribe - http://bit.ly/2aN1OuO' </summary>
    </meta>
    <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=w89jEtqydds/</link>
    <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/w89jEtqydds/sddefault.jpg</thumbnail>
</item>

<item>
    <title>Overwatch | Pharah Advanced Movement and Aiming Guide ft Valkia</title>
    <meta>
        <summary>b"CHECK OUT VALKIA's STREAM: https://www.twitch.tv/valkia\nToday we take a close look at Pharah tips and tricks regarding movemenet and aim.\n__\n Need a new mouse? Check this one out! http://hyperx.gg/PulsefireOWC?track=YouTube [AD]\n\n Send in your own clips: http://goo.gl/forms/JsizriSpRL\n__\n\nFollow us!\nTwitch: http://www.twitch.tv/overwatchcentral\nTwitter: https://twitter.com/OWCentral\nGoogle+: https://plus.google.com/+OverwatchCentral\n__\n\nMusic: Epidemic Sound\n\nApproaching Nirvana - Super Happy Fun Time\nhttp://youtube.com/user/approachingnirvana\nApproaching Nirvana on iTunes: https://itunes.apple.com/us/artist/approaching-nirvana/id313583565\n__\n\nThanks for watching! #Overwatch" </summary>
    </meta>
    <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=lUkai2J7USU/</link>
    <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/lUkai2J7USU/sddefault.jpg</thumbnail>
</item>

<item>
    <title>Overwatch: Pharah Rocket Aim Mastery - Advanced Guide</title>
    <meta>
        <summary>b'Want to hit more rockets? In this video FREEDO breaks down in depth the different types of Pharah shots you want to go for and where to place your rockets so they connect. It\'s all about setting yourself up and predicting your target and this video breaks down how to attack at an angle, duel close range, mid-air and long range snipe. \n\n"Part 1" of my most recent Pharah guides https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=53PzjykFd2o&ab_channel=YourOverwatch \n\nMore Pharah! https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCEzOHrh9snmHJSGu9wmOvsw/search?query=pharah?&ab_channel=YourOverwatch\n\n\n\nSubscribe here: https://www.youtube.com/c/youroverwatch?sub_confirmation=1\n\nWe are YOUR OVERWATCH:\nTwitch - https://www.twitch.tv/youroverwatch \nTwitter - https://twitter.com/youroverwatchyt\nSubscribe - http://bit.ly/2aN1OuO\n\nDiscord Server:\nhttps://discordapp.com/invite/youroverwatch\n\nFREEDO\'s personal channel for Overwatch esports talk and more!\nhttps://www.youtube.com/user/xfreeedo' </summary>
    </meta>
    <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=w0SWeTny88g/</link>
    <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/w0SWeTny88g/sddefault.jpg</thumbnail>
</item>

<item>
    <title>1 PHARAH TIP for EVERY HERO ft. Valkia</title>
    <meta>
        <summary>b"Here is UK's finest Pharah player Valkia giving you 26 Pharah tips - 1 tip vs every hero to help you deal with the match-ups. Valkia has a fantastic YouTube channel that goes further in depth with Pharah matchups, strategies, and analysis. Tons of the content from this video was taken by him - please check his stuff out!\n\nhttps://twitch.tv/valkia\nhttps://youtube.com/valkia\n\n\n\nTwitch  https://twitch.tv/KarQ (Stream 5x weekly)\nMerch  https://teespring.com/stores/karq  \nDiscord  https://discord.gg/karq\nTwitter  https://twitter.com/KarQGames\nInstagram  http://instagram.com/KarQGames\nFacebook  https://www.facebook.com/KarQGames/\n\n\n Music Used:\n\n Otis McDonald - Scarlet Fire https://youtu.be/8yOskhDn468\n Sub.Sound - Feel the Buzz [NCS Release]\nhttps://youtu.be/L-pqDqfQf1k" </summary>
    </meta>
    <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=TgwQ30kS8-M/</link>
    <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/TgwQ30kS8-M/sddefault.jpg</thumbnail>
</item>

<item>
    <title>Pharah - Overwatch One Trick Guide</title>
    <meta>
        <summary>b'JUSTICE RAINS FROM BLEGHAAAA\n\nEdited by - https://twitter.com/BeardBoxGaming\n\nTwitter - https://twitter.com/Bricky\nTwitch - http://www.twitch.tv/bricky\nBigBrickPlays - https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCHcODW8jrSHWw7Na0dC6qcA\nInstagram - BrickyIG\n\nIronside Computers | Click here to customize your own PC -  http://ironsidecomputers.com\n\nLF Gaming Chairs - https://lfgaming.com/shop/?ref=11\n\nP.O. Box\nBrickyOrchid8\n22365 El Toro Road.\nLake Forest, CA 92630\n#338' </summary>
    </meta>
    <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=JHWiUhYo5HY/</link>
    <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/JHWiUhYo5HY/sddefault.jpg</thumbnail>
</item>

<item>
    <title>Overwatch: PERFECT Mid-Air Rockets! - Pharah Advanced Guide</title>
    <meta>
        <summary>b"Destiny Channel! -\n https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCb4Jomiox07xosU843EYTiw\nMid air projectiles are the height of projectile aim difficulty in Overwatch Gameplay but being able to confidently take a Pharah mid air duel, or to land rockets on heroes that think they're safe flying through the sky can really elevate your impact on the rocket queen as well as other projectile heroes. In this video we specifically look at the Pharah vs. Pharah duel, as its one of the most direct and stable ways to deal with the aerial threat, however it also applies to all projectile aim as trapping a given hero in a predictable movement animation motion or frame is key to 'seeing the future' and hitting a projectile prediction. If you enjoyed the video please leave a like! \n\nYourDestiny https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCb4Jomiox07xosU843EYTiw\n\nSubscribe here - http://bit.ly/2aN1OuO\n\nWe are YOUR OVERWATCH:\nDestiny Channel: https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCb4Jomiox07xosU843EYTiw\nPatreon - https://www.patreon.com/YourOverwatch\nTwitter - https://twitter.com/youroverwatchyt\nTwitch - https://www.twitch.tv/youroverwatch \n\nDiscord Server:\nhttps://discordapp.com/invite/youroverwatch\n\nFREEDO's personal channel for Overwatch esports talk and more!\nhttps://www.youtube.com/user/xfreeedo" </summary>
    </meta>
    <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=-tJHy4aCCYc/</link>
    <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/-tJHy4aCCYc/sddefault.jpg</thumbnail>
</item>

<item>
    <title>Overwatch In Depth: Pharah Guide</title>
    <meta>
        <summary>b'Overwatch In Depth Torbjorn: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Ca8DmqlaKVU\nPharah is an extremely powerful hero in Overwatch that can be good on offense, defense, and nuetral point maps. She is really only limted by the map geometry and not as much by the gametype. This episode of Overwatch In Depth is a complete Pharah Guide that covers all of her stats and best strategies. I have a few personal tips and tricks mixed as well.\nMy Twitter: http://www.twitter.com/drift0r\n\nI capture console gameplay with The Elgato HD60 because it\'s the most professional device on the market for 1080p 60fps console capture.\nElgato website: http://bit.ly/LCO57Q \nAmazon Link: http://amzn.to/1y6Y759\n\nNEW DRIFT0R SHIRTS! http://www.coregamewear.com/drift0r\n\nI game exclusively on the Netduma R1 because it is best gaming router I have ever used.\nNetduma website: http://www.netduma.com/\nUse code "DRFT" for $10 off!\n\nI use ASTRO Headsets for all my gaming. They are very high quality gaming headsets. I also have a 5% off link with them. Clicking this link automatically gives you 5% off of everything ASTRO: http://bit.ly/1NIzdQi' </summary>
    </meta>
    <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=5UHccnqwnBs/</link>
    <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/5UHccnqwnBs/sddefault.jpg</thumbnail>
</item>

<item>
    <title>Pharah counters Widowmaker - Explanation & Guide || Valkia [Overwatch]</title>
    <meta>
        <summary>b"There have been plenty of people telling me that I should never play Pharah into Widowmaker, this video gives a guide on how to play Pharah into Widowmaker and proving that it is possible. Even a high skilled Widowmaker will have problems with this.\n\nThe step by step guide helps teach you how to deal with Widowmakers and how to think when playing vs them.\n\nHitscan Video: https://youtu.be/nkP1H0ggylo\n\n\n////////////////////////////////\n\n[NEW] Merchandise:\n\n   https://www.designbyhumans.com/shop/Valkia/\n\n\nSocial Links:\n\n   http://www.discord.gg/valkia\n   http://www.twitch.tv/valkia\n   http://www.twitter.com/officialvalkia\n   http://www.instagram.com/officialvalkia\n   http://www.facebook.com/valkiatv\n\nBusiness email valkiatv@gmail.com\n\n////////////////////////////////\n\nDon't forget to subscribe to my channel for Overwatch tips, tricks and tutorials. My guides are easy to follow and make it easy for learning. If you're wanting to improve your gameplay for Pharah, along with other heroes, make sure to follow the step-by-step quick guides to help you get better at heroes.\n\n////////////////////////////////\n\nSponsors:\n\nHyperX Headsets http://hyperx.gg/ValkiaHeadset\nHyperX Keyboards: http://hyperx.gg/ValkiaKeyboard\nHyperX Mousepads: http://hyperx.gg/ValkiaMousepad\n\nNoblechairs http://bit.ly/valkianoblechair\nOverclockers UK: http://www.overclockers.co.uk" </summary>
    </meta>
    <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=J7MeM4natr8/</link>
    <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/J7MeM4natr8/sddefault.jpg</thumbnail>
</item>

<item>
    <title>Grandmaster Pharah Guide: What makes Good & Bad maps [Overwatch]</title>
    <meta>
        <summary>b"[SUBSCRIBE FOR MORE OVERWATCH CONTENT]\n\nI've wanted to make a video covering points to why some maps are great for Pharah and some maps are not so great. These tips and tricks will explain in my own thoughts why some maps work better than others for Pharah. \n\nI should hopefully be doing individual map guides / flank routes for Pharah. These may prove obvious but i'm sure some people (newer players) can benefit from it.\n\n////////////////////////////////\n\nFollow Me:\nJoin Discord here: http://www.discord.gg/valkia\nhttp://www.twitch.tv/valkia\nhttp://www.twitter.com/markpurdy1337\nhttp://www.facebook.com/valkiatv\n\nBusiness email valkiatv@gmail.com\n\n\n////////////////////////////////\n\nDon't forget to subscribe to my channel for Overwatch tips, tricks and tutorials. My guides are easy to follow and make it easy for learning. If you're wanting to improve your gameplay for Pharah, Tracer, Widowmaker and other heroes, make sure to follow the step-by-step quick guides to help you get better at heroes. All new content from Overwatch will be posted by me, including skins, legendary skins from loot boxes, new heroes, settings including how to set a custom crosshair, change language and more.\n\nTips and Tricks playlist: https://www.youtube.com/playlist?list=PLCLdaElD3CIoR4VLK-L4h8rG_6wSt2qGx" </summary>
    </meta>
    <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=aQ7FQYttRaY/</link>
    <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/aQ7FQYttRaY/sddefault.jpg</thumbnail>
</item>

