<item>
    <title>Reaper Ability Overview | Overwatch</title>
    <meta>
        <summary>b"Death walks among you: http://bit.ly/MeetReaper\n\nSome speak of a black-robed terrorist known only as the Reaper. While his true identity and motives are a mystery, what is known is that where he appears, death follows. An extremely volatile mercenary, Reaper has been responsible for attacks across the globe, and some now believe he is hunting former Overwatch agents and systematically eliminating them. \n\nWith his twin Hellfire shotguns and ability to move unscathed through the shadows, Reaper is one of the world's deadliest threats.\n\nSign Up for Beta: http://bit.ly/JoinOverwatch \nLike Us on Facebook: http://www.facebook.com/playoverwatch \nFollow Us on Twitter: http://www.twitter.com/playoverwatch" </summary>
    </meta>
    <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=uK4WSF0rCcM/</link>
    <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/uK4WSF0rCcM/sddefault.jpg</thumbnail>
</item>

<item>
    <title>Overwatch - Reaper Guide - DEATH COMES! (Tips and Advice)</title>
    <meta>
        <summary>b"Reaper is a close range, durable and very mobile killing machine! Using his Hellfire shotguns at close range, Reaper can rip apart any target in seconds! He excels at tearing down tough targets such as tanks!\n\n PATREON CAMPAIGN! http://www.patreon.com/unitlost\n Steam Curator Page http://store.steampowered.com/curator/2666675/\n SUBSCRIBE! https://www.youtube.com/subscription_center?add_user=unitlosttube\n http://www.unitlost.com - Join our AWESOME community forums!\n T-shirts! http://unitlost.spreadshirt.co.uk/\n Sty's Twitter https://twitter.com/unitlostgaming\n Kiri's Twitter https://twitter.com/kirioth\n Live Stream http://www.twitch.tv/unitlost" </summary>
    </meta>
    <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=0UoljaChKuA/</link>
    <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/0UoljaChKuA/sddefault.jpg</thumbnail>
</item>

<item>
    <title>1 REAPER TIP for EVERY HERO ft. Spirit</title>
    <meta>
        <summary>b"Although Reaper isn't doing the greatest in the Brigitte meta, here is 1 REAPER TIP vs EVERY HERO to help you get started with SPIRIT from Grizzlys Esports. \n\nSpirit Socials:\n- https://www.twitch.tv/spiritow\n- https://www.youtube.com/montrealesports\n\n\n\n KARQ SOCIALS:\n\nTwitch  https://twitch.tv/KarQ \nMerch  https://karqgames.com\nDiscord  https://discord.gg/karq\nTwitter  https://twitter.com/KarQGames\nInstagram  http://instagram.com/KarQGames\nFacebook  https://www.facebook.com/KarQGames/\n\n- Thank you Abort3d & Steak8oz for helping me film!\n\n\n Music Used:\n\n Otis McDonald - Scarlet Fire https://youtu.be/8yOskhDn468\n GetSix - Orion https://soundcloud.com/getsixofficial" </summary>
    </meta>
    <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=tBYXmr7P2Ik/</link>
    <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/tBYXmr7P2Ik/sddefault.jpg</thumbnail>
</item>

<item>
    <title>Overwatch: High Impact Reaper Flank Tactics - Advanced Guide</title>
    <meta>
        <summary>b"Edgelords UNITE! Reaper is seemingly a basic hero, but executing his plays in order to get impactful value takes a bit of finesse, talon trickery if-you-will. We've made more full reaper guides in the past on how to Lurk and Pounce targets which are linked below as well as on a clickable card on-screen, but today we slow down into the minutia of both the mechanics and psychology of executing a play, which requires you to both know how to set it up as well as see it through with confidence to result in high impact reaper flanks. This style of advanced guide is a little different from what we've done in the past and updates our previous guides in a way that unlocks those tactics mentioned earlier if you struggled with them. Let us know your thoughts on the format and we can continue with this almost coach-style to them to isolate typical player problems with 'the plays' Overwatch heroes make. \n\nMore Reaper videos! \nhttps://www.youtube.com/channel/UCEzOHrh9snmHJSGu9wmOvsw/search?query=reaper?&ab_channel=YourOverwatch\n\nSubscribe here - http://bit.ly/2aN1OuO\n\nRazer makes the best equipment, check out here! http://rzr.to/lnvvm\n\nWe are YOUR OVERWATCH:\nDestiny Channel: https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCb4Jomiox07xosU843EYTiw\nPatreon - https://www.patreon.com/YourOverwatch\nTwitter - https://twitter.com/youroverwatchyt\nTwitch - https://www.twitch.tv/youroverwatch \n\nDiscord Server:\nhttps://discordapp.com/invite/youroverwatch\n\nFREEDO's personal channel for Overwatch esports talk and more!\nhttps://www.youtube.com/user/xfreeedo" </summary>
    </meta>
    <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=UzZXSvTliMg/</link>
    <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/UzZXSvTliMg/sddefault.jpg</thumbnail>
</item>

<item>
    <title>Overwatch PRO Reaper Guide: the GIGA-FLANK</title>
    <meta>
        <summary>b' Join NOW! https://ow.gameleap.com/ - Learn from Top 500 Pros and carry your games!\n\nThis Overwatch guide features pro coach, Satellites, CRUSHING a Top 500 Reaper game on Anubis. He will guide you through his Reaper plays step-by-step so you can carry your games too!\n\nThanks for watching. If you have any questions or want to reach us, please send an email at support@game-leap.com and we will get back to you shortly.' </summary>
    </meta>
    <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=j0yEIhyakXU/</link>
    <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/j0yEIhyakXU/sddefault.jpg</thumbnail>
</item>

<item>
    <title>Overwatch: NEW Reaper Playstyle! - Advanced Guide</title>
    <meta>
        <summary>b"Overwatch's reaper has seen a few buffs recently which has resulted in him being a great pick against many comps. In this advanced guide we break down his new playstyle as a brawler and where you can still use his old lurk and pounce play style. Let us know what you think and be sure to drop a Like & Subscribe if you enjoyed!\nSubscribe here - http://bit.ly/2aN1OuO\n\nWe are YOUR OVERWATCH:\nDestiny Channel: https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCb4Jomiox07xosU843EYTiw\nPatreon - https://www.patreon.com/YourOverwatch\nTwitter - https://twitter.com/youroverwatchyt\nTwitch - https://www.twitch.tv/youroverwatch \n\nDiscord Server:\nhttps://discordapp.com/invite/youroverwatch\n\nFREEDO's personal channel for Overwatch esports talk and more!\nhttps://www.youtube.com/user/xfreeedo" </summary>
    </meta>
    <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Hhbc0CJLh6Y/</link>
    <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/Hhbc0CJLh6Y/sddefault.jpg</thumbnail>
</item>

<item>
    <title>SPIRIT - GRANDMASTER REAPER GAMEPLAY TIPS | How To Improve As Reaper Guide - Overwatch Season 8</title>
    <meta>
        <summary>b"Today we are back again trying a top 500 tip Reaper video because I think its fun and people just love Reaper it seems. Today we are talking about how the grandmaster Reaper player can carry his competitive games in season 8 overwatch competitive ranked mode guide for overwatch season 8 placement matches and overwatch season 8 changes. Going over some Reaper season 8 tips and guide or whatever you want to call it. I hope that these tips can help to have you guys learn how to improve as Reaper and hope this works as a mini Reaper guide tip trick thing for all that want to improve as her. Anyways, thanks! *Reaper in the new season competitive ranked 8 guide tips.*\n\n\n\n\nMore GM Gameplay Tip Videos Here! : https://www.youtube.com/playlist?list=PLefC4eOMnbRF5Xm7uCjfU73bh0ybup9Df\n\n\n\nGameplay: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=GztX_uD510A\nThumbnail:\n-----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------\n\n-Credits:\nSpirit\nhttps://twitter.com/spiritow_\nhttps://twitch.tv/spiritow\nhttps://discord.gg/rwqn3q3\n\n======================================================================\n\nTIPS I WROTE DOWN FROM THE VIDEO:\n-his team is runnning dive comp, take high ground to beat the enemy shields\n-reaper can play as a sheild breaker or a burst flanker, look at your teamcomps and theirs to decide which\n-its hard for reaper to take out a lot of dps by himself, but with a support or tank you can 2v2 them easily\n-he focuses junk first as he has little peel and no self heal\n-spirit likes to go on high ground but will fall back down often\n-when rat tires he instantly tries to shoot it, and wraith forms at the last second\n-spirit is using high ground a lot more than he used to, if he knows the enemies arent on it, he takes it\n-when you see a mccree, try to shoot him once and then wraith form, wastes his flashbang and you can escape\n-on this last teamfight he focuses reinhardt first to get life steal and stay alive\n\n-reaper can work ok on defense with one healer because of self heal, easier to do with aan orisa or rein tho\n-the only way you can kill widow is to flank her without her noticing you, if she keeps finding you, play frontline\n-your hitbox is huge and many heroes CAN EASILY one shot you, sometimes you need to take thatrisk\n-ask in voice chat to be nano boosted, and try to get the boost as you wraith form in\n-try to always get a shot off on somebody before you ult to guarentee a kill\n-against most heroes at mid range just shoot their mid bodies,\n-if a tank is looking away from you, also shoot their midb bodies to hit the most pellets\n-if you camp high ground you can stop enemy dva or winston from taking it, thats better than your benefit\n-try to not run at the enemies through open ground, if there is a side route to getting somewhere, go there\n-try to not waste your ult vs a zen ult, to do this bodyshot somebody and then ult, you will at least get that kill\n-reaper is one of the best heroes to nano without ult, try to take out the tanks with headshots first here\n\n\n\n======================================================================\n\n\n\n\n\nHow GRANDMASTER Players DESTORY with Reaper - Overwatch Top 500 PRO Tricks Overwatch - 20 TricksReaper Grandmasters ABUSE That You Don't! Some tips and tricks to master Reaper! Overwatch - 8 OP Tips and Tricks Grandmaster Players use every game! Reaper overwatch, Reaper guide top 500 tips and tricks  Reaper master gameplay, how Reaper is played, SPIRITgameplay Reaper overwatch competitive esports vod grandmaster Reaper tricks grandmaster top 500 Reaper, overwatch top 800 Reaper esports vod Reaper esports gameplay, grandmaster Reaper tricks top 500 tricks tips, how to play Reaper, Reaper season 8, overwatch competitive season 8 Reaper, Reaper season 8 offense, Reaper season 8 defense, overwatch season 8 Reaper guide       overwatch,Reaper tricks,Tricks Reaper Grandmasters ABUSE That You Don't,Tricks Reaper Grandmasters ABUSE That You Don't overwatch,overwatch Tricks Reaper Grandmasters ABUSE That You Don't,tricks grandmasters abuse that you dont,overwatch tricks grandmasters abuse that you dont,grandmaster tricks overwatch,Reaper grandmaster,Reaper top 500 trick,How GRANDMASTER Players DESTROY with Reaper,Reaper season 8 competitive,Reaper vod,grandmaster, Reaper CUSTA, SPIRITReaper, best Reaper, strongest Reaper, best Reaper player, overwatch CUSTA\n\n\n\nTitle:GRANDMASTER Reaper GAMEPLAY TIPS | How To Improve As Reaper Guide - Overwatch Season 8 Competitive Tricks" </summary>
    </meta>
    <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=h-fxs3GkVDI/</link>
    <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/h-fxs3GkVDI/sddefault.jpg</thumbnail>
</item>

<item>
    <title>Let's Git Gud | Reaper Gameplay - Guide & Tips</title>
    <meta>
        <summary>b"A review of Reaper gameplay with tips and tricks\nOur Discord server: https://discord.gg/UJzwMS4\nOther VoD Reviews:\nhttps://www.youtube.com/playlist?list=PLRxsC0vIWul2iy4rDTt0R-zg7TD5plHt2\nSubmit your own VoD for review: \ntrilby1227@gmail.com\nSupport me on Patreon:\nhttps://www.patreon.com/user?u=5667329\nMy Let's Play Channel:\nhttps://www.youtube.com/channel/UCdPBXrNmPEqTgsZCrsme81g" </summary>
    </meta>
    <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=5TrbYszwEJQ/</link>
    <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/5TrbYszwEJQ/sddefault.jpg</thumbnail>
</item>

<item>
    <title>Overwatch: How to Be a Pro Reaper - Lurk & Pounce Advanced Guide</title>
    <meta>
        <summary>b'HarryHook is the one pro right now that utilizes Reaper. At MLG Vegas, Harryhook used Reaper in a Lurk and Pounce playstyle to quickly take duels against enemy DPS\' , win the duel and snowball teamfights from there. The key to utilizing an "on-meta" hero like this, is to set up the hero by avoiding their counters and finding their value fast. In this way, Reaper doesn\'t look off-meta at all, just simply a way to dish out burst damage, if you hit the close range shots putting all the spread into the hitbox. -F\n\nSubscribe here: https://www.youtube.com/c/youroverwatch?sub_confirmation=1\n\nWe are YOUR OVERWATCH:\nTwitch - https://www.twitch.tv/youroverwatch \nTwitter - https://twitter.com/youroverwatchyt\nSubscribe - http://bit.ly/2aN1OuO\n\nDiscord Server:\nhttps://discordapp.com/invite/FadSx3u\n\nFREEDO\'s personal channel for Overwatch esports talk and more!\nhttps://www.youtube.com/user/xfreeedo' </summary>
    </meta>
    <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=-3fpji4xkus/</link>
    <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/-3fpji4xkus/sddefault.jpg</thumbnail>
</item>

<item>
    <title>Overwatch Coaching - NEW Reaper - SILVER 1650 SR - [OverAnalyzed]</title>
    <meta>
        <summary>b'Overwatch Reaper coaching! Welcome to OverAnalyzed! In this series, we as a community help our fellow players with tips and advice on how to become better players!\n\n UNIT LOST STORE! http://bit.ly/ulstore\n HyperX - CHECK THEM OUT! http://bit.ly/UnitLostFPS [AD]\n Discord JOIN NOW! http://discord.gg/unitlost  \n PATREON CAMPAIGN! http://www.patreon.com/unitlost\n Twitter https://twitter.com/unitlostgaming\n Live Stream http://www.twitch.tv/unitlost\n http://www.unitlost.com - Join our AWESOME community forums!\n\nSystem Specs\n\nIntel i7 6900K overclocked @ 4.6Ghz\nWater Loop Coolant: Mayhem Aurora Blue\nAdditional Static Pressure Fan: Corsair SP120 LED Blue High Static Pressure 120mm Fan\nStatic Pressure Fans: Corsair SP120 LED Blue High Static Pressure 120mm Fan - Twin Pack\n32GB Corsair 3000mhz Vengeance LPX DDR4 (4x8GB) \n2 x NVIDIA GeForce GTX 1080 Strix 8GB \nAsus ROG STRIX Intel X99 RGB LED GAMING ATX Motherboard\nWindows 10 Home (64-bit)\nIntel 400GB 750 PCIe SSD\n4TB S-ATAIII 6.0Gb/s \n4TB S-ATAIII 6.0Gb/s \nBlue Camo Vinyl\nCorsair Carbide 600C Windowed\nCase Fans: Corsair AF120 LED Blue Quiet Edition High Airflow 120mm Fan - Twin Pack\nAdditional Case Fan: Corsair AF120 LED Blue Quiet Edition High Airflow 120mm Fan\nBraided Cables: PSU Braided Extension Cable set Black\nPSU: 850W Corsair RMX Fully Modular' </summary>
    </meta>
    <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=8ru6gK3rY_0/</link>
    <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/8ru6gK3rY_0/sddefault.jpg</thumbnail>
</item>

<item>
    <title>Overwatch: You Should FEAR REAPER - Advanced Guide</title>
    <meta>
        <summary>b"Edgelords unite! Reaper has an odd reputation for how mechanically easy he is for how quickly devastating he can be to Overwatch Gameplay. In this video, FREEDO dismantles common Reaper misconceptions and shows what opportunities you should be looking for as Reaper to find great success. Reaper can find himself controlling valuable real estate on the map and being very punishing while doing it, as within his effective range, he is drastically favored in most duels. FEAR the REAPER!\n\nProduction Music courtesy of Epidemic Sound: http://www.epidemicsound.com\n\nCheck out these other Reaper videos! \n\nPro Reaper Harryhook https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=-3fpji4xkus&ab_channel=YourOverwatch\n\nReaper is bad against tanks? https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=SdtGYhxa4Zo&ab_channel=YourOverwatch\n\nMore Reaper Videos! https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCEzOHrh9snmHJSGu9wmOvsw/search?query=reaper?&ab_channel=YourOverwatch\n\n\n\nSubscribe here: https://www.youtube.com/c/youroverwatch?sub_confirmation=1\n\nWe are YOUR OVERWATCH:\nTwitch - https://www.twitch.tv/youroverwatch \nTwitter - https://twitter.com/youroverwatchyt\nSubscribe - http://bit.ly/2aN1OuO\n\nDiscord Server:\nhttps://discordapp.com/invite/youroverwatch\n\nFREEDO's personal channel for Overwatch esports talk and more!\nhttps://www.youtube.com/user/xfreeedo" </summary>
    </meta>
    <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=QJYNK-yeoPk/</link>
    <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/QJYNK-yeoPk/sddefault.jpg</thumbnail>
</item>

<item>
    <title>Overwatch Reaper Guide - FASTEST Start Of Match Flanks | Part 1</title>
    <meta>
        <summary>b"Overwatch Reaper Guide - FASTEST Start Of Match Flanks \nThis is a video showing some of my favorite spots to use reapers shadow step ability on hard capture points at the start of games. These spots are designed to get fast kills at the beginning of rounds to help your team break enemy defenses as fast as possible.\n\nSince Overwatch was released I've always loved Reapers ability to output insane amounts of damage. When you add Reapers damage with his flanking capacity you can really become a problem for the enemy team. If you can learn how to utilize this hero's toolkit you may find it a bit easier to start ranking up in competitive games. \n\nCurrent 2 battletags #Zowlufin #Randomized / Peak - Master 3658\n\nI hope you found some of this information helpful, please leave a like and let me know in the comments which 2 maps you would like to see next.\n\nDiscord Community Server: https://discord.gg/SMfbEyA\n\nLike My Content? Subscribe for More!\nhttps://goo.gl/M92cN6" </summary>
    </meta>
    <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=pbl6TRibyS4/</link>
    <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/pbl6TRibyS4/sddefault.jpg</thumbnail>
</item>

<item>
    <title>The ULTIMATE Reaper Guide to Shadowsteps, Flanks & Death Blossom Locations Pt. 1 ► Overwatch</title>
    <meta>
        <summary>b"Reaper is definitely one of those heroes you can carry with if you have great flanking potential and aim. But please bare in mind that all of these Shadow-Step locations are situational and depend on the enemy teams positioning in each and every game!\nTemple of Anubis - 0:23\nKing's Row - 3:07\nHanamura - 6:03\nWatchpoint Gibraltar - 8:14\nNumbani - 9:10\nVolskaya Industries - 10:06\nEichenwalde - 11:11\n Subscribe - https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCwHH... \n\n Twitter - https://twitter.com/GhostGamingG  Facebook - https://www.facebook.com/pages/Ghost-...\n\n Twitch - http://www.twitch.tv/ghostgaminggg  BF4 Platoon - http://battlelog.battlefield.com/bf4/..." </summary>
    </meta>
    <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=-efdihNC4bM/</link>
    <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/-efdihNC4bM/sddefault.jpg</thumbnail>
</item>

<item>
    <title>Overwatch Advanced Reaper Guide - Kill Everything</title>
    <meta>
        <summary>b'Reaper is considered one of the easier heroes in overwatch but in this advanced guide ill be giving tips on how to kill everything efficiently and get the most out of this hero!\nSubscribe here: https://www.youtube.com/c/youroverwatch?sub_confirmation=1\n\nWe are YOUR OVERWATCH:\nTwitch - https://www.twitch.tv/youroverwatch \nTwitter - https://twitter.com/youroverwatchyt\nSubscribe - http://bit.ly/2aN1OuO' </summary>
    </meta>
    <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=n8CaYF-Gmis/</link>
    <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/n8CaYF-Gmis/sddefault.jpg</thumbnail>
</item>

<item>
    <title>Let's Git Gud | Reaper Gameplay - Guide & Tips</title>
    <meta>
        <summary>b"A review of Reaper gameplay with tips and tricks\nOur Discord server: https://discord.gg/UJzwMS4\nOther VoD Reviews:\nhttps://www.youtube.com/playlist?list=PLRxsC0vIWul2iy4rDTt0R-zg7TD5plHt2\nSubmit your own VoD for review: \ntrilby1227@gmail.com\nSupport me on Patreon:\nhttps://www.patreon.com/user?u=5667329\nMy Let's Play Channel:\nhttps://www.youtube.com/channel/UCdPBXrNmPEqTgsZCrsme81g" </summary>
    </meta>
    <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Zp1uL_ypRR8/</link>
    <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/Zp1uL_ypRR8/sddefault.jpg</thumbnail>
</item>

<item>
    <title>Beginner's Guide to Using Reaper (Updated)</title>
    <meta>
        <summary>b'This is an updated Beginner\'s Guide to using Reaper as a DAW (digital audio workstation) to record, edit, and export audio files.  I made one a few years ago, but wanted to update it with some more basic information for an absolute beginner.\n\nMore Reaper guides:\n\nHow to Install VST Plugins - https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=CByHPXk3Flw\n\nHow to Use EQ - https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=hGP7neSQORY\n\nDouble Tracking - https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=VqN6g1fSkQU\n\nUsing Drum Samples - https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=z4MSd7cYb2o\n\nWorkflow Tips - https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=CsQeBti5xkU\n\nMixing Tutorial - https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=IHaN543FJsE\n\n\n\nHit "Subscribe" for more videos!\n\nhttp://www.youtube.com/subscription_center?add_user=kleydj13' </summary>
    </meta>
    <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=0AXRerY1mf4/</link>
    <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/0AXRerY1mf4/sddefault.jpg</thumbnail>
</item>

<item>
    <title>Reaper - Overwatch Hero Guide</title>
    <meta>
        <summary>b"Are you a hate filled creature? Do you like dark clothes & muttering under your breath? Then join Chris & Erick as they give you their beginner's tips for playing as Reaper in Overwatch.\n\nMore from GameSpot's Overwatch Hero Guide:\nhttps://www.youtube.com/playlist?list=PLpg6WLs8kxGOwCOjDZVbCMuUCoLPPLW0V\n\nFollow Overwatch at GameSpot.com!\nhttp://www.gamespot.com/overwatch/\nOfficial Site - http://us.battle.net/overwatch/\n\nCheck out our review!\nWatch - https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=JF2nEfY_Thg\nRead - http://www.gamespot.com/reviews/overwatch-review/1900-6416439/\n\nSubscribe to us on YouTube Gaming!\nhttp://gaming.youtube.com/gamespot\n\nVisit all of our channels:\nFeatures & Reviews - http://www.youtube.com/GameSpot\nGameplay & Guides - http://www.youtube.com/GameSpotGameplay\nTrailers - http://www.youtube.com/GameSpotTrailers\nMobile Gaming - http://www.youtube.com/GameSpotMobile\n\nLike  - http://www.facebook.com/GameSpot\nFollow - http://www.twitter.com/GameSpot\n\nhttp://www.gamespot.com" </summary>
    </meta>
    <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=cxA4894HtEg/</link>
    <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/cxA4894HtEg/sddefault.jpg</thumbnail>
</item>

<item>
    <title>Quickie w/ Reaper - Top 5 Quick Tips | Overwatch Beginner’s Guide</title>
    <meta>
        <summary>b'Here are 5 quick Reaper tips & tricks. I go over his 3 side roles (Flanker, Tank Buster, & Peeler), how to flank, how to peel, specific synergies, and when to pick him based on team comps and maps.\n\nI was curious about why Reaper worked in some games while in others he was weak. This had me thinking about the different conditions that had to be met to make him a solid hero choice. So I played a bunch of games to see what worked and what didnt and put almost everything I learned about Reaper in this video.\n\nLike, sub, & hit the notification bell for more gaming content.\n------------------------------------------------------------------------------------\n Subscribe: http://bit.ly/1Tnap2Q\n\n Twitter: https://twitter.com/NiccoG6\n\n Facebook: https://www.facebook.com/NiccoG6\n------------------------------------------------------------------------------------\nSong: LoFi Chillhop Hip-Hop Instrumental Rap Beat | Ryan Little - Day 15 \n(https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=3roOzW6nJxQ)\nSoundCloud: https://soundcloud.com/iamryanlittle\nTwitter: https://twitter.com/iamryanlittle' </summary>
    </meta>
    <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=MVfok79Tdd8/</link>
    <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/MVfok79Tdd8/sddefault.jpg</thumbnail>
</item>

<item>
    <title>Overwatch Reaper Guide | How to Play REAPER (In-Depth Stats, Tips, and Match Ups) Reaper Gameplay</title>
    <meta>
        <summary>b"Today in Overwatch, I'll be showing you how to play Reaper with some tips and tricks on how to do better with this hero. This guide will go pretty in depth as far as numbers go, but I won't be surprised if the numbers get changed as Overwatch ages so I'll be sure to catalog the changes down here in the description.\n\nAdditional tips:\n\nPapiDimmi 1 hour ago\nThis is a fantastic video. Youve earned yourself a new subscriber, my man. Well, I knew all of this information, but I still found your gameplay enjoyable (especially when you camped the Teleporter), as well as your commentary.\n\nHowever, you forgot to mention that you move faster than normally in Wraith Form, which can be useful to use to get back into battle after you respawn after your death. You can also get quickly back into bettle using Shadow Step; however, thats quite self-explanatory.\n\nYou also did not mention that using your melee attack right after reloading shortens the reload time to one second, which can be useful to reload faster mid-battle.\n\nAlso, you didnt mention that you can jump during the use of Death Blossom, and that you can collect health packs (and Souls) during the use of Wraith Form.\n\n\nSpecial thanks goes out to MOARNial for the Overwatch Victory Theme REMIX, check it out here:\nhttps://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ciA-SxFhIMQ\n\ntwitter: @moarnial\n\n*Channel Banner and Logo made by Tomographic (HIT HIM UP IF YOU WANT AWESOME ARTWORK DONE!)\nhttps://twitter.com/ItsTomographic\nhttps://www.youtube.com/channel/UCOt5hVyS2-nbcJ3_FP41Ajg" </summary>
    </meta>
    <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=hi9VOz_m1us/</link>
    <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/hi9VOz_m1us/sddefault.jpg</thumbnail>
</item>

<item>
    <title>Overwatch Reaper Guide - FASTEST Start Of Match Flanks | Part 2</title>
    <meta>
        <summary>b'Overwatch Reaper Guide - FASTEST Start Of Match Flanks | Part 2.\nThis is my second video showing some of my favorite spots to use reapers shadow step ability on hard capture points at the start of a match. These small map tricks are designed to get fast kills at the beginning of rounds to help your team break enemy defenses as fast as possible.\n\nI plan to eventually cover all of the different choke point heavy maps but In this video, we went over Hollywood and Temple Of Anubis. I also show during the second half that it is not uncommon to pick up first blood within 13 sec of the round starting. So I do hope this little Overwatch Reaper guide helps someone out there pick up a few extra wins along the way! \n\nI hope you find some of this information helpful, please leave a like and let me know in the comments what you would like to see next.\n\nLike My Content? Subscribe for More!\nhttps://goo.gl/M92cN6 \n\nDiscord Community Channel: https://discord.gg/SMfbEyA\n\nCurrent 2 battletags #Zowlufin #Randomized / Peak - Master 3658' </summary>
    </meta>
    <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Gfejyfajd54/</link>
    <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/Gfejyfajd54/sddefault.jpg</thumbnail>
</item>

<item>
    <title>Overwatch Reaper Guide - FASTEST Start Of Match Flanks | Part 3</title>
    <meta>
        <summary>b"Overwatch Reaper Guide - FASTEST Start Of Match Flanks | Part 3 of the ongoing series where I show my favorite spots to use reapers shadow step ability at the start of a match. These flanks help me to pick up some really fast kills and secure some of the harder capture points in overwatch. I hope they can work the same for you. \n\nThis video is a bit different from the others in this series. I wouldn't say Horizon Lunar Colony is necessarily a hard capture point on attack, but I show how effective one of these flanks can be here. Junkertown, on the other hand, can be quite tricky if the enemy team stops your first push, so I'm happy to share the way I like to use reaper on both maps. \n\nI hope you find some of this information helpful, please leave a like and let me know in the comments what you would like to see next.\nThe plan is to at least have 2-3 more videos in this reaper fast flanks series, but while I'm gathering clips I'll also be working on some new projects within overwatch and out in other games. \n\nI'm super happy with the feedback that I've received so far in these reaper videos, so if your reading this thank you for stopping by! =D\n\nFor future reference:  when I'm playing competitively in any game I will always keep pretty positive and rage free. Worst case with leavers or when I feel that I could have done better, I may get frustrated and stop for the day. When I'm not playing competitive games then I'm probably off somewhere being a subtle troll in some other multiplayer game. It's a passion and it brings real joy to my life lol\n\nLike My Content? Subscribe for More!\nhttps://goo.gl/M92cN6 \n\nIf you want to give me any suggestion on new video ideas, join the discord and let me know. I'd love to also bring a community of gamers together that like to share or talk about music/art/anime/games/randomness\n\nDiscord Community Channel: https://discord.gg/SMfbEyA\n\nCurrent 2 battletags #Zowlufin #Randomized / Peak - Master 3658" </summary>
    </meta>
    <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=2qnOsXlLIr8/</link>
    <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/2qnOsXlLIr8/sddefault.jpg</thumbnail>
</item>

