################################################################################
  <thumbnail>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PiDiaries/wow/master/sprays/rein.png</thumbnail>
  <fanart>https://d1u1mce87gyfbn.cloudfront.net/media/screenshot/reinhardt-screenshot-003.jpg</fanart>
  <summary>Clad in powered armor and swinging his hammer, Reinhardt leads a rocket-propelled charge across the battleground and defends his squadmates with a massive energy barrier.
  Reinhardt Wilhelm styles himself as a champion of a bygone age, who lives by the knightly codes of valor, justice, and courage.

Over thirty years ago, Overwatch was founded to counter the threat of the robot uprisings around the world. Reinhardt, a highly decorated German soldier, was inducted as part of the original Overwatch strike team that put an end to the Omnic Crisis. After the conflict's resolution, Overwatch grew into a global institution, keeping the peace in a war-torn world. Reinhardt proved himself to be one of its most stalwart champions.

Reinhardt's unique ethics and larger-than-life persona earned the admiration of his peers and superiors alike. Never afraid to speak his mind, he was Overwatch's most vocal supporter and, when necessary, its harshest critic, providing a constant reminder that Overwatch was meant to be a force for good.

Having served into his late fifties, Reinhardt was faced with mandatory retirement from combat operations. Despondent about being removed from active duty, Reinhardt feared that his days of purpose and glory had ended. As times grew darker and Overwatch came under suspicion of corruption and sedition, Reinhardt could only watch as the cause he had dedicated his life to defending surrendered in disgrace.

Though Overwatch was eventually disbanded, Reinhardt was not content to sit idly by while the world fell to disorder. Once again donning his Crusader armor, he has vowed to fight for justice across Europe like a knight of old, defending the innocent and winning hearts and minds with the promise of better days to come.
</summary>

################################################################################
<item>
  <title>Reinhardt Ability Overview</title>
  <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch/zLFbm6YckoU</link>
  <thumbnail>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PiDiaries/wow/master/sprays/rein.png</thumbnail>
  <fanart>https://d1u1mce87gyfbn.cloudfront.net/media/screenshot/reinhardt-screenshot-003.jpg</fanart>
  <summary>One of Overwatch’s first and finest agents, Reinhardt Wilhelm styles himself as a champion of a bygone age. Though Overwatch was eventually disbanded, Reinhardt was not content to sit idly by while the world fell to disorder. Donning his Crusader siege armor, he has vowed to fight for justice like a knight of old, defending the innocent and winning hearts and minds with the promise of better days to come.

With his powerful hammer, Reinhardt leads rocket-propelled charges across the battlefield. He wades into the fray, crushing enemies into walls, bringing combatants to their knees, and defending his allies with a massive energy shield.</summary>
</item>


<item>
  <title>Overwatch - Reinhardt Guide - HAMMER DOWN! (Tips and Advice)</title>
  <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch/ACGy_xt0htI</link>
  <thumbnail>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PiDiaries/wow/master/sprays/rein.png</thumbnail>
  <fanart>https://d1u1mce87gyfbn.cloudfront.net/media/screenshot/reinhardt-screenshot-003.jpg</fanart>
  <summary>Reinhardt is an ultra durable, high health and armour, team protection tank!. He excels at protecting his team with his barrier shield! In this guide video I give advice and tips on how best to use Reinhardt.
  </summary>
</item>


<item>
  <title>REINHARDT GRANDMASTER GUIDE (20 TIPS)</title>
  <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch/0JJ76MUXmew</link>
  <thumbnail>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PiDiaries/wow/master/sprays/rein.png</thumbnail>
  <fanart>https://d1u1mce87gyfbn.cloudfront.net/media/screenshot/reinhardt-screenshot-003.jpg</fanart>
  <summary></summary>
</item>
