
################################################################################
  <thumbnail>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PiDiaries/wow/master/sprays/hog.png</thumbnail>
<fanart>https://d1u1mce87gyfbn.cloudfront.net/media/screenshot/roadhog-screenshot-004.jpg</fanart>
  <summary>Roadhog uses his signature Chain Hook to pull his enemies close before shredding them with blasts from his Scrap Gun. He’s hardy enough to withstand tremendous damage, and can recover his health with a short breather.
   Roadhog is a ruthless killer with a well-earned reputation for cruelty and wanton destruction.

After the Omnic Crisis, government officials gifted the Australian omnium and the surrounding area to the omnics that had nearly destroyed their country, hoping to establish a long-term peace accord. This arrangement permanently displaced Mako Rutledge and a large number of the Outback's residents, a scattered collection of survivalists, solar farmers, and people who just wanted to be left alone.

Furious over the loss of their homes, Mako and others turned to violent rebellion. They formed the Australian Liberation Front and struck against the omnium and its robot population to take back the lands that had been stolen. Events continued to escalate until the rebels sabotaged the omnium's fusion core, resulting in an explosion that destroyed the facility, irradiated the region, and littered the Outback with twisted metal and wreckage for kilometers around.

Mako watched as his home became an apocalyptic wasteland, and he was forever changed.

Adapting to his environment, he donned a mask and took to the broken highways of the Outback on his ramshackle chopper. Little by little, his humanity was forgotten. The last vestiges of Mako faded away and the ruthless killer Roadhog was born.
</summary>

################################################################################
<item>
  <title>Introducing Roadhog and Junkrat</title>
  <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch/DqhiLbRXGUQ</link>
  <thumbnail></thumbnail>
  <summary>Meet Roadhog and Junkrat—two criminals on a spree of mayhem and destruction around the world.</summary>
</item>
<item>
  <title>A Moment in Crime Special Report: "The Junkers"</title>
  <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch/l5kTATxt7bE</link>
  <thumbnail></thumbnail>
  <summary>Their spree of mayhem and chaos has caused untold millions in property damage around the world. But who are these two deranged Junkers, and what is behind their destructive rampage? Find out in this special episode of A Moment in Crime!  </summary>
</item>
<item>
  <title>Roadhog Ability Overview</title>
  <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch/5URzijwRPfk</link>
  <thumbnail></thumbnail>
  <summary>After taking part in a violent anti-omnic rebellion that led to nuclear disaster, the man once known as Mako Rutledge watched the Australian Outback become a wasteland. Adapting to his new environment, he donned a mask and took to the broken highways on his ramshackle chopper—and the ruthless killer known as Roadhog was born. 

Roadhog uses his signature Chain Hook to pull his enemies close before shredding them with a blast from his Scrap Gun. He can heal himself by stopping to Take a Breather, and when his rage takes hold, he goes Whole Hog—overloading his Scrap Gun and knocking back foes with a stream of devastating shrapnel.</summary>
</item>

<item>
  <title>Overwatch - Roadhog Guide - THE BOSS HOG! (Tips and Advice)</title>
  <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch/HnCWSk92V50</link>
  <thumbnail></thumbnail>
  <summary>Roadhog is the ultimate brawler tank. A man (hog) mountain specifcally designed to keep in the fight! Between Roadhog’s hook, self heal and shotgun attacks he’s a close range brawler tank elite!
  </summary>
</item>
