
########################################################################################################
  <thumbnail>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PiDiaries/wow/master/sprays/sombra.png</thumbnail>
<fanart>https://d1u1mce87gyfbn.cloudfront.net/media/screenshot/sombra-screenshot-006-6de9884047e0fa523c234ce979e9418a573ea758ab7166d58c90e6118a3a849b6dab2a0ead43a7b4720e657c502e1fe94fc1913ff5a2be7df0b01d8b36ec9c3b.jpg</fanart>
  <summary>Stealth and debilitating attacks make Sombra a powerful infiltrator. Her hacking can disrupt her enemies, ensuring they're easier to take out, while her EMP provides the upper hand against multiple foes at once. Sombra’s ability to Translocate and camouflage herself makes her a hard target to pin down.
  
  One of the world's most notorious hackers, Sombra uses information to manipulate those in power.

Long before she took up the alias "Sombra," ░░░░░░ was among the thousands of children who were left orphaned in the aftermath of the Omnic Crisis. With much of her country's infrastructure destroyed, she survived by utilizing her natural gifts with hacking and computers.

After ░░░░░░ was taken in by Mexico's Los Muertos gang, she aided it in its self-styled revolution against the government. Los Muertos believed that the rebuilding of Mexico had primarily benefited the rich and the influential, leaving behind those who were most in need of assistance.

Following her many conquests, ░░░░░░ was supremely confident in her skills, but she was caught unprepared when she stumbled into the web of a global conspiracy—one that had also noticed her. With her security irreparably compromised, ░░░░░░ was forced to delete all traces of her identity and went into hiding.

She later reemerged as Sombra, upgraded and determined to find out the truth behind the conspiracy she had uncovered. Sombra launched an even more audacious string of hacks, and her exploits earned her no shortage of admirers, including Talon. She joined the organization's ranks and is believed to have contributed to its massive cyberattacks against corporations with strong ties to their governments. These efforts incited a popular revolution in Mexico against LumériCo and breached the security of Volskaya Industries, the manufacturing arm of Russia's anti-omnic defense.

Now, with Talon's extensive resources to call upon, Sombra can focus on her true goal: to unravel the conspiracy and use the power behind it to her own ends.</summary>
#########################################################################################################

<item>
  <title>Overwatch | Master Sombra ft CodeyNiku (World #1 Sombra) - Tips and Advice (Guide)</title>
  <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch/mO214WfPpUs</link>
  <thumbnail></thumbnail>
  <summary>Sombra is a tricky hero to master. We grabbed our top 500 Sombra friend Codeyniku to talk about Sombra and provide some tips / advice. Enjoy!
  </summary>
</item>

<item>
  <title>Overwatch Coaching - NEW Sombra! WTF ARE YOU DOING! [OverAnalyzed]</title>
  <link>https://youtube.com/watch/iNHgUdi0kLc</link>
  <summary>Overwatch NEW Sombra coaching! JOIN THE UNIT LOST DISCORD http://discord.gg/unitlost
Overwatch Sombra coaching! Season 9 Sombra tips and advice! Welcome to OverAnalyzed! In this series, we as a community help our fellow players with tips and advice on how to become better players! Good Aim, Bad Positioning t-shirt! http://bit.ly/ulstore
</summary>
</item>
