<item>
    <title>Symmetra Ability Overview | Overwatch</title>
    <meta>
        <summary>b'From order springs harmony: http://bit.ly/MeetSymmetra\n\nSatya Vaswani literally bends reality. By manipulating hard-light constructs, she crafts the world as she wishes it to be, in hopes of engineering a more perfect, orderly society. Given the name Symmetra by her employer, the Vishkar Corporation, she believes her actions serve the greater good, but there are times when she wonders whether the control and order she desires are truly best for humanity.\n\nSymmetra utilizes her light-bending photon projector to burn down adversaries and protect her associates. She also puts her technological prowess to work by building sentry drones and setting up teleporters that help her allies rapidly bring the fight to the front lines.\n\nSign Up for Beta: http://bit.ly/JoinOverwatch \nLike Us on Facebook: http://www.facebook.com/playoverwatch \nFollow Us on Twitter: http://www.twitter.com/playoverwatch' </summary>
    </meta>
    <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=-0TPg0rgmBo/</link>
    <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/-0TPg0rgmBo/sddefault.jpg</thumbnail>
</item>

<item>
    <title>Overwatch - New Symmetra Rework! ALL NEW ABILITIES!</title>
    <meta>
        <summary>b"The new Symmetra rework is now live on the Overwatch PTR! She's actually INSANE!!!!!!\n\n HyperX - CHECK THEM OUT! http://hyperx.gg/AlphaUnitLost [AD]\n UNIT LOST STORE! http://bit.ly/ulstore\n Discord JOIN NOW! http://discord.gg/unitlost  \n PATREON CAMPAIGN! http://www.patreon.com/unitlost\n Twitter https://twitter.com/unitlostgaming\n Live Stream http://www.twitch.tv/unitlost\n http://www.unitlost.com - Join our AWESOME community forums!" </summary>
    </meta>
    <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=khexvy-y_TQ/</link>
    <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/khexvy-y_TQ/sddefault.jpg</thumbnail>
</item>

<item>
    <title>Overwatch - Symmetra Guide - Teleporter Online! (Tips and Advice)</title>
    <meta>
        <summary>b"Symmetra is an unconventional support character, in this guide video I give tips and advice on how to best use Symmetras deployable turrets and teleporter. Symmetra is quickly becoming one of my favourite support heroes!\n\n PATREON CAMPAIGN! http://www.patreon.com/unitlost\n Steam Curator Page http://store.steampowered.com/curator/2666675/\n SUBSCRIBE! https://www.youtube.com/subscription_center?add_user=unitlosttube\n http://www.unitlost.com - Join our AWESOME community forums!\n T-shirts! http://unitlost.spreadshirt.co.uk/\n Sty's Twitter https://twitter.com/unitlostgaming\n Kiri's Twitter https://twitter.com/kirioth\n Live Stream http://www.twitch.tv/unitlost" </summary>
    </meta>
    <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=dBirsCrTzh0/</link>
    <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/dBirsCrTzh0/sddefault.jpg</thumbnail>
</item>

<item>
    <title>1 SYMMETRA TIP for EVERY HERO ft. Stevooo</title>
    <meta>
        <summary>b'Symmetra 3.0 rework tips with Stevooo! I waited until this recent rework before finally tackling Symm in the 1 Tips Series. \n\n Stevooo Socials:\n- https://twitch.tv/just_stevo\n- https://www.youtube.com/just_stevo\n\n\n KARQ SOCIALS:\n\nTwitch  https://twitch.tv/KarQ (Stream 5x weekly)\nMerch  https://karqgames.com\nDiscord  https://discord.gg/karq\nTwitter  https://twitter.com/KarQGames\nInstagram  http://instagram.com/KarQGames\nFacebook  https://www.facebook.com/KarQGames/\n\nThank you for helping me film:\nFormless, Qrae, HansiHufeise, Grimm, Avalil, Dekinaiyo, Kouta, Player, Trigger, F0k, MudaMuda, dxtrum, Alex, Snip3r, Littlepuptoo, Exile, RhysHo, nTic, TR8R, Gravel, xXlan213Xx, Fireblood248, artia678, Toasty, Frisky, Bork, Minnemann, littlebunny, Kinghd818, Xartoz, GigaFrans, Sykelone, Cocotte, TrashDpsMain, Banish72\n\n\n Music Used:\n\n Otis McDonald - Scarlet Fire https://youtu.be/8yOskhDn468\n GetSix - Chasing the Dragon https://soundcloud.com/getsixofficial' </summary>
    </meta>
    <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=TJtMZ8xMsjE/</link>
    <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/TJtMZ8xMsjE/sddefault.jpg</thumbnail>
</item>

<item>
    <title>Overwatch: How to Be a PRO Symmetra 3.0 - Seagull Advanced Guide</title>
    <meta>
        <summary>b'The NEW Symmetra 3.0 rework changes her play style significantly and today we study the play of Dallas Fuel Pro and streaming superstar Seagull who\'s famous for mastering these kind of niche heroes. In this advanced guide we show off symmetra\'s new weapon/offensive attack capabilities, teleporter and ultimate. The biggest synergies in play come when you give the instant mobility for her team to characters that are either entirely or functionally immobile most of the time like Ana, Orisa, Bastion, Torbjorn and when you start to "bounce the bunker" to instantly teleport characters that normally have limiting or NO mobility at all, to all of a sudden quickly escape, flank or get to spots they normally couldn\'t access at all, or not reliably in the chaos of a fight. BIG Game changing stuff coming in from the new Symmetra who essentially is a new hero release with how different she now plays. If you enjoyed today\'s guide video, be sure to leave it a like and check out the streamers featured in today\'s video linked below! \n\nCheck out the streamers featured! \nSeagull https://www.twitch.tv/a_seagull\nMendo https://www.twitch.tv/mendokusaii\n\n\n\nOUR VARIETY STREAM! https://www.fb.gg/yogaming\n\nSubscribe here - http://bit.ly/2aN1OuO\n\nRazer makes the best equipment, check out here! http://rzr.to/lnvvm\n\nWe are YOUR OVERWATCH:\nPatreon - https://www.patreon.com/YourOverwatch\nTwitter - https://twitter.com/youroverwatchyt\nTwitch - https://www.twitch.tv/youroverwatch \n\nDiscord Server:\nhttps://discordapp.com/invite/youroverwatch\n\nFREEDO\'s personal channel for Overwatch esports talk and more!\nhttps://www.youtube.com/user/xfreeedo' </summary>
    </meta>
    <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=96b8McQAAvc/</link>
    <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/96b8McQAAvc/sddefault.jpg</thumbnail>
</item>

<item>
    <title>Overwatch NEW Symmetra REWORK Gameplay! - ALL Abilities Breakdown!</title>
    <meta>
        <summary>b"Blizzard have released the new Symmetra to Overwatch today with a whole host of new and tweaked abilities and today we break it all down in a gameplay video! Let us know what you think and be sure to drop a Like & Subscribe if you enjoyed!\nSubscribe here - http://bit.ly/2aN1OuO\n\nNew Stream! https://www.fb.gg/yogaming\n\nRazer makes the best equipment, check out here! http://rzr.to/lnvvm\n\nWe are YOUR OVERWATCH:\nDestiny Channel: https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCb4Jomiox07xosU843EYTiw\nPatreon - https://www.patreon.com/YourOverwatch\nTwitter - https://twitter.com/youroverwatchyt\nTwitch - https://www.twitch.tv/youroverwatch \n\nDiscord Server:\nhttps://discordapp.com/invite/youroverwatch\n\nFREEDO's personal channel for Overwatch esports talk and more!\nhttps://www.youtube.com/user/xfreeedo" </summary>
    </meta>
    <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=QMGqjcy1Kag/</link>
    <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/QMGqjcy1Kag/sddefault.jpg</thumbnail>
</item>

<item>
    <title>Overwatch | NEW SYMMETRA - Top 5 Mistakes You Need To Avoid! /w Rank #1 Sym (ft MrBobWagner)</title>
    <meta>
        <summary>b'Check out Bob here! https://www.twitch.tv/mrbobwagner_\nToday we go over some big mistakes made by new Symmetra players. Our guest is ranked #1 Symmetra Mrbobwagner who tells us how to effectively use her abilities and know her role!\n CHECK OUT THIS AWESOME RGB KEYBOARD WE USE http://hyperx.gg/RGBOWC (sponsored)\n POWERED BY OMEN by HP, CHECK THEM OUT! http://bit.ly/OWC_OMEN (sponsored)\nWANT YOUR OW VOD REVIEWED? https://goo.gl/forms/y44NI061GD5aWfKZ2\n__\nFollow us!\nTwitter: https://twitter.com/OWCentral\nTwitch - Mysca: http://www.twitch.tv/mysca\nTwitch - Ryan: http://www.twitch.tv/ryancentral\n__\n\nMusic: Epidemic Sound\n\nApproaching Nirvana - Super Happy Fun Time\nhttp://youtube.com/user/approachingnirvana\nApproaching Nirvana on iTunes: https://itunes.apple.com/us/artist/approaching-nirvana/id313583565\n__\nThanks for watching!\n\n#Overwatch' </summary>
    </meta>
    <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=wGNYp8fOlCA/</link>
    <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/wGNYp8fOlCA/sddefault.jpg</thumbnail>
</item>

