
################################################################################
  <thumbnail>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PiDiaries/wow/master/sprays/widow.png</thumbnail>
  <fanart>https://d1u1mce87gyfbn.cloudfront.net/media/screenshot/widowmaker-screenshot-004.jpg</fanart>
  <summary>Widowmaker equips herself with whatever it takes to eliminate her targets, including mines that dispense poisonous gas, a visor that grants her squad infra-sight, and a powerful sniper rifle that can fire in fully-automatic mode.
  
 Widowmaker is the perfect assassin: a patient, ruthlessly efficient killer who shows neither emotion nor remorse.

It is believed that in her former life, Widowmaker was married to Gérard Lacroix, an Overwatch agent spearheading operations against the Talon terrorist organization. After several unsuccessful attempts to eliminate Gérard, Talon decided to change its focus to his wife, Amélie. Talon operatives kidnapped her and subjected her to an intense program of neural reconditioning. They broke her will, suppressed her personality, and reprogrammed her as a sleeper agent. She was eventually found by Overwatch agents, apparently none the worse for wear, and returned to her normal life.

Two weeks later she killed Gérard in his sleep.

Her mission complete, Amélie returned to Talon, and they completed the process of turning her into a living weapon. She was given extensive training in the covert arts, and then her physiology was altered, drastically slowing her heart, which turned her skin cold and blue and numbed her ability to experience human emotion. Amélie was gone.

Now, Widowmaker is Talon's most effective assassin, feeling little save the satisfaction of a job well done.
  </summary>
####################################################################################
<item>
  <title>Widowmaker Ability Overview</title>
  <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch/fvPp6XbbTb0</link>
  <thumbnail>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PiDiaries/wow/master/sprays/widow.png</thumbnail>
  <fanart>https://d1u1mce87gyfbn.cloudfront.net/media/screenshot/widowmaker-screenshot-004.jpg</fanart>
  <summary>Widowmaker is the perfect assassin: a patient, ruthlessly efficient killer who shows neither emotion nor remorse. She possesses extensive training in the covert arts, and with her scientifically altered physiology—which has drastically slowed her heart and turned her skin blue—she feels little more than the satisfaction of a job well done. 

Widowmaker is equipped with essential tools for eliminating her targets: poison gas mines; a powerful sniper rifle that has an alternate, fully automatic firing mode; a grappling hook for quickly reaching the perfect perch; and her signature visor, which grants infra-sight that’s shared with her allies, revealing the location of nearby enemies.  </summary>
</item>


<item>
  <title>Overwatch - Widowmaker Guide - One Shot, One Kill! (Tips and Advice)</title>
  <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch/EY2U9npriuA</link>
  <thumbnail>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PiDiaries/wow/master/sprays/widow.png</thumbnail>
  <fanart>https://d1u1mce87gyfbn.cloudfront.net/media/screenshot/widowmaker-screenshot-004.jpg</fanart>
  <summary>Widowmaker is the sniper. With a pinpoint accurate long range attack, she’s absolutely deadly in the hands of highly accurate FPS players. This video gives some solid Widowmaker tips and advice.
  </summary>
</item>
