<item>
    <title>Widowmaker Ability Overview | Overwatch</title>
    <meta>
        <summary>b'One shot, one kill: http://bit.ly/MeetWidowmaker\n\nWidowmaker is the perfect assassin: a patient, ruthlessly efficient killer who shows neither emotion nor remorse. She possesses extensive training in the covert arts, and with her scientifically altered physiologywhich has drastically slowed her heart and turned her skin blueshe feels little more than the satisfaction of a job well done. \n\nWidowmaker is equipped with essential tools for eliminating her targets: poison gas mines; a powerful sniper rifle that has an alternate, fully automatic firing mode; a grappling hook for quickly reaching the perfect perch; and her signature visor, which grants infra-sight thats shared with her allies, revealing the location of nearby enemies.  \n\nSign Up for Beta: http://bit.ly/JoinOverwatch \nLike Us on Facebook: http://www.facebook.com/playoverwatch \nFollow Us on Twitter: http://www.twitter.com/playoverwatch' </summary>
    </meta>
    <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=fvPp6XbbTb0/</link>
    <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/fvPp6XbbTb0/sddefault.jpg</thumbnail>
</item>

<item>
    <title>Overwatch - Widowmaker Guide - One Shot, One Kill! (Tips and Advice)</title>
    <meta>
        <summary>b"Widowmaker is the sniper. With a pinpoint accurate long range attack, shes absolutely deadly in the hands of highly accurate FPS players. This video gives some solid Widowmaker tips and advice.\n\n PATREON CAMPAIGN! http://www.patreon.com/unitlost\n Steam Curator Page http://store.steampowered.com/curator/2666675/\n SUBSCRIBE! https://www.youtube.com/subscription_center?add_user=unitlosttube\n http://www.unitlost.com - Join our AWESOME community forums!\n T-shirts! http://unitlost.spreadshirt.co.uk/\n Sty's Twitter https://twitter.com/unitlostgaming\n Kiri's Twitter https://twitter.com/kirioth\n Live Stream http://www.twitch.tv/unitlost" </summary>
    </meta>
    <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=EY2U9npriuA/</link>
    <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/EY2U9npriuA/sddefault.jpg</thumbnail>
</item>

<item>
    <title>The Ultimate Widowmaker Guide - EVERYTHING you Need to Know!</title>
    <meta>
        <summary>b'Teaching you how to become the sniping master.\n\nTwitter: https://twitter.com/L0NEHAWK\n\nSubreddit (Gaming Stuff): reddit.com/r/HawkSquad\n\nIntro by Marv DE: https://www.youtube.com/user/marvluebke/videos\n\nMusic Provided by NoCopyrightSounds(In order):\nTobu-Roots https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=7wNb0pHyGuI\nTobu-Life https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=OBwl2glmqC0\nTobu-Candyland https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=IIrCDAV3EgI\nTobu https://soundcloud.com/7obu\n \nVexento-Masked Raver https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Nvc0hgt9I1g\nVexento  https://soundcloud.com/vexento\n \nJim Yosef-Eclipse https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=1WP_YLn1D1c\nJim Yosef https://soundcloud.com/jim-yosef\n \nJJD-Adventure  https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=f2xGxd9xPYA\nJJD  https://soundcloud.com/jjdofficial\n \nAlan Walker-Force https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=xshEZzpS4CQ\nAlan Walker  https://soundcloud.com/alanwalkermusic\n \nJensation-Donuts https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=jxrorclF18Y\nJensation https://soundcloud.com/dj-jensation' </summary>
    </meta>
    <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=zu8myDcfV9g/</link>
    <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/zu8myDcfV9g/sddefault.jpg</thumbnail>
</item>

<item>
    <title>Overwatch: Hard Shots MADE EASY! - Improve Accuracy Guide!</title>
    <meta>
        <summary>b"Overwatch Deathadder Elite GIVEAWAY! https://gleam.io/h2nNX/youroverwatch-razer-giveaway\n\nBuy the Mouse for yourself! http://rzr.to/iCQsf\n\nWidowmaker is one of the hardest heroes to play and master, however knowledge is half the battle in Overwatch Gameplay. If you know what to look for and how to simply prepare yourself for EASY shots your Widowmaker reliability goes far up. Thanks to Razer for supplying the 3 Overwatch Deathadder Elites that we are giving away as well as supporting us in general.\n\nSubscribe here - http://bit.ly/2aN1OuO\n\nRazer makes the best equipment, check out here! http://rzr.to/lnvvm\n\nWe are YOUR OVERWATCH:\nDestiny Channel: https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCb4Jomiox07xosU843EYTiw\nPatreon - https://www.patreon.com/YourOverwatch\nTwitter - https://twitter.com/youroverwatchyt\nTwitch - https://www.twitch.tv/youroverwatch \n\nDiscord Server:\nhttps://discordapp.com/invite/youroverwatch\n\nFREEDO's personal channel for Overwatch esports talk and more!\nhttps://www.youtube.com/user/xfreeedo" </summary>
    </meta>
    <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=5g5dY7qMkH4/</link>
    <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/5g5dY7qMkH4/sddefault.jpg</thumbnail>
</item>

<item>
    <title>WIDOWMAKER GUIDE: HOW TO LAND MORE SHOTS! [OVERWATCH]</title>
    <meta>
        <summary>b'This video covers a specific topic that a lot of Widowmakers are constantly asking and that question is "how to improve your accuracy with Widowmaker". In this video I cover 7 fundamentals to land more shots with widowmaker and how those fundamentals can help you improve your accuracy! Thank you for watching my Widowmaker Guide, feel free to LIKE the video if you found it helpful and make sure to SUBSCRIBE so you dont miss out on my future content. Furthermore feel free to check out my Widowmaker Guides playlist below!\n\nWidowmaker Guides Playlist: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=uKGu985UeIg&list=PLY47JQRhX-kgCS3C_UwqZSGzGYhBAAwQu\nWidowmaker map guide playlist: https://www.youtube.com/playlist?list=PLY47JQRhX-kgwX9TTGulNsJ9wh3F1a23c\nOverwatch Guides Playlist: https://www.youtube.com/playlist?list=PLY47JQRhX-kgWvEs0bENU9wC6ePl3npfe\n\nThe Overwatch Playlist: https://www.youtube.com/playlist?list=PLY47JQRhX-khgl3nNDp-3u1f03p2AHjMB\n\nInstagram: https://www.instagram.com/salvajee\nTwitch: https://www.twitch.tv/salvajee\nJoin the TSC Discord Server: https://discord.gg/mTpfKJa\nTwitter: https://twitter.com/salvajeefromtsc\nSubscribe to The Salvaje Cartel: https://www.youtube.com/thesalvajecartel?sub_confirmation=1' </summary>
    </meta>
    <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=vAYs_k39YDg/</link>
    <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/vAYs_k39YDg/sddefault.jpg</thumbnail>
</item>

<item>
    <title>Top 5 Widowmaker Tips to Rank Up FAST! Beginner to Advanced - Overwatch Guide</title>
    <meta>
        <summary>b'Top 5 Widowmaker Tips! Beginner to Advanced - Overwatch Guide. Master widow with these tips and tricks and pro player gameplay. Improve your aim and play style to rank up fast and easy! No more bronze, silver, gold and platinum. Say hello to diamond, masters and grandmaster! Become as good as PINE! ...well maybe not but you can try ;)\n\n\n\nIn this video we talk about: \nOverwatch Widowmaker Guide\nOverwatch Widowmaker Tips\nOverwatch Widowmaker Advice\nOverwatch Widowmaker Improve\n\nMore Overwatch Guides:\nhttps://www.youtube.com/playlist?list=PLsSYS03ynFoEoy_5fYcyq1WehB3elOg8D\n\n\n STAY CONNECTED! \n\n\nFollow Us on Social Media!\n Twitter: http://Twitter.com/UltraGuides\n Discord: https://discord.gg/ultra\n Twitch: http://Twitch.tv/UltraGuides\n\n\nSources \nhttps://www.twitch.tv/crosyph\nhttps://www.twitch.tv/hjm3935\nhttps://www.twitch.tv/aimbotcalvin\nhttps://www.twitch.tv/kephrii\nhttps://www.twitch.tv/tf2pine\nhttps://www.twitch.tv/overwatchleague\nhttps://www.twitch.tv/zeerocious\n___\n\n\nThat just about does it for this video guys, if you liked Top 5 Widowmaker Tips to Rank Up FAST! Beginner to Advanced - Overwatch Guide , hit that like button, if you want to see more videos like this as they are made public, subscribe. If you want to enter in some sick giveaways, you can follow us on twitter @UltraGuides. If you wanna hang with me and the other UG members, you can join our Discord server.  Thank you so much for staying till the end of the video. Stay amazing, and we will see you, in the next one.' </summary>
    </meta>
    <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=l9_9R5DNE5o/</link>
    <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/l9_9R5DNE5o/sddefault.jpg</thumbnail>
</item>

<item>
    <title>Overwatch PRO Widowmaker Guide: Dorado DOMINATION</title>
    <meta>
        <summary>b' Join NOW! https://ow.gameleap.com/ - Learn from Top 500 Pros and carry your games!\n\nIn this guide, GM and Top 500 Widowmaker Ahlekss will share some top tips and tricks for Widowmaker in this pro gameplay analysis of a Dorado game.\n\nThanks for watching. If you have any questions or want to reach us, please send an email at support@game-leap.com and we will get back to you shortly.' </summary>
    </meta>
    <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=xwf6pvNrOLQ/</link>
    <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/xwf6pvNrOLQ/sddefault.jpg</thumbnail>
</item>

<item>
    <title>1 WIDOWMAKER TIP for EVERY HERO ft. j0000mla25</title>
    <meta>
        <summary>b'Widow tips? You mean just shoot their heads 4Head? In all seriousness I hope you find this 1 WIDOW TIP vs EVERY HERO video insightful and that you learn something!\n\n j00m Socials:\n- https://www.twitch.tv/j0000mla25\n- https://twitter.com/j0000mla25\n\n\n KARQ SOCIALS:\n\nTwitch  https://twitch.tv/KarQ \nMerch  https://teespring.com/stores/karq\nDiscord  https://discord.gg/karq\nTwitter  https://twitter.com/KarQGames\nInstagram  http://instagram.com/KarQGames\nFacebook  https://www.facebook.com/KarQGames/\n\n- Thank you KojiNatu, RawLatexPilot, HFCPhoenix, Katmayla for helping me film!\n\n- The map graphics/tool during the Widow v Widow tip were provided by: https://statbanana.com/\n\n\n Music Used:\n\n Otis McDonald - Scarlet Fire https://youtu.be/8yOskhDn468\n GetSix - Chasing the Dragon https://soundcloud.com/getsixofficial' </summary>
    </meta>
    <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=yRVLdXyZ0wE/</link>
    <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/yRVLdXyZ0wE/sddefault.jpg</thumbnail>
</item>

<item>
    <title>Basic Widowmaker tips on Widow Vs Widow | Surefour Tutorials</title>
    <meta>
        <summary>b'Tutorial  0:10\nQ&A / Explanations  16:49\nHandcam Footage 24:43\nWatch me @ https://twitch.tv/Surefour\nFollow me @  https://twitter.com/Surefour\nFollow me @ https://www.instagram.com/surefourofficial/?hl=en\n\nEditor - Nscwalk @ https://twitter.com/Nscwalk\nThumbnail made by- Junedori' </summary>
    </meta>
    <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=IWdHcx4Qs64/</link>
    <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/IWdHcx4Qs64/sddefault.jpg</thumbnail>
</item>

<item>
    <title>Overwatch Widowmaker Guide: Improve Scoped Accuracy</title>
    <meta>
        <summary>b"Widowmaker is a fan favorite that takes a lot of skill to master, but with this guide's tactics you can develop your effectiveness at any level of play. \n\nWe are YOUR OVERWATCH \nhttps://twitter.com/eddythechump\nhttps://twitter.com/thelegalweagal\nhttps://twitter.com/xfreeedo\n\n\nCut and Run - Electronic Hard by Kevin MacLeod is licensed under a Creative Commons Attribution license (https://creativecommons.org/licenses/by/4.0/)\nSource: http://incompetech.com/music/royalty-free/index.html?isrc=USUAN1100851\nArtist: http://incompetech.com/" </summary>
    </meta>
    <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=KrSY1Jljilk/</link>
    <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/KrSY1Jljilk/sddefault.jpg</thumbnail>
</item>

<item>
    <title>Widowmaker Tips - Secret Spots and Flanks</title>
    <meta>
        <summary>b"Here is a little guide of useful spots to be as Widowmaker. I wouldn't call this a full blown guide or anything, just some secret spots that I like to use that you may not know about.\n\nSubscribe for DANK videos! \n\nMy sensitivity! 85 Horz / 75 Vert / 68 Scope / 69 Grapple  / 80 Aim Assist / 96 Aim Smoothing / 10 Aim Window / Dual Zone\n\nMY TWITTER!! - https://twitter.com/BacKoFFmyJanKzz\n\nTHE DANK SQUAD DISCORD - https://discordapp.com/invite/danksquad\n\n***Follow Chicken9man on twitch - https://www.twitch.tv/chicken9man_live\n\nIntro creator's channel : https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCDPHQbgIVv4pK5NkJOtrpHA\n\nChannel art by - https://twitter.com/TheEmperuh\n\nMusic by Knox Hill - https://twitter.com/theknoxhill\n                                    -https://www.youtube.com/user/KnoxHillDMV" </summary>
    </meta>
    <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Y6pRc2yRgFg/</link>
    <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/Y6pRc2yRgFg/sddefault.jpg</thumbnail>
</item>

<item>
    <title>YOU'RE DYING TOO MUCH! Advanced Positioning Guide (Overwatch)</title>
    <meta>
        <summary>b'Today, we focus on your positioning in Overwatch, which can help you die less and rank up!\n\nTwitter: https://twitter.com/L0NEHAWK\n\nSong: Alan Walker - FADE (NCS) https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=bM7SZ5SBzyY\nhttps://twitter.com/IAmAlanWalker\n\nSubreddit (Gaming Stuff): reddit.com/r/HawkSquad\n\nIntro by Marv DE: https://www.youtube.com/user/marvluebke/videos' </summary>
    </meta>
    <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ba46jIWwp0Q/</link>
    <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/ba46jIWwp0Q/sddefault.jpg</thumbnail>
</item>

<item>
    <title>The Complete History and Lore of Widowmaker</title>
    <meta>
        <summary>b"The Complete History and Lore of Widowmaker. We keep on looking at the complete history and lore of Overwatch heroes.\n Subscribe to TGN for daily video game videos! Click to Subscribe!  http://bit.ly/1KJq3G2 \nVoiced by TGN Network Partner Moxness: https://twitter.com/JonathanMoxness\nWritten by Jeffrey Harris\nEdited by TGN Network Partner Fgeitas: https://www.youtube.com/MagicalNoob\n\nThe TGN channel is a collaboration between the TGN Network and TGN partners. We work directly with TGN Partners in the Network to  create and co-produced videos for this channel. If you're interested in joining TGN and working with us, click below for more information. \n\nPartner with TGN  http://bit.ly/1VDyHq3\nStore  http://shop.tgn.tv\nWebsite  http://central.tgn.tv/\nLike Us  https://www.facebook.com/TGNTV\nFollow Us  https://twitter.com/tgntv\nSquadron  https://www.youtube.com/user/Games\nMinecraft  https://www.youtube.com/user/TGNMinecraft\nTwitch  http://www.twitch.tv/tgn\n\nMusic by Epidemic Sound http://www.epidemicsound.com\n\n\n\nTGN is your source for Overwatch YouTube! We post daily gaming videos including a Overwatch facts, Overwatch lore, Overwatch tips, and Overwatch Community Highlights." </summary>
    </meta>
    <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=q5RY7znZjuE/</link>
    <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/q5RY7znZjuE/sddefault.jpg</thumbnail>
</item>

<item>
    <title>Widowmaker Guide to Improve Beginners on Console</title>
    <meta>
        <summary>b"The Advanced Guide is finished! Be sure to check that out!\n\nSimple, quick guide to help people starting out as Widowmaker to improve faster! Don't forget this is only a basic guide - I don't speak about abilities and basics of the hero but rather speak on basic ways to improve. I will make an advanced guide for those above average and looking for little tips to improve even more!\n\nSubscribe for DANK videos! \n\nJoin the #DankSquad! Search Dank Squad on communities on the PS4 to keep up with the memes, action, and competitive shenanigans!\n\nFollow Chicken9man on twitch - www.twitch.tv/chicken9man_" </summary>
    </meta>
    <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=qLH4lIvjCjc/</link>
    <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/qLH4lIvjCjc/sddefault.jpg</thumbnail>
</item>

<item>
    <title>WIDOWMAKER - Overwatch One Trick Guide</title>
    <meta>
        <summary>b'Man I sure do love http://lootcrate.com/bricky and Promo Code - Bricky for 10% off just like I love Widowmaker.\n\nTwitter - https://twitter.com/BrickyOrchid8\nTwitch - http://www.twitch.tv/brickyorchid8\nBigBrickPlays - https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCHcODW8jrSHWw7Na0dC6qcA\nInstagram - BrickyOrchid8\n\nIronside Computers | Click here to customize your own PC -  http://ironsidecomputers.com\n\nLF Gaming Chairs - https://lfgaming.com/shop/?ref=11\n\nP.O. Box\nBrickyOrchid8\n22365 El Toro Road.\nLake Forest, CA 92630\n#338\n\nAll P.O BOX items sent will be opened every other week!' </summary>
    </meta>
    <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=B4vh-QNc9ls/</link>
    <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/B4vh-QNc9ls/sddefault.jpg</thumbnail>
</item>

<item>
    <title>Overwatch Widowmaker Guide: Everything You Need To Know</title>
    <meta>
        <summary>b'In this video, we go over everything I could think of from my 100+ hours of Widowmaker in Overwatch. We go over aim, positioning, Widow vs Widow matchup, and more!\n\nEnd Song: JJD - Adventure\n\nTwitter: https://twitter.com/Skyline_OW\n\nTwitch: https://www.twitch.tv/skyline_ow' </summary>
    </meta>
    <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=f_DXy9ln1Xg/</link>
    <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/f_DXy9ln1Xg/sddefault.jpg</thumbnail>
</item>

<item>
    <title>How GRANDMASTER Players DESTROY With Widowmaker | TAIMOU - Overwatch Season 7 Competitive Guide</title>
    <meta>
        <summary>b'----------------------------------------------------------------\nThis video was sponsored by Guilded. Find out more about the best Overwatch LFG around, plus a chance at a $50 Blizzard Card giveaway here: https://www.guilded.gg/JoeKingYT\n----------------------------------------------------------------\n\n\nToday we are back again trying a top 500 tip Widowmaker video because I think its fun and people just love Widowmaker it seems. Today we are talking about how the grandmaster Widowmaker player can carry his competitive games in season 7 overwatch competitive ranked mode. Going over some Widowmaker season 7 tips and guide or whatever you want to call it. thanks! \n\n\n\n\nMore Videos! : https://www.youtube.com/playlist?list=PLefC4eOMnbRF5Xm7uCjfU73bh0ybup9Df\n\n\n\nGameplay: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=7177L-GNkDk\nThumbnail:https://pbs.twimg.com/media/C_Q2U6MUMAAa2hV.jpg\n-----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------\n\n\n\n======================================================================\n\nTIPS I WROTE DOWN FROM THE VIDEO:\n-While your team is starting to push up, wait for people to peak around corners for a pick\n-always go in after your team has already engaged\n-Dont ignore tanks\n-Use your hookshot to send you flying to escape people following you\n-If you are facing a shield, its ok to run trhough it and finish off tanks with your machinegun mode\n-After you get a teamwipe, push up a ton for free picks\n-If you are getting healed and someone is attacking you, just scope and try to get the 1 shot\n-If you dont think you can get the headshot on a close range tank, just machine gun him\n-Charge up your sniper before you walk around walls/doors\n-Dont use your hookshot until the Widowmaker has jumped\n-You dont need tanks on your team to play widow, just use height and distance to stay safe\n\n\n-put a mine at enemy spawn for free ult charge, then shoot another one out for more charge/vision\n-try to position to where you will be the furthest away from when enemies dive\n-Your ult makes you beat widow in 1v1 always\n-Dont be afraid to just double bodyshot supports, especially a non ulting mercy\n-dont peak around walls if enemies have a widow, use your hookshot to get in position\n-bodyshotting a tracer forces her to waste her e, keeping you pretty safe\n-switch to another hero if the map gets way to close in and there is no good long range angles\n\n======================================================================\n\n\n\n\n\nWhat is overwatch?: Well overwatch is Blizzards new take on the fps genre. In this game you choose a hero or "Class" to take on enemies, push payloads, and take control points. The point of the game is to beat the other team over and it is indeed a whole bunch of fun to play. The game includes 27 heroes so far and Is a blast to play. In this video I mostly go over playing it in a commentary type of manner, and these types of videos will usually be overwatch live commentaries or overwatch group commentaries. As well expect a few guides of this game in the future and some box openings as well. Anyways, hope you enjoy blizzards new hit!\'\n\nWho is JoeKing aka me. Im a overwatch youtuber that likes to talk about character updates, how to get better, and the competitive community. Trying to help you get better at overwatch and entertain at the same time hopefully. How GRANDMASTER Players DESTORY with Widowmaker - Overwatch Top 500 PRO Tricks Overwatch - 20 TricksWidowmaker Grandmasters ABUSE That You Don\'t! Some tips and tricks to master Widowmaker! Overwatch - 7 OP Tips and Tricks Grandmaster Players use every game! Widowmaker overwatch, Widowmaker guide top 500 tips and tricks  Widowmaker master gameplay, how Widowmaker is played, shadowburn gameplay Widowmaker overwatch competitive esports vod grandmaster Widowmaker tricks grandmaster top 500 Widowmaker, overwatch top 700 Widowmaker esports vod Widowmaker esports gameplay, grandmaster Widowmaker tricks top 500 tricks tips, how to play Widowmaker, Widowmaker season 7, overwatch competitive season 7 Widowmaker, Widowmaker season 7 offense, Widowmaker season 7 defense, overwatch season 7 Widowmaker guide       overwatch,Widowmaker tricks,Tricks Widowmaker Grandmasters ABUSE That You Don\'t,Tricks Widowmaker Grandmasters ABUSE That You Don\'t overwatch,overwatch Tricks Widowmaker Grandmasters ABUSE That You Don\'t,tricks grandmasters abuse that you dont,overwatch tricks grandmasters abuse that you dont,grandmaster tricks overwatch,Widowmaker grandmaster,Widowmaker top 500 trick,How GRANDMASTER Players DESTROY with Widowmaker,Widowmaker season 7 competitive,Widowmaker vod,grandmaster, Widowmaker seagull, seagull Widowmaker, best Widowmaker, strongest Widowmaker, best Widowmaker player, overwatch seagull\n\n\n\nTitle:How GRANDMASTER Players DESTROY With Widowmaker | KEPHRII - Overwatch Season 7 Competitive Guide Tips' </summary>
    </meta>
    <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=u3QMloI57T8/</link>
    <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/u3QMloI57T8/sddefault.jpg</thumbnail>
</item>

<item>
    <title>How to improve your Widowmaker/ DPS play Dramatically: Overwatch Coaching GrandMaster Vod review</title>
    <meta>
        <summary>b"This video is a testament to the typical answer from dps players who wish their aim was better, this vod features a player who has top notch aim but lacks in other areas including cool down management and positioning. You need more than just aim to reach the top.\nPoints of interest: 2.00- first fight advantages \n3.00-  identifying threats and reacting\n6.00- re engagement critical thinking \n11.00- identifying a lost or won fight and playing for better positioning on the next one\n12:30- my biggest tip to DPS players who think that they deserve to be higher, part of this being they have good aim\n20.00 Lines of sight, lanes and map control \n25.00- staying alive, identifying when your the enemy greatest threat\n27.30- more sight line management \n31.00- setting up crossfires \n34.00- how being spawn camped or being hard focused can be turned into a positive \n37.00 echinwalde 3rd point sight lines\n41.00- even if you're beginning to loose duels, how to stay effective\n44.50- 3 takeaways\n50.30- Bonus content: deeper explanation of cross angles and setting up crossfires" </summary>
    </meta>
    <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=vOq_cNIH9k0/</link>
    <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/vOq_cNIH9k0/sddefault.jpg</thumbnail>
</item>

<item>
    <title>Overwatch: How to improve your aim on Console | (PS4 Xbox One Overwatch)</title>
    <meta>
        <summary>b'Struggling with McCree and Widowmaker on console Overwatch? Here\'s a few tips that will help you improve!\nIt will still take some work and dedication from you, if you really want to improve, but this video covers the most important techniques you wanna know, when you\'re just starting out with hit-scan heroes.\n\nBackground music:\nIHF - Departure\nIHF - Arrival\nIHF - Fade\n\nFor updates, stream announcements and more random stuff, follow me on Twitter! https://twitter.com/ApexCris\n\nI\'m partnered on Twitch! You should totally check out my channel and drop it a follow! http://www.twitch.tv/apexcris\n\nI\'m sponsored by KontrolFreeks! You can use the discount code "CRIS" for 10% off all their products!\nhttp://www.kontrolfreek.com' </summary>
    </meta>
    <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Qk3l8N7QeYA/</link>
    <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/Qk3l8N7QeYA/sddefault.jpg</thumbnail>
</item>

<item>
    <title>Widowmaker Aim Guide | All Forms Basic To Advanced</title>
    <meta>
        <summary>b'Today we are talking about widowmaker aim styles, how to do them, when to do them and so on.\n\nEnter the giveaway: Type #Action into the comment section!\n\nWatch me live and ask me questions! https://www.twitch.tv/jonal_ow\n\nJoin the community on Discord and talk with me: https://discord.me/jonalgaming\n\nKeep updated! follow me on Twitter: https://twitter.com/Jonal_ow\n\nHope You Enjoyed, Drop Your Opinion Down In The Comments \n\\(^.^)/\n\n\nTrack: Jo Cohen & Sex Whales - Run Away (feat. Lusil) [NCS Release]\nMusic provided by NoCopyrightSounds.\nWatch: https://youtu.be/wHHSN6tdeZI' </summary>
    </meta>
    <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=iVUAZ7EaHXM/</link>
    <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/iVUAZ7EaHXM/sddefault.jpg</thumbnail>
</item>

<item>
    <title>[Rating: 81] Kephrii's Widowmaker Warmup</title>
    <meta>
        <summary>b'400 DPI, 8 Sensitivity, 35 Scope, 6 Windows, 1000hz Polling Rate\nRazer Deathadder Chroma on a Razer Goliathus Control Mouse Pad' </summary>
    </meta>
    <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=bG1pk8ifhSk/</link>
    <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/bG1pk8ifhSk/sddefault.jpg</thumbnail>
</item>

<item>
    <title>Overwatch - A Handy Dandy Guide to Widowmaker</title>
    <meta>
        <summary>b"Through the fire and flames.\n\nThis is my very first Overwatch video, so I guess we'll see how things go, eh? In this tutorial I'll be going over the basics of playing widowmaker, as well as a few ways to improve your aim.\n\n----------------------------------------------------------------------------\n Steam Group! http://goo.gl/XHGl1f\n Twitch Stream! http://goo.gl/gWJ4Kh\n Twitter! https://goo.gl/zHuP9s\n Facebook! https://goo.gl/Ay0mDP\n----------------------------------------------------------------------------\n\n Songs:\nSuper Monkey Ball - Monkey Mall\nSuper Monkey Ball - Arctic\n\nHave an idea for a video? Leave a comment below!" </summary>
    </meta>
    <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=m0KO0qUWYu8/</link>
    <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/m0KO0qUWYu8/sddefault.jpg</thumbnail>
</item>

<item>
    <title>Fuel Pro Tips | Widowmaker Tips and Tricks | aKm</title>
    <meta>
        <summary>b'*Please help our videos reach everyone by adding close captions*\nhttp://www.youtube.com/timedtext_cs_panel?c=UCj4XSmDqIhRT4frKzRTMyrA&tab=2\n\n#DallasFuel #Burnblue\n\nDress like the Fuel:\nhttps://gear.blizzard.com/us/dallas-fuel\n\nFollow the Fuel:\nFacebook:\nhttp://facebook.com/TheDallasFuel\n\nInstagram:\nhttp://instagram.com/DallasFuel \n\nYouTube:\nhttp://youtube.com/DallasFuel' </summary>
    </meta>
    <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=d0k45GBk_TU/</link>
    <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/d0k45GBk_TU/sddefault.jpg</thumbnail>
</item>

<item>
    <title>Overwatch Widowmaker Guide - Best Sensitivity For YOU</title>
    <meta>
        <summary>b"Trouble figuring out where to set your sensitivity in Overwatch? Weagal breaks down the pros and cons to different philosophies on where to set your sensitivity. Ultimately, it will be based on preference, the lower you play, the more mouse mat you'd need and will require your whole arm to aim, the higher you play on will test your ability to control and may cause you to miss what you're aiming at if you can't handle it. Note this video was created before the Widowmaker nerf dropped. \nSubscribe here: https://www.youtube.com/c/youroverwatch?sub_confirmation=1\nWe are YOUR OVERWATCH \nhttps://twitter.com/eddythechump\nhttps://twitter.com/thelegalweagal\nhttps://twitter.com/xfreeedo" </summary>
    </meta>
    <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=dlMi1rxfNZU/</link>
    <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/dlMi1rxfNZU/sddefault.jpg</thumbnail>
</item>

<item>
    <title>SOON - How PROS Use WIDOWMAKER In Overwatch League - Overwatch Season 8 Competitive Widowmaker Guide</title>
    <meta>
        <summary>b"Today im talking about how pros use Widowmaker in the overwatch league and give some quick tips to players trying to learn how to play Widowmaker in overwatch competitive season 8 ranked, this is a mini guide video on positioning and where to be and also how to deal with some of the most problematic heroes in this season. Enjoy\n\n\n\n\nPlaylist: https://www.youtube.com/playlist?list=PLefC4eOMnbRF5Xm7uCjfU73bh0ybup9Df\n\n\nthumbnail: in game\n\n\nGameplays:\nOverwatch League : https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=mGY8mhTIvqg\nBackground gameplay : https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=cArnjs5WJlk\n------------------------------------------------------------------------------------\n\n\n\n\n\n\nAnyways, hope you enjoy blizzards new hit!'overwatch,overwatch,joe king,Overwatch Season 8 Placements,overwatch season 8,overwatch season 8 meta,overwatch season 8 tips,overwatch season 8 changes,overwatch season 8 competitive,overwatch season 8 start,overwatch season 8 update,overwatch season 8 guide,overwatch season 8 start date,season 8,season 8 overwatch,overwatch s8,season 8 guide,how to get to diamond overwatch season 8,overwatch placements,overwatch placement matches,overwatch placement tips,placements, how to climb to diamond, how to get to diamond season 8, how to climb out of bronze, bronze to silver, silver to gold, gold to platinum, platinum to diamond, diamond to masters, masters to grandmasters season 8,overwatch,joe king,overwatch league,overwatch esports,overwatch league analysis,overwatch league highlights,overwatch league vods,overwatch season 8,how to rank up overwatch season 8,overwatch league skins,overwatch league teams,overwatch league games,overwatch league gameplay,overwatch league houston outlaws,overwatch league full match,houston outlaws,overwatch esports 2018,overwatch esports highlights,overwatch league live,overwatch league tips,league,ow\n\nVideo Title: Soon - How PROS Use Widowmaker In Overwatch League - Season 8 Competitive Widowmaker Guide / Tips / Rank Up" </summary>
    </meta>
    <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=b7aaO5e-DGE/</link>
    <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/b7aaO5e-DGE/sddefault.jpg</thumbnail>
</item>

<item>
    <title>How to git gud at Widowmaker</title>
    <meta>
        <summary>b'Welcome to this Overwatch Guide on how to improve as Widowmaker. \n\nJoin my discord server:\n\n https://discord.gg/sirswag\n\nSupport me on Patreon:\n\n https://www.patreon.com/SirSwag\n\nBuy a dank t-shirt:\n\nhttps://shop.spreadshirt.com/100251595/\n\nSongs used:\n\nLynx  Apollo\n\nhttps://www.youtube.com/watch?v=oduJFOiwnZI&ab_channel=EtherealRecords' </summary>
    </meta>
    <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=OU2kH0jgsso/</link>
    <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/OU2kH0jgsso/sddefault.jpg</thumbnail>
</item>

<item>
    <title>Overwatch: How To Play Widowmaker Guide (Beginner Tips, Abilities & Mechanics)</title>
    <meta>
        <summary>b'This Widowmaker beginner guide is designed to teach you the abilities, mechanics, and tips to help you better play Widowmaker in Overwatch. This hero starter guide was designed for beginners or those wanting more basic tips.\n\nIf you liked the video, please leave a like and if you want to see more content, please subscribe and follow me on Facebook and Twitter.\n\nSubscribe:https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCYzCvF2KO2ms9hADC9hS4og?sub_confirmation=1\n\nFacebook: https://www.facebook.com/RealToastGaming\n\nTwitter: https://www.twitter.com/RealToastGaming' </summary>
    </meta>
    <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=1yA34AQStwc/</link>
    <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/1yA34AQStwc/sddefault.jpg</thumbnail>
</item>

<item>
    <title>WIDOWMAKER GUIDE: POSITIONING MADE EASY!</title>
    <meta>
        <summary>b'In this video I am bringing you guys a widowmaker positioning guide in which is will be sharing with you guys 3 questions so you guys can master widowmaker positioning easily by asking yourselves these questions. These are the core fundamentals of widowmaker positioning and the stepping stone to take start taking your positioning to the next level! Thank you for watching my Widowmaker Guide, feel free to LIKE the video if you found it helpful and make sure to SUBSCRIBE so you dont miss out on my future content. Furthermore feel free to check out my Widowmaker Guides playlist below!\n\nWidowmaker Guides Playlist: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=uKGu985UeIg&list=PLY47JQRhX-kgCS3C_UwqZSGzGYhBAAwQu\nWidowmaker map guide playlist: https://www.youtube.com/playlist?list=PLY47JQRhX-kgwX9TTGulNsJ9wh3F1a23c\nOverwatch Guides Playlist: https://www.youtube.com/playlist?list=PLY47JQRhX-kgWvEs0bENU9wC6ePl3npfe\n\nThe Overwatch Playlist: https://www.youtube.com/playlist?list=PLY47JQRhX-khgl3nNDp-3u1f03p2AHjMB\n\nInstagram: https://www.instagram.com/salvajee\nTwitch: https://www.twitch.tv/salvajee\nJoin the TSC Discord Server: https://discord.gg/mTpfKJa\nTwitter: https://twitter.com/salvajeefromtsc\nSubscribe to The Salvaje Cartel: https://www.youtube.com/thesalvajecartel?sub_confirmation=1\n#TheSalvajeCartel #Overwatch #WidowmakerGuide' </summary>
    </meta>
    <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=DhVZEAJzJ0Y/</link>
    <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/DhVZEAJzJ0Y/sddefault.jpg</thumbnail>
</item>

<item>
    <title>[LEARN OVERWATCH] Widowmaker Practice Drills Improve Your Aim Guide</title>
    <meta>
        <summary>b"Some Widowmaker practice drills I used to or still do.\nThey helped me a lot back when my aim was non-existent, hope they'll help you as well!\n______________________________________\n\nParts:\n0:25 - Training mode practice (Basic drills)\n1:36 - Widow forbidden jutsu!\n3:29 - Custom game practice (Advanced drills).\n5:29 - Giving my love  to you!\n______________________________________\n\nSettings for the custom game\n\nMODES:\n-SKIRMISH\n * HEALTH PACK RESPAWN TIME SCALAR: 10%\n * RESPAWN TIME SCALAR: 0%\n\nMAPS\n-SKIRMISH\n *NUMBANI (ALL OTHER MAPS ARE TURNED OFF IN ALL OF THE MODES)\n\nHEROES\n-GENERAL\n *ABILITY COOLDOWN TIME: 0%\n *NO AMMUNITION REQUIREMENT: ON\n *RECEIVE HEADSHOTS ONLY: ON\n-ANA\n *BIOTIC GRENADE: OFF\n *DMG DEALT: 10%\n *HEALING DEALT: 10%\n *HEALING RECEIVED: 10%\n *HEALTH: 500%\n *SLEEP DART: OFF\n *ULTIMATE ABILITY: OFF\n-SOLDIER 76\n *DMG DEALT: 10%\n *HEALING DEALT: 10%\n *HEALING RECEIVED: 10%\n *HEALTH: 500%\n *ULTIMATE ABILITY: OFF\n-WIDOWMAKER\n *DAMAGE DEALT: 500%\n *DAMAGE RECEIVED: 10%\n *HEALING RECEIVED: 500%\n *HEALTH: 500%\n *RECEIVE HEADSHOTS ONLY: ON\nIf you liked the video, check out my channel and subscribe to see all the latest uploads. \n\nSocial Media\nTwitch: twitch.tv/slay4joy\nTwitter: twitter.com/slay4joy" </summary>
    </meta>
    <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=s2vzYoVZoO0/</link>
    <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/s2vzYoVZoO0/sddefault.jpg</thumbnail>
</item>

<item>
    <title>Advanced Guide for Widowmakers on Console / PC</title>
    <meta>
        <summary>b'I really hope that this guide will help you become a better Widowmaker! I was very straight and to the point to not waste much time so hopefully I got the points across well enough with the example clips provided. If you see some something needing of improvement, let me know in the comments below! \n\nSubscribe for DANK videos! \n\nMy sensitivty! 80 Horz / 70 Vert / 50 Scope / 50 Grapple Dual Zone\n\nJoin the #DankSquad! Search Dank Squad on communities on the PS4 to keep up with the memes, action, and competitive shenanigans!\n\nFollow Chicken9man on twitch - www.twitch.tv/chicken9man_' </summary>
    </meta>
    <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Jpb5okE_k-E/</link>
    <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/Jpb5okE_k-E/sddefault.jpg</thumbnail>
</item>

