
################################################################################
  <thumbnail>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PiDiaries/wow/master/sprays/winston.png</thumbnail>
  <fanart>https://d1u1mce87gyfbn.cloudfront.net/media/screenshot/winston-screenshot-007.jpg</fanart>
  <summary>Winston wields impressive inventions—a jump pack, electricity-blasting Tesla Cannon, portable shield projector and more—with literal gorilla strength.
  A super-intelligent, genetically engineered gorilla, Winston is a brilliant scientist and a champion for humanity's potential.

The Horizon Lunar Colony was established as a first step for humanity's renewed exploration of space. Among its residents was a group of genetically enhanced gorillas that were intended to test the effects of prolonged habitation in space.

One gorilla displayed such rapid brain development from the gene therapy that he was taken under the wing of Dr. Harold Winston, who taught him science and inspired him with tales of human ingenuity. The young gorilla passed his days assisting with the scientists' experiments, watching the distant blue world outside his habitat window, dreaming of the endless possibilities that awaited him there.

But his life was thrown into chaos when the other gorillas led an uprising, killed the mission scientists, and claimed the colony for their own. Taking on the name of his beloved human caretaker, Winston built a makeshift rocket and escaped to Earth. There he found a new home with Overwatch, an organization that represented everything he had come to admire about humanity. Winston was finally able to live up to the heroic ideal that had been instilled in him.

Now with the fall of Overwatch, Winston has gone into seclusion, once again cut off from the world he believes in, but longing for the days of heroism to return.</summary>

####################################################################################
<item>
  <title>Winston Ability Overview</title>
  <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch/JNJ42WCOxV0</link>
  <thumbnail></thumbnail>
  <summary>
A super-intelligent, genetically engineered gorilla, Winston is a brilliant scientist and champion for humanity's potential. After spending several years working as a scientist for Overwatch, Winston has gone into seclusion since its fall, cut off from the world he believes in, longing for the days of heroism to return. 

Winston wields impressive inventions on the battlefield—including a short-ranged Tesla cannon, jump pack, and portable shield projector. But his most powerful weapon can only be unleashed by embracing his animal nature. </summary>
</item>

<item>
  <title>Overwatch - Winston Guide - Hi There! (Tips and Advice)</title>
  <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch/v72_J_FnqJM</link>
  <thumbnail></thumbnail>
  <summary>Hi there! I’m Winston! This Winston guide shows you how to best use this MASSIVE rocket powered, Tesla fuelled gorilla tank! Winston is extremely powerful, provided you engage and disengage at the right times! Oh yeah, he’s also a super-intelligent, genetically engineered gorilla.
  </summary>
</item>

<item>
  <title>WINSTON GRANDMASTER GUIDE (24 TIPS)</title>
  <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch/IjykEqIF1ds</link>
  <thumbnail></thumbnail>
  <summary>Learn to be a better Winston with these positioning tips from Super!</summary>
</item>


<item>
  <title>Winston Positioning Tips w/ Super</title>
  <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch/_Vr_JMcUCi4</link>
  <thumbnail></thumbnail>
  <summary>Learn to be a better Winston with these positioning tips from Super!
  </summary>
</item>
