<item>
    <title>Winston Ability Overview | Overwatch</title>
    <meta>
        <summary>b"Imagination is the essence of discovery: http://www.playoverwatch.com/heroes/winston\n\nA super-intelligent, genetically engineered gorilla, Winston is a brilliant scientist and champion for humanity's potential. After spending several years working as a scientist for Overwatch, Winston has gone into seclusion since its fall, cut off from the world he believes in, longing for the days of heroism to return. \n\nWinston wields impressive inventions on the battlefieldincluding a short-ranged Tesla cannon, jump pack, and portable shield projector. But his most powerful weapon can only be unleashed by embracing his animal nature. \n\nSign Up for Beta: http://bit.ly/JoinOverwatch \nLike Us on Facebook: http://www.facebook.com/playoverwatch \nFollow Us on Twitter: http://www.twitter.com/playoverwatch" </summary>
    </meta>
    <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=JNJ42WCOxV0/</link>
    <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/JNJ42WCOxV0/sddefault.jpg</thumbnail>
</item>

<item>
    <title>Overwatch - Winston Guide - Hi There! (Tips and Advice)</title>
    <meta>
        <summary>b"Hi there! Im Winston! This Winston guide shows you how to best use this MASSIVE rocket powered, Tesla fuelled gorilla tank! Winston is extremely powerful, provided you engage and disengage at the right times! Oh yeah, hes also a super-intelligent, genetically engineered gorilla.\n\n PATREON CAMPAIGN! http://www.patreon.com/unitlost\n Steam Curator Page http://store.steampowered.com/curator/2666675/\n SUBSCRIBE! https://www.youtube.com/subscription_center?add_user=unitlosttube\n http://www.unitlost.com - Join our AWESOME community forums!\n T-shirts! http://unitlost.spreadshirt.co.uk/\n Sty's Twitter https://twitter.com/unitlostgaming\n Kiri's Twitter https://twitter.com/kirioth\n Live Stream http://www.twitch.tv/unitlost" </summary>
    </meta>
    <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=v72_J_FnqJM/</link>
    <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/v72_J_FnqJM/sddefault.jpg</thumbnail>
</item>

<item>
    <title>WINSTON GRANDMASTER GUIDE (24 TIPS)</title>
    <meta>
        <summary>b'My first crack at a hero guide in Overwatch, hopefully you can learn something from it. :)\n\nJoin my discord! https://discord.gg/4D8ShQz\nI have a twitter! https://www.twitter.com/Agonius1\n\nSong #2: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=8er4CQCxPRQ' </summary>
    </meta>
    <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=IjykEqIF1ds/</link>
    <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/IjykEqIF1ds/sddefault.jpg</thumbnail>
</item>

<item>
    <title>Winston Positioning Tips w/ Super</title>
    <meta>
        <summary>b'Learn to be a better Winston with these positioning tips from Super!' </summary>
    </meta>
    <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=_Vr_JMcUCi4/</link>
    <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/_Vr_JMcUCi4/sddefault.jpg</thumbnail>
</item>

<item>
    <title>Overwatch: Advanced Winston Guide - MAXIMUM MONKEY!</title>
    <meta>
        <summary>b"Overwatch's Winston has been creeping back into the meta and for this advanced guide we break down all the do's, don'ts and big plays with gameplay examples that you can make as our favorite peanut butter enthusiast. Let us know what you think and be sure to drop a Like & Subscribe if you enjoyed!\nSubscribe here: https://www.youtube.com/c/youroverwatch?sub_confirmation=1\n\nWe are YOUR OVERWATCH:\nTwitch - https://www.twitch.tv/youroverwatch \nTwitter - https://twitter.com/youroverwatchyt\nSubscribe - http://bit.ly/2aN1OuO\n\nDiscord Server:\nhttps://discordapp.com/invite/youroverwatch\n\nFREEDO's personal channel for Overwatch esports talk and more!\nhttps://www.youtube.com/user/xfreeedo" </summary>
    </meta>
    <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=hZrkwH9sa20/</link>
    <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/hZrkwH9sa20/sddefault.jpg</thumbnail>
</item>

<item>
    <title>SMURF MONKEY - Pro Winston Gameplay Tips Guide | Overwatch Guide</title>
    <meta>
        <summary>b' Join NOW! https://ow.gameleap.com/ - Learn from Top 500 Pros and carry your games!\n\nThis Winston guide by Pro Winston Artorigold will cover tips for your gameplay. Enjoy the SMURF Monkey domination in this Overwatch guide.\n\nThanks for watching. If you have any questions or want to reach us, please send an email at support@game-leap.com and we will get back to you shortly.' </summary>
    </meta>
    <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=bMLL5VsAIag/</link>
    <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/bMLL5VsAIag/sddefault.jpg</thumbnail>
</item>

<item>
    <title>WINSTON ... For Noobs</title>
    <meta>
        <summary>b"Winston, the loveable Gorilla Scientist from Space, is my favorite Overwatch hero. SO I'm here to help you know this hero inside and out. Here is the most comprehensive guide you'll ever need AKA WINSTON FOR NOOBS\n\nSUPPORT ME ON PATREON: https://www.patreon.com/TheMacroShow\n\nWatch me stream on Twitch!\nTWITCH: https://www.twitch.tv/TheMacroShow\n\nFollow me on social media:\nTWITTER: https://twitter.com/TheMacroShow\nINSTA: https://instagram.com/TheMacroShow\n\nThumbnail art by @nesskian check him out: http://nesskain.tumblr.com/\nIntro song: DJ Quads - For A While\n\n#winston #overwatch #macro" </summary>
    </meta>
    <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=iJ7ulblP7Ss/</link>
    <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/iJ7ulblP7Ss/sddefault.jpg</thumbnail>
</item>

<item>
    <title>Top 500 Guide To Winston</title>
    <meta>
        <summary>b'This is a guide to playing winston, done by Flats a Top 500 Main Tank @ https://www.twitch.tv/flats_ow Winston juggle video link https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=MqUj9BSMois&t=2s\n\nI hope this can help you improve your Winston!\nfor updates my  Twitter is https://twitter.com/Flats_Ow\n\nEdits done by Andrew Kiklis/DandyKnoxville' </summary>
    </meta>
    <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=dVr6sdgckdM/</link>
    <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/dVr6sdgckdM/sddefault.jpg</thumbnail>
</item>

<item>
    <title>WINSTON: Tips and Tricks to Improve | Overwatch Guide</title>
    <meta>
        <summary>b' Join NOW! https://ow.gameleap.com/ - Learn from Top 500 Pros and carry your games!\n\nThis Overwatch Winston guide covers 4 tips and tricks to improve your Winston play in minutes! \n\nThanks for watching. If you have any questions or want to reach us, please send an email at support@game-leap.com and we will get back to you shortly.' </summary>
    </meta>
    <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=bxeECHNnCsU/</link>
    <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/bxeECHNnCsU/sddefault.jpg</thumbnail>
</item>

<item>
    <title>1 WINSTON TIP for EVERY HERO ft. xQc</title>
    <meta>
        <summary>b"This is how one of the best Winston's in the world (#1 peak) xQc deals with every hero matchup. xQc explains some tips and tricks vs all 25 heroes in the game of Overwatch including butt jumps and counter movement mechanics.\n\nFOLLOW xQc:\nhttps://twitch.tv/xqcow\nhttps://www.youtube.com/xqcow\n\n\nTwitch  https://twitch.tv/KarQ (Stream 5x weekly)\nMerch  https://teespring.com/stores/karq  \nDiscord  https://discord.gg/karq\nTwitter  https://twitter.com/KarQGames\nInstagram  http://instagram.com/KarQGames\nFacebook  https://www.facebook.com/KarQGames/\n\n\n Music Used:\n\n Otis McDonald - Scarlet Fire https://youtu.be/8yOskhDn468\n Rob Gasser - Happy [NCS Release] https://youtu.be/f1bsZkXP24k" </summary>
    </meta>
    <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=QYENCtK3RQE/</link>
    <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/QYENCtK3RQE/sddefault.jpg</thumbnail>
</item>

<item>
    <title>How GRANDMASTER Players DESTROY With WINSTON | XQC - Overwatch Season 7 Competitive Guide</title>
    <meta>
        <summary>b'----------------------------------------------------------------\nThis video was sponsored by Guilded. Find out more about the best Overwatch LFG around, plus a chance at a $50 Blizzard Card giveaway here: https://www.guilded.gg/JoeKingYT\n----------------------------------------------------------------\n\n\nToday we are back again trying a top 500 tip Winston video because I think its fun and people just love Winston it seems. Today we are talking about how the grandmaster Winston player can carry his competitive games in season 7 overwatch competitive ranked mode. Going over some Winston season 7 tips and guide or whatever you want to call it. thanks! \n\n\n\n\nMore Videos! : https://www.youtube.com/playlist?list=PLefC4eOMnbRF5Xm7uCjfU73bh0ybup9Df\n\n\n\nGameplay: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=vuQYDAersGE\nThumbnail:https://orig00.deviantart.net/87bf/f/2016/128/d/d/winston___overwatch__fanart__by_asteltainn-da1r7az.jpg\n-----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------\n\n\n\n======================================================================\n\nTIPS I WROTE DOWN FROM THE VIDEO:\n-You need to play winston in a dive comp, and if you dive well you can kill a slow push mercy comp\n-playing winston is more about knowing where to be and when to be there over mechanics\n-with zarya on your team push up fruther than you wuld think\n-dont be afraid to get into the backline, but make sure you have an escape and dont waste jump\n-focus the mercy, but if she escapes dont waste jump chasing unless you up many people\n-Use your buble after you have taken a bit of damage so your healers get some ult charge\n-Callout when the mercy goes in too far, and tell people you are going ham\n-to finish tracer and genji make sure to melee,\n-Dont be afraid to use your ult to stall or just to get in to finish a low hp support\n-make sure to push up as much as possible to keep them staggered\n\n-if you think you may get traped by anything, just start walking backwards\n-Your shield can hep waste a lot of abilities, like the meis iceicle\n-wait around walls to get behind the enmy team, if you have ult there isnt much to fear\n-hit people in ult towards walls to combo or towards the other rim\n-you can never beat roadhog in 1v1, but you can stall a lot of time wlaking through your shiled\n-Use your jump to pick up healthpacks if you are about to die\n-Callout to go in the second you get a pick\n-Use to push reaper away from your team, or to tank mcree ult shots\n-Reapers again counters you, but if you push up with shild and make him overextend you can win\n\n======================================================================\n\n\n\n\n\nWhat is overwatch?: Well overwatch is Blizzards new take on the fps genre. In this game you choose a hero or "Class" to take on enemies, push payloads, and take control points. The point of the game is to beat the other team over and it is indeed a whole bunch of fun to play. The game includes 27 heroes so far and Is a blast to play. In this video I mostly go over playing it in a commentary type of manner, and these types of videos will usually be overwatch live commentaries or overwatch group commentaries. As well expect a few guides of this game in the future and some box openings as well. Anyways, hope you enjoy blizzards new hit!\'\n\nWho is JoeKing aka me. Im a overwatch youtuber that likes to talk about character updates, how to get better, and the competitive community. Trying to help you get better at overwatch and entertain at the same time hopefully. How GRANDMASTER Players DESTORY with Winston - Overwatch Top 500 PRO Tricks Overwatch - 20 TricksWinston Grandmasters ABUSE That You Don\'t! Some tips and tricks to master Winston! Overwatch - 7 OP Tips and Tricks Grandmaster Players use every game! Winston overwatch, Winston guide top 500 tips and tricks  Winston master gameplay, how Winston is played, shadowburn gameplay Winston overwatch competitive esports vod grandmaster Winston tricks grandmaster top 500 Winston, overwatch top 700 Winston esports vod Winston esports gameplay, grandmaster Winston tricks top 500 tricks tips, how to play Winston, Winston season 7, overwatch competitive season 7 Winston, Winston season 7 offense, Winston season 7 defense, overwatch season 7 Winston guide       overwatch,Winston tricks,Tricks Winston Grandmasters ABUSE That You Don\'t,Tricks Winston Grandmasters ABUSE That You Don\'t overwatch,overwatch Tricks Winston Grandmasters ABUSE That You Don\'t,tricks grandmasters abuse that you dont,overwatch tricks grandmasters abuse that you dont,grandmaster tricks overwatch,Winston grandmaster,Winston top 500 trick,How GRANDMASTER Players DESTROY with Winston,Winston season 7 competitive,Winston vod,grandmaster, Winston seagull, seagull Winston, best Winston, strongest Winston, best Winston player, overwatch seagull\n\n\n\nTitle:How GRANDMASTER Players DESTROY With Winston | xqc - Overwatch Season 7 Competitive Guide Tips' </summary>
    </meta>
    <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=_4X7TBh1DfM/</link>
    <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/_4X7TBh1DfM/sddefault.jpg</thumbnail>
</item>

<item>
    <title>Overwatch Coaching - HARDSTUCK BRONZE WINSTON?! [OverAnalyzed]</title>
    <meta>
        <summary>b'Overwatch Winston coaching! JOIN THE UNIT LOST DISCORD http://discord.gg/unitlost\nOverwatch Winston coaching! Season 8 Winston tips and advice! Welcome to OverAnalyzed! In this series, we as a community help our fellow players with tips and advice on how to become better players! Good Aim, Bad Positioning t-shirt! http://bit.ly/ulstore\n\n HyperX - CHECK THEM OUT! http://hyperx.gg/AlphaUnitLost [AD]\n UNIT LOST STORE! http://bit.ly/ulstore\n Discord JOIN NOW! http://discord.gg/unitlost  \n PATREON CAMPAIGN! http://www.patreon.com/unitlost\n Twitter https://twitter.com/unitlostgaming\n Live Stream http://www.twitch.tv/unitlost\n http://www.unitlost.com - Join our AWESOME community forums!' </summary>
    </meta>
    <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=fNp0Vx73SHM/</link>
    <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/fNp0Vx73SHM/sddefault.jpg</thumbnail>
</item>

<item>
    <title>Jayne Reviews: Gold Winston</title>
    <meta>
        <summary>b'Winston main tank VOD review. \n\nFollow me:\nTwitch: https://www.twitch.tv/Jayne\nTwitter: https://twitter.com/AskJayne\n\nJoin us on Discord!\nhttps://discord.gg/6guPUDF' </summary>
    </meta>
    <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=6p_QfaNpnbw/</link>
    <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/6p_QfaNpnbw/sddefault.jpg</thumbnail>
</item>

<item>
    <title>REINHARDT GRANDMASTER GUIDE (20 TIPS)</title>
    <meta>
        <summary>b'Abilities: 0:51\nMechanics: 2:23\nReinhardt Mirror: 6:57\n20 Tips: 9:07\n\nDiscord: https://discord.gg/7pHwjdn' </summary>
    </meta>
    <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=0JJ76MUXmew/</link>
    <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/0JJ76MUXmew/sddefault.jpg</thumbnail>
</item>

<item>
    <title>Overwatch In Depth: Winston Guide</title>
    <meta>
        <summary>b'Overwatch Teamp Comp: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=-u9xnImVgBo\nWinston is one the least picked heroes in Overwatch. Kind of a shame really because I think he a great hero that just isn\'t used properly. Winston is a tank that doesn\'t really tank but flanks instead. Today\'s video is going to go over all of Winston\'s stats and some of his secrets.\nMy Twitter: http://www.twitter.com/drift0r\n\nI capture console gameplay with The Elgato HD60 because it\'s the most professional device on the market for 1080p 60fps console capture.\nElgato website: http://bit.ly/LCO57Q \nAmazon Link: http://amzn.to/1y6Y759\n\nNEW DRIFT0R SHIRTS! http://www.coregamewear.com/drift0r\n\nI game exclusively on the Netduma R1 because it is best gaming router I have ever used.\nNetduma website: http://www.netduma.com/\nUse code "DRFT" for $10 off!\n\nI use ASTRO Headsets for all my gaming. They are very high quality gaming headsets. I also have a 5% off link with them. Clicking this link automatically gives you 5% off of everything ASTRO: http://bit.ly/1NIzdQi' </summary>
    </meta>
    <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=P4j9xx-Jh_I/</link>
    <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/P4j9xx-Jh_I/sddefault.jpg</thumbnail>
</item>

<item>
    <title>WINSTON GUIDE | HOW TO BECOME T500 | AceOFSpades - PART 1</title>
    <meta>
        <summary>b'https://www.twitch.tv/AceOFSpadesOW\nhttps://twitter.com/AceOFSpadesOW\nJoin my discord community for the latest updates!\nhttps://discord.gg/GfFWEVt' </summary>
    </meta>
    <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=7JmTv5rjsfI/</link>
    <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/7JmTv5rjsfI/sddefault.jpg</thumbnail>
</item>

<item>
    <title>HOW TO USE PRIMAL RAGE & JUGGLE - WINSTON GUIDE -- AceOFSpades</title>
    <meta>
        <summary>b'https://www.twitch.tv/AceOFSpadesOW\nhttps://twitter.com/AceOFSpadesOW\nJoin my discord community for the latest updates!\nhttps://discord.gg/GfFWEVt' </summary>
    </meta>
    <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=NoAC3qHuSNc/</link>
    <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/NoAC3qHuSNc/sddefault.jpg</thumbnail>
</item>

<item>
    <title>Jayne Reviews: Grandmaster Winston on Watchpoint: Gibraltar</title>
    <meta>
        <summary>b"You can never have too much Winston in your life can you? We're looking at a Grand Master ranked Winston. This player has been a top 500 D.Va in previous seasons. \n\nWant to have your own Gameplay Reviewed? \nRecord your gameplay. 720p or better video. Good audio.\nUpload it to YouTube or record on Twitch. \nThen go here: https://jayne.as.me\n\nFollow me:\nTwitch: https://www.twitch.tv/Jayne\nTwitter: https://twitter.com/AskJayne" </summary>
    </meta>
    <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=xASPUeC4FJQ/</link>
    <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/xASPUeC4FJQ/sddefault.jpg</thumbnail>
</item>

<item>
    <title>Overwatch - Top Five Tips For Winston - HOW TO BECOME A PRO WINSTON!?</title>
    <meta>
        <summary>b'Thank you guys for all the recent support!!\nCan we get 20 likes on this video!?\n\nWinston is one of the best winston characters but countered by many such as roadhog and reaper. But play him well and you can avoid these counters. He may be one of the most fun overwatch heroes but he is also very impactful. \n\nHope you guys enjoyed!!! \nSubscribe because it helps be so much, every single sub means a lot!' </summary>
    </meta>
    <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=kwc16cUWYbU/</link>
    <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/kwc16cUWYbU/sddefault.jpg</thumbnail>
</item>

<item>
    <title>Overwatch | Master Winston ft Numlocked - Advanced Guide</title>
    <meta>
        <summary>b'Numlocked joins us again for Master Winston and gives us his professional tips and tricks playing our favourite scientist. Winston is finding more use in dive comps and the meta as a whole so we wanted to get an advanced guide set up to go over him! \n\n__\n\n Need a new headset? Buy this one and support us! http://hyperx.gg/StingerOWC [AD]\n\n Send in your own clips: http://goo.gl/forms/JsizriSpRL\n__\n\nFollow us!\nTwitch: http://www.twitch.tv/overwatchcentral\nTwitter: https://twitter.com/OWCentral\nGoogle+: https://plus.google.com/+OverwatchCentral\n__\n\nMusic: Epidemic Sound\n\nApproaching Nirvana - Super Happy Fun Time\nhttp://youtube.com/user/approachingnirvana\nApproaching Nirvana on iTunes: https://itunes.apple.com/us/artist/approaching-nirvana/id313583565\n__\n\nThanks for watching! #Overwatch' </summary>
    </meta>
    <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=iUDkcQwcsHk/</link>
    <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/iUDkcQwcsHk/sddefault.jpg</thumbnail>
</item>

<item>
    <title>SMURF WINSTON PT 2 - Pro Monkey Gameplay Tips Teamfight Analysis Guide | Overwatch Guide</title>
    <meta>
        <summary>b' Join NOW! https://ow.gameleap.com/ - Learn from Top 500 Pros and carry your games!\n\nArtorigold goes over SMURF WINSTON PT 2 - Pro Monkey Gameplay Tips Teamfight Analysis Guide | Overwatch Guide\n\nThanks for watching. If you have any questions or want to reach us, please send an email at support@game-leap.com and we will get back to you shortly.' </summary>
    </meta>
    <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=xyXZgnyka2w/</link>
    <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/xyXZgnyka2w/sddefault.jpg</thumbnail>
</item>

<item>
    <title>SMURF WINSTON - Pro Gorilla GOD Gameplay Tips Teamfight Analysis Guide | Overwatch Guide</title>
    <meta>
        <summary>b' Join NOW! https://ow.gameleap.com/ - Learn from Top 500 Pros and carry your games!\n\nSMURF WINSTON - Pro Gorilla GOD Gameplay Tips Teamfight Analysis Guide | Overwatch Guide\n\nThanks for watching. If you have any questions or want to reach us, please send an email at support@game-leap.com and we will get back to you shortly.' </summary>
    </meta>
    <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=5sHw1W3oF0c/</link>
    <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/5sHw1W3oF0c/sddefault.jpg</thumbnail>
</item>

<item>
    <title>Jayne Reviews: Master Tank (Console)</title>
    <meta>
        <summary>b"We always get requests for more console gameplay and we aim to please. We're looking at a Master console tank player. \n\nWant to have your own Gameplay Reviewed? \nRecord your gameplay. 720p or better video. Good audio.\nUpload it to YouTube or record on Twitch. \nThen go here: https://jayne.as.me\n\nFollow me:\nTwitch: https://www.twitch.tv/Jayne\nTwitter: https://twitter.com/AskJayne\n\nJoin us on Discord!\nhttps://discord.gg/6guPUDF" </summary>
    </meta>
    <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Z65_osQHah0/</link>
    <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/Z65_osQHah0/sddefault.jpg</thumbnail>
</item>

<item>
    <title>Overwatch | How To DOMINATE With New Dva! - T500 Gameplay Coaching</title>
    <meta>
        <summary>b"New style of video. Lowkeynerd is one of the best Dva's on ladder currently. We breakdown his gameplay and talk about how to properly utilise the new iteration of the Korean Queen.\n CHECK OUT THE HYPERX CLOUD ALPHA http://hyperx.gg/AlphaOverwatchCentral \n__\nFollow us!\nTwitter: https://twitter.com/OWCentral\nTwitch - Mysca: http://www.twitch.tv/mysca_\nTwitch - Ryan: http://www.twitch.tv/ryancentral_\n__\n\nMusic: Epidemic Sound\n\nApproaching Nirvana - Super Happy Fun Time\nhttp://youtube.com/user/approachingnirvana\nApproaching Nirvana on iTunes: https://itunes.apple.com/us/artist/approaching-nirvana/id313583565\n__\n\nThanks for watching! #Overwatch" </summary>
    </meta>
    <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=HMrvVird7Ng/</link>
    <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/HMrvVird7Ng/sddefault.jpg</thumbnail>
</item>

<item>
    <title>XQC - GRANDMASTER WINSTON GAMEPLAY TIPS | How To Improve As Winston Guide - Overwatch Season 7</title>
    <meta>
        <summary>b"----------------------------------------------------------------\nCHECK THE SERVICE OUT HERE: \nhttps://playvig.com/\n\nAnd if you have questions or concerns, check this out.\nhttps://support.playvig.com/hc/en-us/requests/new\n----------------------------------------------------------------\n\n\nToday we are back again trying a top 500 tip Winston video because I think its fun and people just love Winston it seems. Today we are talking about how the grandmaster Winston player can carry his competitive games in season 7 overwatch competitive ranked mode guide for overwatch season 7 placement matches and overwatch season 7 changes. Going over some Winston season 7 tips and guide or whatever you want to call it. I hope that these tips can help to have you guys learn how to improve as Winston and hope this works as a mini Winston guide tip trick thing for all that want to improve as her. Anyways, thanks! \n\n\n\n\nMore Videos! : https://www.youtube.com/playlist?list=PLefC4eOMnbRF5Xm7uCjfU73bh0ybup9Df\n\n\n\nGameplay: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=zD7NZBDatDA\nThumbnail: https://i.pinimg.com/736x/a2/72/e7/a272e7385043dcc59106d599bbe6e104--overwatch-winston-pc-online.jpg\n-----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------\n\n\n\n======================================================================\n\nTIPS I WROTE DOWN FROM THE VIDEO:\n-winston isnt a must pick anymore, but dive comps still beat most other comps if played correctly\n-solo tank winston works ok on KOTH Maps, so if you cant get a second tank its ok\n-he doesnt instantly dive in on the first fight, plays next to his team and peels\n-cant face tank reaper so he backs up, this allows his dps to deal with reaper and he reingages\n-you dont need to kill the reaper, just take all of his attention\n-he doesnt really jump in at the start of fights, usually just shield and tanks around corners, then reingages\n-doesnt chase people, just hits the closest person and lets his supports stay safe around him\n-jumping in the backline while winning a fight can be good, but jumping in at the beginng is unsafe\n-if the enemy team isnt deathballed at any time, call out to your team to go in with ults and DIVEE\n\n-jumps to high ground to force others off of it, not for his dmaage\n-every time his team loses a fight he tells them to save ults and regroup. Simple but effective\n-he shoots whoever is nearest, unless he sees a mercy by herself. Then take the chance\n-Dont ever dive in 1v6. Wait until they are split \n-on this much more open map he focuses on diving backline than protecting his own, hard to protect here\n-try to land on your enemy and melee then zap. Gives winston some burst\n-dont ult whenever you are on low hp, if a fight is lost just save it\n\n-get ahead of your team with shift to get corners first\n-enemies have a lucio and xqc doesnt, he needs to play a lot slower\n-hide inside your shield vs dps until you get help, if you dont get help just JUMP AWAY DONT FIGHT\n-whenever he changes target he melees them to get that small burst\n-use the health packs with your jump to relieve pressure on support healing\n-to beat a winston 1v1 you need to melee all the time\n-when genji ults, just try to kill him or just kill his backline. People ignore the backline when engaging\n\n\n\n\n======================================================================\n\n\n\nhow to get better, and the competitive community. Trying to help you get better at overwatch and entertain at the same time hopefully. How GRANDMASTER Players DESTORY with Winston - Overwatch Top 500 PRO Tricks Overwatch - 20 TricksWinston Grandmasters ABUSE That You Don't! Some tips and tricks to master Winston! Overwatch - 7 OP Tips and Tricks Grandmaster Players use every game! Winston overwatch, Winston guide top 500 tips and tricks  Winston master gameplay, how Winston is played, shadowburn gameplay Winston overwatch competitive esports vod grandmaster Winston tricks grandmaster top 500 Winston, overwatch top 700 Winston esports vod Winston esports gameplay, grandmaster Winston tricks top 500 tricks tips, how to play Winston, Winston season 7, overwatch competitive season 7 Winston, Winston season 7 offense, Winston season 7 defense, overwatch season 7 Winston guide       overwatch,Winston tricks,Tricks Winston Grandmasters ABUSE That You Don't,Tricks Winston Grandmasters ABUSE That You Don't overwatch,overwatch Tricks Winston Grandmasters ABUSE That You Don't,tricks grandmasters abuse that you dont,overwatch tricks grandmasters abuse that you dont,grandmaster tricks overwatch,Winston grandmaster,Winston top 500 trick,How GRANDMASTER Players DESTROY with Winston,Winston season 7 competitive,Winston vod,grandmaster, Winston seagull, seagull Winston, best Winston, strongest Winston, best Winston player, overwatch seagull\n\n\n\nTitle:GRANDMASTER Winston GAMEPLAY TIPS | How To Improve As Winston Guide - Overwatch Season 7 Competitive Tricks" </summary>
    </meta>
    <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ZaCpgDxcURI/</link>
    <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/ZaCpgDxcURI/sddefault.jpg</thumbnail>
</item>

<item>
    <title>How to be a Winston GOD just like xQc | Overwatch Guide | Pro Winston Tips and Tricks</title>
    <meta>
        <summary>b' Join NOW! https://ow.gameleap.com/ - Learn from Top 500 Pros and carry your games!\n\nArtorigold goes over How to be a Winston GOD just like xQc | Overwatch Guide | Pro Winston Tips and Tricks\n\nThanks for watching. If you have any questions or want to reach us, please send an email at support@game-leap.com and we will get back to you shortly.' </summary>
    </meta>
    <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=6ALLeCL6qJE/</link>
    <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/6ALLeCL6qJE/sddefault.jpg</thumbnail>
</item>

<item>
    <title>The Holy Guide of how to play Winston</title>
    <meta>
        <summary>b"I'll show you how to become king of the jungle. Lets strap it on and learn how to play Winston, the scientist. Your enemies wont know what hit them. \n\n\nBe cool and subscribe, you won't be disappointed: https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCscG74HJwH4ZJrEYnnp7g_w?sub_confirmation=1" </summary>
    </meta>
    <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=lDmcMQFn46E/</link>
    <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/lDmcMQFn46E/sddefault.jpg</thumbnail>
</item>

<item>
    <title>Jayne Reviews: Platinum Main Tank</title>
    <meta>
        <summary>b"Good day to you all. We're back to review more Platinum Main Tank play. Also have you heard of the contest we are running? Take a peek at the full rules here:\n\nhttps://www.reddit.com/r/Competitiveoverwatch/comments/8mqsdd/amateur_overwatch_coaching_and_analysis_contest/\n\nWant to have your own Gameplay Reviewed?\n\nTwitch subscribers can submit a 720p30fps recording of their gameplay, with good audio, and no background music on Discord. Submissions from YouTube and Twitch are both accepted.\n\nWhich are VODs are accepted is based on video quality, scheduled guests, as well as the uniqueness of the recording. Footage from scrims, PUGs, and tournaments are welcome - and Console, too!\n\nSocials:\nTwitch: https://www.twitch.tv/Jayne\nTwitter: https://twitter.com/AskJayne\n\nJoin our Discord!\nhttps://discord.gg/SdzAcBb" </summary>
    </meta>
    <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=dcQbvhxBFi8/</link>
    <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/dcQbvhxBFi8/sddefault.jpg</thumbnail>
</item>

