
################################################################################
  <thumbnail>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PiDiaries/wow/master/sprays/zarya.png</thumbnail>
  <fanart>https://d1u1mce87gyfbn.cloudfront.net/media/screenshot/zarya-screenshot-004.jpg</fanart>
  <summary>Deploying powerful personal barriers that convert incoming damage into energy for her massive Particle Cannon, Zarya is an invaluable asset on the front lines of any battle.
  Aleksandra Zaryanova is one of the world's strongest women, a celebrated athlete who sacrificed personal glory to protect her family, friends, and country in a time of war.

Aleksandra was born in a remote Siberian village that was on the front lines of the Omnic Crisis, which began some thirty years ago. Although Russian forces defeated the robots and shut down their omnium, the region was devastated by the conflict. Only a child at the time, Aleksandra was surrounded by the post-war destruction, and as she grew older, she swore that she would gain the strength to help her people recover.

Focusing on weightlifting and bodybuilding, Aleksandra was identified by the national athletics program as a potential star. She trained extensively, moving up the ranks while representing her country, and was expected to shatter longstanding records in the upcoming world championships.

But on the eve of the tournament, an attack came from the long-dormant Siberian omnium, and her village was thrust into war once again. Aleksandra immediately withdrew from the competition and rushed home to enlist in the local defense forces, sacrificing the life of fame and fortune she might have had.

Now she serves—a symbol to some, a stalwart fellow soldier to others. But for Aleksandra, it is a chance to use her great strength to protect the ones she loves. </summary>

####################################################################################
<item>
  <title>Zarya Ability Overview</title>
  <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch/gTcKbsKDkWk</link>
  <thumbnail></thumbnail>
  <summary>Zarya is one of the world's strongest women, a celebrated athlete who sacrificed personal glory when her home was thrust into war. Now she uses her great strength to protect her family, friends, and country.

Deploying powerful personal barriers that convert incoming damage into energy for her particle cannon, Zarya is an invaluable asset on the front lines of any battle. When the enemy forces rally, a well-placed graviton surge can turn the tide of battle, drawing foes into its field and leaving them vulnerable.</summary>
</item>

<item>
  <title>Overwatch - Zarya Guide - The Reckless Russian! (Tips and Advice)</title>
  <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch/OtdbIaG4pAs</link>
  <thumbnail></thumbnail>
  <summary>Zarya tips and advice! Zarya is the big Russian lady with an even bigger particle cannon! She’s a no nonsense frontline brawler tank that just begs to take all the damage to charge up that massive weapon! She’s excellent for breaking defensive positions and supporting squishy characters. Not to mention she has awesome crowd control with her ultimate, Graviton Surge!
  </summary>
</item>
